What a weird dream.
My name is Iwatani Naofumi.
I'm a second-year college student,
and somewhat of an otaku.
It's bright out.
When my kid brother started heading down the
wrong path, I helped bring him back in line,
and so I was given the privilege of living
at home, allowance included.
With no need to work part-time,
I got to enjoy an idyllic otaku life.
That said, I certainly wasn't
one of your so-called shut-ins.
When I ran out of money to spend,
I would go to the library like this to
browse through light novels.
I was a completely run-of-the-mill otaku
leading a completely ordinary life.
Ow!
What the hell?
But it all changed when
I picked up this book.
"The Records of the Four Great Weapons"?
"The Waves of Apocalyptic Catastrophe...
To save the world from them, four heroes
will be summoned from another world."
It's sorta like a light novel.
"Each of the four heroes
wield a characteristic weapon:
a sword, a spear, a bow, or a shield."
Uh, I'm pretty sure a shield
is more like armor than a weapon.
The heroine isn't showing up at all.
This princess seems... kinda slutty.
Huh... Each of the heroes seems
impressive and pretty damn cool.
I guess all four of them
are the protagonists.
The sword, spear, and bow
heroes all get spotlights,
and even the shield hero has a story...
What the heck?
We did it! It worked!
Where am I?
O brave heroes, please save our world!
Excuse me?
Who are these guys?
And where am I, anyway?
The hell is this?
A shield?
O brave heroes, please save our world!
Seriously?
What do you mean by that?
There is a long and complicated
story behind this,
but we've summoned you Four Great
Heroes here using an ancient ritual.
"Four Great"? So he thinks the
four of us are heroes of legend?
Our world teeters on the
brink of destruction.
We beg you, O brave heroes! Please lend your aid!
I guess I could hear you out, at least.
I refuse.
Yeah, agreed.
We can go back to our world, right?
We'll talk about your problems after that.
Don't you guys feel any guilt at all for
bringing us here without our consent?
And if you throw us out as soon as peace
is restored, we'd have worked for nothing.
How willing are you to accommodate us?
Depending on your answer, we might end
up becoming your enemies instead.
Not only are these guys
taking all this in stride,
they've already started to
demand respect and rewards!
F-First, we'd like you to have an audience
with the king of our country, Melromarc.
You can negotiate your reward
after that, so please...
Fine, I guess.
I suppose we could consider their offer.
Not like our demands are gonna change,
no matter who we talk to.
Yeesh! Could these guys
be any more confident?
We really are in another world, huh?
We sure are.
Such a pleasant breeze...
It's like the sales pitches
in all those overseas travel brochures.
Wait, you've never been
outside of Japan before?
Going by the breeze outside,
this place probably has your
standard Mediterranean climate.
Yeah, yeah. Excuse me for my lack
of knowledge and vocabulary.
So these men are the Four Great
Heroes of ancient legend?
I am the king of Melromarc,
Aultcray Melromarc XXXII.
Heroes,
name yourselves.
Amaki Ren, sixteen years old, high schooler.
I'm Kitamura Motoyasu. Twenty-one,
and a college student.
I suppose I'm up next.
Kawasumi Itsuki, seventeen years
old, and a high schooler.
And lastly, me. I'm...
I see.
Ren, Motoyasu, and Itsuki, huh?
K-king, aren't you forgetting me?
Hmm? Oh, sorry.
"Yo, King"? You mustn't be so disrespectful.
"His Highness", then?
That's too formal, no?
"King" is fine.
Well, anyway.
My name is Iwatani Naofumi. I'm
twenty, and a college student.
Now...
I suppose I owe you an explanation first.
You're ignoring me?
My country, Melromarc, and the entire
world is headed toward destruction.
I'm still pissed off at how the king's
treating me, but here's the long story short:
This world has an apocalyptic prophecy,
which mentions "Waves" that
will lead the world to ruin
and reportedly appear in,
well, several waves.
Unless the calamities wrought
by the Waves are thwarted,
the world will end.
Each country here has an
ancient dragon hourglass
which can predict the arrival of the Waves.
The first Wave washed over this
country before we were summoned.
Local knights and traveling adventurers
somehow managed to fend it off,
but the following Waves
will be even more potent.
The hourglass's sands will keep trickling
as long as the Waves keep coming...
Currently, less than a month
remains until the second Wave.
We underestimated the prophesied Waves.
We realized once we actually experienced one
that only the Four Great
Heroes could stand against them.
And so, we followed the
legend and summoned you four.
We have no time to lose!
Wait a sec.
Isn't this the exact same story
as the one in that book?
We get the gist of it now.
Anyway, surely you didn't summon us
expecting us to save you for free.
Of course, once you repel all the Waves,
we shall reward you handsomely.
Will you, now? Well,
as long as we have your word.
We'll work with you provided
you don't turn on us.
But don't think for a moment
that you can tame us.
Exactly. We can't have
you taking us lightly.
R-Right...
God, these guys are so high-and-mighty.
I trust we have an agreement.
Then, heroes, you should
all check your statuses.
Wait, what's a status?
Uh...
What's wrong with you guys?
It should've been the first thing
you noticed in this world.
Oh, get over yourself! Quit acting
like you know everything!
Don't you see an icon in
the corner of your field of vision?
Huh?
You're right. There it is.
Try focusing on it.
Like this?
"Level 1"?
That's worrying.
Yeah. No telling if we can fight like this.
What's all this, anyway?
Status Magic, an ability
exclusive to the heroes.
So what are we supposed to do?
You must leave on an adventure
to develop and upgrade the legendary
weapons that you have equipped.
They aren't strong out of the box?
Mine isn't even a weapon in the first place.
Couldn't we just wield other
weapons until these are usable?
We can figure that out as we go.
Anyway, it looks like we
ought to train ourselves.
We'll have to level up as much as we can.
Then if the four of us form a party...
One moment, heroes.
You will each recruit and
adventure separately.
And why is that?
It is said that the legendary weapons
repel one another by nature.
Problems may arise in the case of the wielders of the legendary weapons
fighting alongside one another. Working seperately is recommended.
If you work together, it apparently
hinders their development.
He's telling the truth, huh?
And the weapons are translating all verbal
and visual information into Japanese for us.
The sun is about to set.
Rest up tonight, and set forth tomorrow.
In the meantime, we'll gather the best
of the best to form your parties.
We've prepared rooms for you.
Please come this way.
I hear the Four Great
Heroes have been summoned.
All of them, in this country?
Are they sure about this?
Which means the Shield Hero is...
I guess you get special treatment
when you're heroes of legend.
The girl who showed us here
was a cutie pie, too.
And our dinner was sumptuous,
though it did taste unusual.
This is kinda like a game, isn't it?
You mean it is one.
It's exactly like Emerald Online.
Huh? What's that game?
Are you serious? It's super famous!
What are you talking about?
This isn't some online game.
It's a world out of a console game.
It's called Dimension Web.
You're wrong. It's a VRMMO.
It's pretty much the exact
same as Brave Star Online.
Let's sort out the information we have.
Ren, can we take "VRMMO" literally?
Yeah.
You guys get what means too, right?
I think a sci-fi game I'm familiar
with explored the concept.
I've read about them in LNs, yeah.
Just to be sure, let's check
our general knowledge.
Who's the person on the thousand yen bill?
One, two...
Yawara Gotaro.
Yuda Masato.
Kodaka Enichi.
Noguchi Hideyo.
Who?!
What won Buzzword of the Year last year?!
Your favorite voice actors?
Which countries won World War II?
Who's the Prime Minister?
It seems we're all from
different versions of Japan.
Looks like it. They sound nothing alike.
So there are parallel world
Japans out there too, huh?
I thought we might just
be from different eras,
but I guess not, if they're so different.
And I can't believe all three of you played
games that are just like this world.
Why am I the only one
unfamiliar with this stuff?
Huh? What is it?
W-Well, I just thought it might
because you're the Shield Hero.
Oh, you too?
It's only natural.
Wh-What're you guys talking about?
Is there something wrong with the shield?
All right, let the expert get
you up to speed on the basics.
As far as I know, the Shielder,
the class that specializes in the shield...
Yeah?
... is one for losers.
No high-level players choose it.
No!
How about in your worlds?
Sorry.
Likewise.
How's the terrain here?
Very similar to what I'm familiar with.
Each weapon has its own ideal hunting ground,
so let's spread out.
Well, whatever.
If I'm weak, I can just rely on my party.
It might have girls and all, too.
The shield's role would be to thwart enemy
attacks and defend the party, right?
And while my life back home was devoid of
romance, I might just find someone here.
It'll be fine. I've been summoned
to another world, after all.
Even if I'm weak, things will work out.
All right! I'm gonna give it my all!
R-Right.
We have to set out on adventures tomorrow.
Let's head back to our rooms
and get a good night's sleep.
Do you think they have baths here?
It's quite likely you'll
have to go outdoors.
That's right.
My grand adventure begins tomorrow!
We have gathered brave warriors who will
fight the Waves with you legendary heroes.
These people will join our parties, huh?
Wow, there are some real lookers here, too.
Now, our future champions!
Time to begin your journey!
What? They're the ones choosing?!
Three... five... four...
Hey, King!
I have to admit, I wasn't expecting this.
No volunteers? He must have no charisma.
So there have been rumors.
Did something happen?
Well, rumors that the Shield Hero is ignorant
of this world have spread around town.
What?
Legend says the heroes come with a
firm understanding of our lands.
And they seem to think he
doesn't meet that criteria.
Maybe someone was eavesdropping
on our chat last night.
Seriously?
Just for that?
Sure, I may not know much, but...
That aside, Ren, you don't need five!
Gimme some of them!
I'm actually more of a loner.
If any of you can't cut it,
I'll leave you behind.
What do you make of this, Motoyasu?
Don't you think it's unfair?
I'm actually surprised that
my party is all girls, too.
It pisses me off that he doesn't
seem all that broken up about it.
It would be best to split them three each,
but if we force it, it could destroy morale.
So, what, you're telling me to go it alone?!
I'm a Shielder, you know!
The class you guys said was for losers!
How am I supposed to grow
stronger without a party?
Sir Hero!
It's her.
Would you allow me to join the Shield Hero?
Are you sure?
Yes!
F-For real?
She'll join my party?
Are there any others who wouldn't
mind joining Naofumi-dono?
I suppose we'll have to take other measures.
Naofumi-dono, you will have to
recruit for your party yourself.
A-All right.
Every month, we shall provide each
hero with the funds they require.
This time, Naofumi-dono's payment
will be higher than the others.
Here are your initial war
chests. Please accept them.
Naofumi-sama gets 800 silver coins.
The others get 600.
Use this to procure all necessary equipment
and set forth on your journey.
Yes, sir!
Later, Naofumi.
Take good care of her, you hear me?
It's sad that we can't help you,
but good luck with your recruiting.
See you again when the time comes.
Y-Yeah.
Um, Shield Hero.
My name is Myne Suphia. It is
an honor to fight with you.
I'm Iwatani Naofumi. Nice to meet you.
My pleasure!
She's so open and friendly.
And she chose to join me
when no one else would.
I've gotta keep her safe, no matter what!
Shall we get going, uh, Myne-san?
Yes, Sir Hero.
Let me show you around the
castle town to start off.
I caught a glimpse last night,
but taking a closer look really drives
it home that this is another world.
What shall we do now, Sir Hero?
Hmm, let's see...
I'd like to check out a shop that
sells weapons and armor first.
That makes sense.
With that much money, you can
buy some fine equipment.
I'll take you to a shop I trust, then.
Yeah, please do.
Sure thing! Follow me!
So cute.
Nothing beats having a
girl in your party, huh?
I wholeheartedly recommend this place.
So this is what a weapons shop is like.
Welcome.
Is this your first time in a weapons shop?
You sure know how to pick 'em.
Actually, she brought me here.
Have we met before, Miss?
Why do you look so familiar?
I've come shopping here before.
Your shop is quite famous, you know.
Ain't that nice of ya.
By the way, who's your companion
with the funny outfit?
Can't you tell, boss?
You mean you're one of the heroes?
Ah, I see you've got a shield.
You must be the dud.
Why are rumors about me
spreading like wildfire?
Whatever. I can't let it get me down.
I'm Iwatani Naofumi, the Shield Hero.
Pleased to meet you!
Naofumi, eh?
Well, if you'll be a regular, I don't give
two hoots if you wield a shield or what.
Nice to meet ya, kid!
Anyway, boss,
could you provide Sir Hero
with the equipment he needs?
Our budget is, let's see...
Around 250 silvers.
Left to right, that's iron, magic iron,
magic steel, and silver iron
in ascending order of cost.
I guarantee they're all
quality swords, though.
Wow. With one of these, even I could...
What the!
Seriously, what's going on?
I don't get it, either.
It looked like it just
flew out of your hand.
What?
A rule of the legendary weapons has been infringed:
The wielding of weapons other than the one specified
"Rule Violation"?
A hero may not hold, with intent to fight,
any weapon other than their assigned legendary weapon
What the hell?
A hero may not hold, with intent to fight,
any weapon other than their assigned legendary weapon
How am I supposed to fight
with just a shield?
Well, looks like I can't use any
weapons other than this shield.
How does that work?
It looks like any other small
shield at first glance.
Doesn't this thing come off?
I can move it around, but I can't
seem to remove it from my body.
That's so weird.
I sense a great amount
of power in this thing,
but even my appraisal magic
isn't telling me anything.
Right...
Well, thanks for showing
me something interesting.
Want to buy some armor instead?
Oh, hey.
You're starting to look the part now.
Thanks.
How much is it?
I'll give you a discount. 120 silvers.
How much would you buy it for?
Huh? Well, if it's mostly new,
I'd pay 100 silvers.
Why do you ask?
When you grow stronger,
you won't need it anymore.
So I'm asking him how much
we could sell it back for.
Makes sense.
All right. We'll take it.
Great! I'll throw in some
innerwear to show my gratitude!
Shall we head off to battle now, Sir Hero?
Y-Yeah!
Time to level up, huh?
My adventure's finally beginning!
Wow. There's no limit to
how much it can absorb.
This must be the power
of a legendary weapon.
Yeah.
It also must be why I don't feel
pain when I'm bitten.
Looks like I need a lot more fodder before
I can upgrade it to a different shield.
I see.
By the way, can we sell these
orange balloon fragments?
Yes, but only for one copper coin at most.
Looking at how Ren destroyed them,
they must be really weak monsters.
I guess that's all they're worth.
That should be enough shield fodder.
It should evolve as I level up, too.
Let's call it a day and head
back to the weapons shop.
If we buy me some new equipment,
we can go that much farther tomorrow.
Fair enough.
Equipment for the lady, huh?
Sure, you'll be much stronger
with good equipment.
Right?
This might get expensive,
so I should start haggling now.
I see our hero is a real comedian.
Eighty percent off.
Are you stupid? Twenty percent extra!
Wh-Why's it going up?
Eighty-nine percent off!
Anyone who tries to haggle without even
seeing the goods deserves to pay double!
Keep talking! Ninety percent off!
Twenty-nine percent extra!
Seriously, stop raising the price!
One hundred percent off!
That's just free, kid!
Free's fine by me!
Hup.
Boss, how much is that in total?
At sixty percent off.
Four hundred and eighty silvers with
a discount. I can't go any lower.
Uh, that'll leave us with 200 silvers...
Myne, can you downgrade a bit?
I don't know how much we'll have to spend
on inns and other living expenses yet.
It'll be fine, Sir Hero.
The stronger I am, the more
loot we'll get from monsters.
That should keep us going.
There's the otherworld trope
I've been waiting for!
F-Fine, I guess.
All right. We'll take these, boss.
Thanks a ton!
I see our hero's got a
real nose for good deals.
Thank you, Sir Hero.
By the way, boss, do you know a
place that'll buy these fragments?
There are shops for monster materials.
They'll buy most things off of ya.
Thanks.
Yum!
The food at the castle was great too,
but a pub is where you experience
real otherworld cuisine!
Take your time and really savor it.
The meadow we fought in
was over here, right?
Yes.
Tomorrow, we'll head to Lafan
Village, which lies beyond this map.
Past Lafan Village lies a dungeon
for novice adventurers.
A dungeon?
We won't make much money there, but it's
a great place for you to level up.
Oh, I see.
Now that I have new equipment,
it should be a walk in the
park with you defending me.
Thanks for all the information.
No problem.
By the way, Sir Hero,
aren't you going to drink your wine?
Oh, I'm not into alcohol.
Really? This is pretty good, you know.
I'd love to drink with you.
She's suddenly become twice as seductive!
But...
S-Sorry. I really don't like it.
Is that so? That's too bad.
That's a hero for you, I suppose.
What do you mean?
This country is a matriarchy.
No man would ever dare turn down
a drink offered by a woman.
Really? I'm not very good at
picking up on this stuff.
Don't worry about it.
I'm glad we got to discuss
our plans moving forward.
I'd like to turn in early tonight.
Is that okay?
Of course.
I'll head up after I drink some more...
Although I feel so lonely drinking alone.
H-Hey, Myne?
Thanks for joining me, a shield
hero who can't fight at all.
I turned you down tonight,
but I'll make it up to you someday.
It's totally fine.
Good night, Sir Hero.
Night.
Two hundred silvers left.
Two rooms at 30 coppers a night each,
and meals for two at five coppers each...
That leaves a little more than 199 silvers.
I'm such a stereotypical Japanese tourist,
stashing money like this.
What a day.
I wonder if that's how it truly
feels to kill a monster.
Today I was basically just popping balloons.
But man, I'm actually in another world!
I leveled up quite a bit today.
I won't let you outshine me tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, then.
Is that Motoyasu and Itsuki?
See you.
Guess I'll sleep.
Early start tomorrow and all.
Time to get some breakfast and head out!
Huh?
Gone...
It's gone!
The silvers, the chain mail,
and even my own clothes I'd
kept for a rainy day are gone!
No way...
I got robbed in my sleep?!
Big trouble, Myne! Our money
and equipment is gone!
Are you still asleep?
Wake up, Myne! We've got big trouble!
You're knights from the castle, right?
I'm glad you're here. Listen to this...
The Shield Hero, yes?
Yeah, why?
The king has issued a summons for you.
Come with us.
Huh?
That hurts!
What's going on?
Myne! You're okay!
Myne?
Yo, King!
I had all my money and equipment other than
the shield stolen while I was asleep!
Please find the culprit
Quiet, brute!
What's that for?
Myne, you poor adventurer,
could you please testify once more for us?
Th-The Shield Hero barged into my
room drunk and pinned me down...
Huh?
He said, "The night is still young,"
and tore my clothes off!
I somehow escaped
and ran to Sir Motoyasu, who happened to
be staying in the same inn, for help!
Wh-What the hell?
If she hadn't asked me to wait
till dawn and call the knights,
I would've cut you down myself!
What are you talking about?!
I went straight to bed
after dinner last night!
Wait, that chain mail...
You were the thief?!
Who are you calling a thief?
Myne gave this to me as a present
when I met her at the pub yesterday.
To think the Shield Hero would commit
the greatest taboo in this country.
Taboo?
In Melromarc, even attempting to sexually
assault a woman is punishable by death!
If you weren't a hero,
you would be executed immediately!
Executed?
I'm telling you, you've got the wrong idea!
I didn't do it!
If you're so convinced I did,
show me the proof!
When we searched the Shield Hero's room,
um, we found this on his bed.
Eek!
You animal!
There you have it. Undeniable proof.
How? It wasn't there when I woke up!
It's too bad.
I was worried something bad might happen,
but I was hoping you'd know better.
He thinks a hero can do whatever the
hell he wants and get away with it.
That's not even the least bit true.
You're not some sort of light
novel protagonist here!
Know your place!
What is all this?
What the hell is going on?
Myne... Myne!
Why would you say stuff like that?
Weren't we supposed to be a party?
I see now.
Joining me was just a ruse so
she could destroy me like this.
It was all a lie!
The smiles she showed me, and her
acts of kindness, were all fake!
You tricked me!
It was a setup all along!
Sir Motoyasu, I'm so scared!
Shut your mouth, you criminal!
Screw you, too!
I bet you did all this to
steal my money and equipment!
You two planned this together, didn't you?!
Yeah, come to think of it...
Myne only ever called me "Sir Hero,"
but she's calling Motoyasu by name!
If that isn't proof they were in it together,
I don't know what is!
Refusing to admit his guilt and
making nonsensical accusations?
I know, right?
I don't think he deserves any mercy, either.
It really was a mistake to
summon all four together.
Exactly. They never should've
summoned the Shield Hero.
But who would've thought he'd be such scum?
The shield... It's all
about the shield again?
Because I'm the Shield Hero...
Because I'm weak, they're trying to knock
me down to make themselves look better.
Disgusting.
These people are all
dirty, disgusting filth!
This country's people don't
believe in me one bit, too.
Why should I have to fight for them?
Fine. I don't care anymore.
Send me back to my world already.
And summon a new Shield Hero
or whatever the hell you want!
Another world? Screw that!
Why should I have to go through
this in a whole different world?!
You're going to run as
soon as things go south?
Could you stoop any lower?
After all you've done, how could you
even think about not doing your job?
Yeah, get lost.
Who wants to fight alongside a rapist?
Shut up!
Now hurry up and return me to my world!
Well, I'd love to do as you
wish and kick you out,
but legend says new heroes can only be
summoned once all Four Great Heroes die.
What?
No way...
So I can't even go home?
Well, you can certainly go home after
you fight off all the incoming Waves.
Are you saying we'll have to
fight alongside a guy like him?
Screw that!
I'll handle the Waves my way, then!
Don't move!
Get off of me already!
This guy...
What'll it be?
Will you throw me in jail
until the Waves arrive?
I won't imprison you.
There's hardly any time until the next Wave.
Scum or not, you're still a hero, one of
the only beings who can fight the Waves.
But news of your crime is already
spreading among the people.
That is your punishment.
Don't think you'll ever get to lead
a decent life in this country.
I know that already!
This is what you wanted, right?
You can shove it up your ass!
Hey! Wait a second!
I'm really weak, you see.
I don't have a second to waste.
And just like that,
all my money, respect, and trust was gone.
I lost it all.
Hey, kid with the shield.
I heard what you did to that girl.
You deserve a punch to the face!
You too?
You...
What? Weren't you going to punch me?
I changed my mind.
I see. Guess I got lucky there.
Wait a second.
You'll never make it dressed like that.
Consider this a parting gift.
How much?
I don't need anything.
But let's call it a clearance
sale and say five coppers.
Gotcha.
I promise to come pay you someday.
Don't die, kid.
I fight all night and finally hit Level 2, huh?
Well, for these things...
How does 1 copper for a pair sound?
Sure. I'll take that.
Thanks.
Come again.
Welcome.
Buy these.
Oh? Orange balloons, huh?
Twenty in all.
How does 1 copper sound?
Didn't you offer that guy 1 copper for two?
Did I, now?
You must understand,
I have a business to run.
That so?
Will these things fetch
a better price, then?
They're pretty lively.
Gah!
S-Stop it!
I'm not trying to rip you off here.
All I want is a fair market price.
Or do you have some reason
to hate me, maybe?
F-Fine! I get it!
I understand, so get these things off me!
We have a deal.
Instead of trying to fleece me,
if you buy from me regularly,
I'm willing to give you a small discount.
U-Understood!
As much as I'd like to refuse,
the goods and money are without sin.
Also, feel free to tell people all about me.
Tell them that any trader that messes with
me will end up with bite marks all over.
No need to ask me. I was
about to do just that.
To a long business relationship.
Aren't these...
New Shields Unlocked
There are shields with available skill unlocks
So by mastering a shield, I can keep its
abilities even after I switch to another one?
Leaf Shield.
This really is like a game,
through and through.
It can improve the material's quality?
Wow, this is good stuff.
Where did you get these?
In the forest right outside the castle.
Didn't you know?
Hmm... I never knew you could
find such fine stuff there.
I was sure the quality was worse.
Ever since that day,
nothing I eat has any flavor.
O Great Shield Hero,
we'll join your party.
That's right. Thank your lucky stars.
Let's go ahead and discuss the terms first.
Okay!
Your pay will be entirely performance-based.
I trust you know what that means.
Nope, no clue!
It means you'll be paid according to
the loot we get on our adventure.
I'm the leader, so I'll
take at least 40 percent.
I'll split the rest at my discretion.
If you do nothing, you get paid nothing.
The hell? That means you could
keep it all for yourself!
I promise to pay you if you do your job.
If you can do your job.
Let's go get us some equipment, then!
Buy your equipment yourselves.
I have no reason to do that much for you.
Huh?
Forget it. Just hand over your money.
If you'd said that to begin with,
we could've saved some time.
What do we have here?
Aren't you awfully obedient.
Quit freakin' out!
Ow...
Shit!
I have the defense,
but lack offensive ability.
Because I lack it, I can't defeat monsters.
And because I can't defeat
them, I can't farm EXP.
And because I can't farm,
my offensive ability never goes up.
What an awful loop!
Damn it!
You seem to be troubled.
Working alone will not be enough.
But I have just what you need.
If you're offering me party members,
thanks but no thanks.
Party members?
No. What I'm offering you is
a service far more convenient.
What would that be?
Do I have your interest?
Get away from me.
That look in your eyes
is the kind I just love.
You're every bit the man
the rumors said you were.
You know who I am?
Of course I do, Shield Hero.
If my offer interests you, please follow me.
Here we are.
So, what exactly are you offering me?
Can you not tell at a glance?
Slaves!
Slaves?
Yes. I run a slave trading business.
What makes you think I want a slave?
The fact that they cannot
lie or betray their master.
Slaves are placed under
the effect of a curse.
A strong, seal-based curse that
can take their very lives.
What do you say?
Show me what you've got.
I knew it. You have everything it
takes to be a most wonderful patron.
I see ones that aren't human, too.
You can call them human, technically.
Tell me more. I don't know
much about this world.
Creatures that look human but
aren't are called demi-humans.
They're mostly used in manual
labor or as servants.
Beastmen are demi-humans whose appearance
leans more toward the animal side.
They're used as bodyguards or as participants
in death matches that are gambled on.
I see.
But they both fall under
the same category, huh?
Indeed. And since demi-humans are
thought to be closer to monsters,
life would be hard for them in this country,
which practices human supremacy.
As such, they're treated as slaves.