What about the missing child?
The child’s a year older than you.
His name’s Houjou Satoshi.
Satoshi
Satoshi?
What’s up with that?
Rena just came up, right?
Rena was—
Rena was definitely here.
She was right outside my room
and overheard my conversation with Ooishi.
Demoned Away
Chapter Three:
Suspicion
When They Cry
What’s this presence I feel behind me wherever I go?
jungf guvf cerfrap srry oruvaq zr jurerire V tb
Whose breath is this?
Jubfr oerngu vf guvf
I plunge my nails deep into this darkness
V cyhatr zl anvyf qrrc vagb guvf qnexarff
Just like back when I tore through the night
Whfg yvxr onpx jura V gber guebhtu gur avtug
Even the raindrops rolling down my cheeks
Rira gur envaqebcf ebyyvat qbja zl purrxf
Are starting to feel like blood
Ner fgnegvat gb srry yvxr oybbq
If you no longer have a place to call home either
Vs lbh ab ybatre unir n cynpr gb pnyy ubzr rvgure
Lend me your fingers
Gura yraq ze svatref
And let me guide you
Naq yrg zr thvqr lbh
To the forgotten forest where the cicadas cry
Gb gur sbetbggra sberfg jurer gur pvpnqnf pel
And no one ever returns from
Naq ab bar rire ergheaf sebz
What’s wrong, Keiichi?
You look pale.
Probably a cold.
Feels like I’ve got a fever.
Oh, that must be Rena.
I think she’s come to pick you up.
Sorry, but I’m not going today.
I’ll go tell Rena, then.
Right.
Maebara, please come to the examination room.
You have a cold.
Let’s give you a shot.
Thank you.
Take care.
Next person.
Oh, really?
Was she really demoned away?
She’s a young one. She probably eloped.
With whom?
Remember that photographer from Tokyo?
Probably with him.
Takano is strong.
She’d do well no matter where she is.
Takano?
Oh, that woman.
Maebara.
Yes?
Hello, Maebara!
What happened to school today?
I-I was feeling under the weather, so I didn’t go.
I was about to go eat.
Care to join me for lunch in Okinomiya?
S-Sure.
I’ve suspected something since
Satoshi went missing last year.
Thanks for waiting.
I did some investigating around what used to be
his group of friends. In other words, your current circle.
Take your time.
The first year’s victim was
the director of the construction site.
However, it seems he had a couple of fights
with Mion Sonozaki a few weeks prior.
With Mion?
The dam-proponent couple had
an accident the second year, right?
Their daughter was also with them there.
And that daughter would be Houjou Satoko.
Satoko...
Satoko?
A priest and his wife died the third year, right?
Their daughter is Furude Rika.
Rika is...
The housewife that died the fourth year
was Houjou Satoko’s aunt-in-law.
At the time, she was taking care of
her due to her parents’ deaths.
Also, the boy who went missing
the fourth year, Houjou Satoshi...
He’s Satoko’s elder brother.
Every death in this series of murders has some kind of
connection to someone in your circle of friends.
It must be a coincidence!
Maebara, be quiet. Everyone is looking.
S-Sorry.
On the other hand, Ryuguu used to live
in the suburbs of Ibaraki until last year.
That’s right. Rena’s different.
Well, upon further invesigation,
we uncovered something about Ryuguu.
It appears she was suspended from
school a few weeks prior to moving.
She supposedly went around school,
shattering all the windows.
Rena did?
A neurologist examined her and
prescribed drugs and therapy.
A neurologist...
There’s a record of what she said
on the doctor’s medical chart.
There’s a specific name that pops up a lot.
What is it?
The name “Oyashiro”.
She said it stood by her pillow nightly
and stared down at her.
She moved to Hinamizawa shortly after that.
Why would an outsider like her...
I wouldn’t call Rena an outsider.
I checked the residency records.
The Ryuguu family used to live in Hinamizawa.
They moved to Ibaraki when
Rena entered grade school.
Then...
What about the last victim, Tomitake?
Who’s he linked to?
Everyone.
Did you forget, Maebara?
All the victims appear to have some
kind of connection to your friends.
Why are you telling me this?
Maebara.
The one most in danger right now
is you.
How are you?
O-Okay.
I’m glad you seem okay.
We were worried sick.
I’m sorry.
Seems you’re still not feeling healthy, huh?
R-Really?
Ah, here’s some ohagi Mi’s grandma made.
Thank you.
Sure. Oh, there’s also one I made in there.
I wonder if you can guess which it is.
This ohagi roulette is your homework
for skipping today’s club.
We put letters on them,
so give us your answer tomorrow.
Are you here for me or for club duty?
Looking nice and healthy.
You’ll be fine tomorrow.
Let’s go, Mi. It’s rude to be too loud.
You’re right.
Oh, by the way, Kei...
What?
What did you have for lunch today?
I-I went out to eat.
You went out for lunch.
How was it? Was it good?
It seemed like you were with some old man.
Who was he?
Is he the same man as last time? Is he?
H-How do you know?
So, what were you talking about?
It seemed things were getting pretty heated.
I-I didn’t talk about you guys.
Something’s suspicious.
Well, no matter what you’re hiding,
I’ll always know what you’re up to.
I just hope you won’t forget that.
Keiichi, you look pale.
Maybe you should lie down.
I agree.
We’re going now.
Don’t be absent tomorrow.
Why?
Why did they...
A-A-A needle?
I don’t know why, but they’re trying to kill me.
Damn it!
I won’t let them get rid of me that easily!
No matter what.
My name is Maebara Keiichi,
and my life is currently in grave danger.
I don’t know why or who is behind it.
But the one thing I do know
is that it has something to do with Oyashiro’s curse.
All right.
Oh, Keiichi. You’re alone today, and you’re early.
I woke up early.
Oh, really? Take care.
That’s right...
There’s no way I could’ve fallen asleep.
Because I knew exactly what I had to do.
Damn.
Was that a...
hit and run?
Can’t drop my guard. I have to protect myself.
This is it.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Oh my, oh my, you sure are early today, Keiichi.
Y-Yeah.
But why do you look like that?
N-No particular reason.
I felt kinda out of shape, so I was
thinking of practicing swings.
I think taking care of your health
is a really good thing.
Y-Yeah.
But please make sure you don’t lose that bat.
Hey, Kei.
Hearing you went up ahead surprised me.
What are you doing?
Can’t you tell? I’m practicing swings!
For the nationals!
Nationals?
Well, good luck.
Damn it!
All right, everyone gather up! It’s club time!
What’s for today? What is?
I shall not lose!
Mi!
Huh? Kei, you going home?
Maebara
I don’t feel up for it.
Could you leave me alone for a while?
Keiichi, you don’t like playing with girls, do you?
Do you?
That’s not what I meant.
What do you want?
N-Nothing, um, uh...
What happened to club?
I was worried about you, so...
Don’t follow me anymore.
I told you to stop following me!
But my home is the same way.
Then go ahead of me.
I’ll go when I can’t see you anymore.
I just want—
Hurry up and go!
I will, but please put that bat down.
You’re scaring me.
Don’t stop!
U-Um, well...
Uh, can I ask you something?
What?
Why do you have the same bat?
What are you talking about?
Well, I was wondering why you’re
carrying around the same bat.
I don’t get what you’re saying! Speak clearer!
Why are you carrying the same bat as Satoshi?
Satoshi?
T-This?
I borrowed it.
Who cares about that anyway?
That’s not what I mean!
Why are you doing the same things Satoshi did?
What do you mean, “the same”?
Even though he joined a team,
he never played any sports.
S-So?
One day, Satoshi suddenly started
walking to school alone too.
Just like you.
And then one day, he suddenly
started practicing his swings.
Just like you.
And then suddenly one day,
he started carrying a bat around!
Just like you!
And then suddenly one day...
Suddenly...
Wh-What happened to Satoshi one day?
Answer me, Rena! What happened to Satoshi?
I told you, Keiichi.
Satoshi transferred.
T-Transferred?
You won’t, right, Keiichi?
W-Won’t what?
Transfer.
Hello?
Oh, Keiichi?
Oh, Mom.
Dad and I will be in Tokyo tonight for work.
Right now?
We’re already here. We left before noon.
Wh-Why all of a sudden?
Dad’s work contract isn’t going very well.
We’ll be back tomorrow night.
You’ll be fine by yourself, right?
Not like I’ll die or something.
Okay. Bye then.
Make sure you wake up tomorrow.
And make sure you eat properly.
Yeah, yeah. Later.
Hello?
Good evening. Sorry for calling so late.
You’re speaking with Ooishi
from the Okinomiya Bookstore.
Ooishi?
How’s it going? Did anything strange happen?
Uh, I have the feeling someone’s trying to kill me.
Really?
It could just be a coincidence, but....
There was a needle in the ohagi
Rena and Mion gave me.
When they visited the other day.
I didn’t swallow it, but isn’t this...
And the needle?
It was a common sewing needle.
No, Maebara, the needle itself.
If you still have it, we might be
able to use it as proof of a threat.
I can’t find it.
I lost my train of thought at the time.
I see.
Oh, that’s not all.
This morning...
Did you catch the van’s license plate?
N-No, sorry.
I only know that it was a white van.
Rena knows about how Satoshi was demoned away.
She knows something.
Can you clarify?
It seems I’m acting exactly like Satoshi did.
She said that at this rate
I’ll end up facing the same fate...
Be more specific.
Like transfer.
Transfer?
Actually, Rena...
To get my happiness I had done everything
I did everything in my power to obtain happiness
But had done nothing to be blamed and accused of
But nothing you could blame or accuse me of
The sound of footsteps became louder every day
The sound of the footsteps increased every day
Then I noticed the fact there was no time
And at some point I realized that I had run out of time
I was a believer in life to be myself always
I believed enough in life to always stay true to myself
And was asking whether I would be alive
Yet I pondered whether or not I’m truly alive
Give me a reason why not to adopt in this way
So give me a reason-Tell me why I shouldn’t adopt these thoughts
Or judge me to be guilty of so many incurable sins
Or judge me guilty of all these incurable sins
Tell me why, or why not
Complaining way too much
You’re complaining oh, so much
Maybe I overlooked something fatal for me
But maybe I had overlooked a fatal flaw within myself all this time
Preview:
Next Chapter
Don’t fear what lies beyond tomorrow.
Preview:
Next Chapter
Don’t scar your own heart.
Don’t apologize for what
happened during days long gone.
When They Cry: “Demoned Away”
Chapter Four: Disturbance.
Disturbance
Demoned Away
Chapter Four:
Disturbance
Can you believe it?