Found it!
So something did happen...
Are you okay? Are you?
You scared me!
You said we needed an axe or something.
So I...
Looks like you brought a rather big one.
But let’s pick this up again tomorrow.
It’s already getting late.
Okay...
What are you making that long face for?
One more day and that Kenta doll’s yours!
You’re right.
Demoned Away
Chapter Two:
The Secret
When They Cry
What’s this presence I feel behind me wherever I go?
jungf guvf cerfrap srry oruvaq zr jurerire V tb
Whose breath is this?
Jubfr oerngu vf guvf
I plunge my nails deep into this darkness
V cyhatr zl anvyf qrrc vagb guvf qnexarff
Just like back when I tore through the night
Whfg yvxr onpx jura V gber guebhtu gur avtug
Even the raindrops rolling down my cheeks
Rira gur envaqebcf ebyyvat qbja zl purrxf
Are starting to feel like blood
Ner fgnegvat gb srry yvxr oybbq
If you no longer have a place to call home either
Vs lbh ab ybatre unir n cynpr gb pnyy ubzr rvgure
Lend me your fingers
Gura yraq ze svatref
And let me guide you
Naq yrg zr thvqr lbh
To the forgotten forest where the cicadas cry
Gb gur sbetbggra sberfg jurer gur pvpnqnf pel
And no one ever returns from
Naq ab bar rire ergheaf sebz
A festival?
I told you.
The Cotton Drifting Festival.
Rika’s on the festival’s executive committee, right?
Yes, I am.
So what’s the Cotton Drifting Festival?
It’s where we take worn-out blankets
or padded kimonos,
thank them for their service over the years,
and hold a memorial service down the stream.
Sounds kinda boring as far as festivals go.
It’ll be far from boring!
We’ll do it again this year!
Cotton Drifting Festival!
Battle of Four Evils!
The hell’s that?
With you here now, it’ll be
the Battle of Five Evils this year.
Five?
You shall be showing off
the skills you’ve honed in our club.
In other words, we’ll be doing
club activities while visiting stalls.
I see.
Right?
Hello!
It’s good to see you again, Keiichi.
Same to you.
Take any good pictures?
A few, I suppose.
Anyway, you’re quite popular, Keiichi.
I wish I were surrounded by such fine girls!
No, it’s not like that.
Will you be staying for the
Cotton Drifting Festival this year?
That’s the plan.
I’ll go back to Tokyo after
taking pictures of the festival.
I hope you win awards for your photos soon.
Oh, man...
Well, we’ll see each other again at the festival.
Goodbye.
You all know Tomitake?
He visits the village two or three times a year.
He takes pictures of seasonal scenery and wild birds.
Wild birds, huh?
A few days later, the day of
the Cotton Drifting Festival arrived.
Hello, everyone.
Wow, very nice!
You most definitely look stunning this year, too!
So cute! I want to take you home!
Onwards! Time to get this party started!
Yeah!
Seems they’re at it again.
All right.
We shall now commence the eating contest!
I won’t lose!
There!
Cotton drifting, huh?
The cotton absorbs all the bad stuff from your body.
Then we throw the cotton
into the stream, and that’s it.
Huh? Where’d Rena head off to?
Tomitake!
Hey, where’s the rest?
We got split up.
Well, Keiichi? Did you enjoy the festival?
I guess.
Really.
Who is she?
Were you able to become a part of Hinamizawa?
I’m not sure.
There’s still a lot I don’t really know much about.
About Hinamizawa?
Like about the dam construction.
Hinamizawa was almost underwater.
It was a huge deal, wasn’t it?
The dam plans started about
seven to eight years ago.
It seemed Hinamizawa and areas
upstream would be submerged.
That much?
Of course protests occurred.
It went to court, and they discovered
scandal after scandal, along with corruption.
While all this took place,
I heard they decided to cancel construction.
Um, there was also a murder case
with a dismembered corpse, right?
There was.
It was roughly four years ago,
around this time of year.
During the Cotton Drifting Festival, too.
It appears the elders are convinced
it was Oyashiro’s curse.
Oyashiro’s curse?
It was thought that Hinamizawa’s guardian deity
punished those involved in the dam construction
trying to submerge the village.
Since then, it happens every year.
Happens? What does?
Every year, during the Cotton Drifting
Festival, somebody winds up dead.
E-Every year?
A year after the dismemberment,
on the day of the festival,
a resident of Hinamizawa who was a
proponent of the dam construction
died while on vacation when he fell
into the water under a cliff.
His wife’s body has yet to be found.
Furthermore, on festival night a year later
a shrine priest suddenly died
of an unknown illness.
His wife drowned herself in
a swamp the very same night.
And once again, on the festival night the next year...
This time around, a local housewife
was found beaten to death.
Housewife?
The victim was family of
the dam proponent’s brother.
The very same one that
fell off a cliff two years prior.
And the fifth Cotton Drifting Festival is, well...
It’s tonight.
Now, how do you solve the next problem?
What Tomitake said shocked me to my core.
The annual streak of strange deaths in Hinamizawa.
But I thought it had nothing to do with me.
I’ve solved the whole mystery.
The suspect is Rika!
The murder weapon is poison!
The scene is the nurse’s office!
Damn it!
I didn’t get it!
I like gentle killing with poison.
That was easy.
Next! Let’s get the next one rolling!
But first, nature’s calling.
Take your time with your number two!
Mi, that’s gross.
Just kidding. I’ll take this time to strategize.
Maebara?
You have a visitor. Please go to the entrance.
A visitor?
Are you Maebara? Maebara Keiichi?
Yes, I am. And you are?
My car has air conditioning,
so why don’t we have a chat in there?
So, what do you want from me?
If you know anything about this man, please tell me.
Isn’t that Tomitake?
Then are you familiar with this woman too?
Well, I don’t know her name,
but she was with Tomitake last night.
When was the last time you saw these two?
I talked to them last night at
the Cotton Drifting Festival.
Did anything strange catch your attention?
Anything will do, so please tell me.
Did something happen?
The man on that photograph passed away last night.
He was killed on festival day.
I trust you understand what that means.
What it means?
Could it be Oyashiro’s curse?
What happened?
Our patrol car found the body on
the way back from security duty.
The time was five to midnight.
Where the road leads out of town,
the part that’s paved.
It had almost no lights.
And in the darkness, we uncovered
Tomitake’s body on the shoulder road.
The asphalt was covered in blood and filth.
The autopsy said his throat
was slit using his own nails.
Nails?
For whatever reason, he clawed at
his throat with all his might.
And he cut through an artery that
nobody has any business touching.
We suspected drugs, but we couldn’t
detect anything of the kind.
However, we found many external wounds on him.
It’s possible he was assaulted,
possibly by multiple people.
Multiple people?
The estimated time of death
is between nine and eleven.
In other words, mere moments
after you last saw him.
What about the woman?
She’s currently missing.
It’s likely she’s involved in this
incident one way or another.
At this rate, Tomitake Jiro will have “died of Oyashiro’s curse”.
During the sacred festival night,
Oyashiro got upset since he was
insensitively taking pictures.
It’ll be swept away like that.
That can’t be...
Besides, death by divine punishment
or curses simply isn’t realistic.
That’s how it is, Maebara.
The help of a resident who doesn’t
believe in curses is essential.
Anything is fine, no matter
how uncertain you may be.
Oh, here’s my phone number.
Everything discussed here is to be
kept between the two of us.
It’s especially vital to keep it a secret
from Sonozaki and her circle of friends.
Sonozaki? You mean Mion?
Why?
I haven’t the slightest who in the village
could be involved, and to what degree.
So I’d like you to keep this
investigation under wraps.
You can’t be...
Then think of it this way:
You’re keeping it secret so the curse-believing
populace doesn’t fall into a state of chaos.
Why not just think of it that way?
I understand...
Um...
Ooishi of the Okinomiya police.
Okay...
I couldn’t sleep at all last night.
Not after what Officer Ooishi told me.
I heard she disappeared on festival night...
But there were others too, right?
I’m not sure if it’s the curse or
if she was demoned away...
Demoned away? What’s that?
There’s another one, right?
If it’s Oyashiro...
Am I next?
You came back though.
But Toshi didn’t, right?
That’s all in the past.
Let’s not talk about it anymore.
Shoot! I have to go help out my uncle today!
Sorry, everyone! No club activity today!
You? Help out your uncle?
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
You’re surprisingly dutiful.
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Murder Weapon
Suspect
Crime Scene
Apologies, everyone.
I’m going home for the day.
Suspect
Then club’s cancelled for today.
Man...
Well, everyone. Good day to you all.
Goodbye.
See you tomorrow.
Be careful on your way home.
Crime Scene
I was looking forward to playing this game.
Satoshi
Satoshi?
Who’s this guy?
Rena, have there been students who
transferred elsewhere from this school?
Sometimes.
Did this Satoshi guy transfer too?
Sorry, I don’t really know.
It seems he transferred around
the time I came here.
So I didn’t get to talk to him much.
Hey, Rena.
You guys aren’t lying or
keeping secrets from me, right?
No, not at all.
That’s not true, is it?
What do you mean, Keiichi?
You’re hiding something from me, right?
What about you, Keiichi?
Aren’t you doing the same thing? Are you?
You’re lying and keeping secrets
from us too, aren’t you?
I’m not doing either of those.
That’s a lie.
Wh-What makes you think I’m lying?
During club yesterday,
you said you were called to
the teacher’s office, didn’t you?
I know that you didn’t go there.
You were talking to someone in
a car near the school gate.
With a man I didn’t know.
Who was that man?
S-Someone I don’t know.
Why would a stranger need to speak with you?
A-As if I’d know.
Then what were you talking about?
Nothing to do with any of you...
You’re lying!
Just like you have things you wish to hide,
so do all of us.
R-Right...
Let’s go.
It’s getting a lot cooler.
Keiichi! There’s a call from the bookstore for you!
Bookstore?
Hello?
Sorry for calling so late.
You’re speaking with Ooishi
from the Okinomiya Bookstore.
Ooishi?
So did anything happen in particular?
Um, what does “demoned away” mean?
It’s an expression unique to that village.
It’s the same meaning as plain ol’ “spirited away”.
Spirited away...
Hinamizawa was feared as the
“village of demons” a long time ago.
Demons? Like the ones in Hell?
Well, more like the man-eating ones.
Those that come to kidnap and devour people.
There was some old, scary fairy tale like that.
Rena and Mion were talking about it.
About Oyashiro and being demoned away.
Maebara, you know about the first incident, right?
The dismemberment?
Yes, of the six murderers,
one is still on the run, right?
What if they weren’t on the run but demoned away?
What about the next year’s accident?
The dam proponent and his wife that died in accidents.
Truthfully, only the husband has been
officially confirmed dead from an accident.
The wife has been declared dead in absentia.
What about the third year?
When a priest died of illness
and his wife committed suicide?
The same rings true for that, too.
The wife’s body has yet to be found,
and we were only left with a suicide note.
I’m not sure if I can attribute it to
“being demoned away”,
but when it comes to Oyashiro’s curse,
one person always ends up missing.
Then what about the housewife
who was beaten to death last year?
Did someone go missing?
The culprit was caught, right?
Yes, he was arrested. He was a drug addict.
But after the suspect was arrested,
we found out that a child of
the victim had gone missing.
Even though the culprit was arrested?
He passed away in the holding cell during the inquiry.
Unfortunately, he took the truth
with him to the grave.
What about the missing child?
The child’s a year older than you.
His name’s Houjou Satoshi.
Satoshi?
Satoshi
He was in your school till last year.
Maebara
Keiichi
That will be your seat.
The former seat of a transferred student.
Hey, Keiichi. Open the door for me.
Sorry, my dad’s here. That’ll be it for tonight.
Please let me know if something happens.
Hey, hurry and open up!
Well then.
Yeah, yeah. I’m coming.
What’s up with that?
Oh, you don’t have to hide it.
Rena just came up, right?
I figured I’d bring you two some tea.
Huh? I might have just barely missed her.
Rena was—
No point in hiding it.
Weren’t you talking with her just now?
Did you see her come upstairs?
Yeah, I did.
I told her your room was straight up the stairs.
Wh-What do you think you’re doing, Keiichi?
You don’t have to be embarrassed!
Rena was definitely here.
She was right outside my room
and overheard my conversation with Ooishi.
To get my happiness I had done everything
I did everything in my power to obtain happiness
But had done nothing to be blamed and accused of
But nothing you could blame or accuse me of
The sound of footsteps became louder every day
The sound of the footsteps increased every day
Then I noticed the fact there was no time
And at some point I realized that I had run out of time
I was a believer in life to be myself always
I believed enough in life to always stay true to myself
And was asking whether I would be alive
Yet I pondered whether or not I’m truly alive
Give me a reason why not to adopt in this way
So give me a reason-Tell me why I shouldn’t adopt these thoughts
Or judge me to be guilty of so many incurable sins
Or judge me guilty of all these incurable sins
Tell me why, or why not
Complaining way too much
You’re complaining oh, so much
Maybe I overlooked something fatal for me
But maybe I had overlooked a fatal flaw within myself all this time
Preview:
Next Chapter
What you see is naught but false whereabouts.
Preview:
Next Chapter
What you see is naught but a blank stare.
What I see is naught but a repetition of sorrow.
When They Cry: “Demoned Away”
Chapter Three: Suspicion.
Demoned Away
Chapter Three:
Suspicion
Can you believe it?