Uh, I have the feeling someone’s trying to kill me.
She said that at this rate
I’ll end up facing the same fate...
Be more specific.
Like transfer.
Transfer?
Demoned Away
Chapter Four:
Disturbance
When They Cry
What’s this presence I feel behind me wherever I go?
jungf guvf cerfrap srry oruvaq zr jurerire V tb
Whose breath is this?
Jubfr oerngu vf guvf
I plunge my nails deep into this darkness
V cyhatr zl anvyf qrrc vagb guvf qnexarff
Just like back when I tore through the night
Whfg yvxr onpx jura V gber guebhtu gur avtug
Even the raindrops rolling down my cheeks
Rira gur envaqebcf ebyyvat qbja zl purrxf
Are starting to feel like blood
Ner fgnegvat gb srry yvxr oybbq
If you no longer have a place to call home either
Vs lbh ab ybatre unir n cynpr gb pnyy ubzr rvgure
Lend me your fingers
Gura yraq ze svatref
And let me guide you
Naq yrg zr thvqr lbh
To the forgotten forest where the cicadas cry
Gb gur sbetbggra sberfg jurer gur pvpnqnf pel
And no one ever returns from
Naq ab bar rire ergheaf sebz
Um, I’ll be right back.
Okay, I don’t mind.
Good evening.
R-Rena...
Why are you here?
Keiichi, have you had dinner yet?
No...
I’m glad.
I brought some side dishes.
I could warm them in your kitchen...
I’m grateful, but it looks like
dinner will be ready soon.
Really?
My mom makes a lot of side dishes,
so, well...
Did your mother really make dinner?
Uh, well, she didn’t, but right now...
Why?
Why do you lie?
It’s not...
That’s a lie!
For dinner you’re having instant ramen, right?
Grilled ginger pork flavour,
which you bought at Seventh Mart.
How...
But that’s not healthy for you.
You should eat some vegetables too.
So Keiichi, could you unlock the door, please?
Go home...
Keiichi, unlock the door.
Please go home.
Keiichi...
Go home.
Go home!
Go home! Go home!
Ouch! It hurts, Keiichi!
Ouch! It really hurts, Keiichi!
Go home! Go home!
I’m sorry for fooling around.
I’m...
Go home!
I’m sorry... I’m sorry...
Go home! Go home!
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
Go home!
I’m oh, so sorry!
Hello? Ooishi?
Rena was just here.
She stopped by to visit?
No...
Ooishi, please tell me more about Rena.
I don’t mind, but don’t tell anyone else.
Also, I’ll be making a couple of assumptions.
Is that all right?
Yes.
I understand.
Truthfully, I’m pretty skeptical.
You think they’re suspects after all?
No, that’s not what I mean.
I’m talking about Oyashiro.
I was wondering if Oyashiro’s curse really exists.
And things like that...
The incident with Ryuguu Rena
that I told you about before...
You mean when she went around
breaking all the windows in her school?
Yes.
There were actually some victims.
She assaulted three male students
she was close with with a bat.
A bat?
But neither the school nor victims prosecuted,
so it didn’t go to court.
For whatever reason, those involved
are unwilling to disclose anything.
One victim even ended up with a broken eye socket,
but he hasn’t pursued any charges,
let alone even so much as talks about it.
Hello?
Maebara, can you hear me?
What is she saying...?
What was that, Maebara?
“I’m sorry...”
Maebara? Maebara?
“I’m sorry.”
Hello?
“I’m sorry, I’m sorry.”
Good morning, Kei!
Were you always into baseball?
I can’t concentrate!
Leave me alone!
Stop swinging already!
What?
Stop swinging already...
I stopped.
I mean, stop swinging for the day.
Why?
I’m not bothering anyone.
You are!
Who did I bother and when?
That’s not even your bat.
It’s something a transfer student forgot, right?
It’s strange, huh...
The older brother transferred,
leaving his little sister behind, right?
You knew?
Houjou Satoshi.
Satoko’s older brother, right?
Suddenly vanished last year.
I heard Satoshi was also practicing his swings.
Right before he went missing, no less.
Is this some kind of forewarning for Oyashiro’s curse?
Either way, you’re scaring everyone.
If you’re just fooling around,
at least stop imitating Satoshi!
I’ll have you know, I don’t know
a damn thing about Satoshi.
Since everyone is hiding it from me.
We weren’t hiding it...
You keeping it quiet because
I might get scared?
You’re shutting me out for such a dumb reason?
No, I didn’t mean...
I asked you if something happened at the dam site.
You said no!
Did you just forget the dismemberment?
As if, you liar!
Sorry, I didn’t mean to lie...
Friends don’t hide things from each other, right?
Isn’t that right?
That’s why you’re not my friends!
K-Kei...
That’s not...
Oh, the ohagi that you gave me was good.
So good it made me bleed.
So, who did it?
You? Rena?
You can’t get rid of me that easily.
Don’t think I’ll go down as easily as Satoshi did.
I know that you got into several fights
with the dam construction director who got killed.
You thought you could hide it from me?
How did you find out even that...?
Let’s go.
It’d suck if we were late.
You’re cruel, Kei.
I see...
The one who told you everything
must have been that guy.
I should’ve killed him back then.
It seems he forgot I pardoned him
since he was going to retire this year.
Damn.
Damn that old bastard.
I’ll definitely kill him.
Old bastard... You mean Ooishi?
Why is she carrying around a cleaver?
I found you, Keiichi.
What do you want?
My home is the same way.
Then what’s that cleaver for?
What is it?
Keiichi, isn’t something bothering you?
You’re scared, aren’t you?
I—
I’m not scared.
I still regret it, back when Satoshi transferred...
I truly regret not paying attention
to what was bothering him.
Transferred... With that you mean
he was demoned away, right?
Who got rid of Satoshi?
Was it you? Or Mion?
Or was it someone from the village? Answer me!
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
Then I’ll ask you in a way that you’ll understand:
Who’s behind those serial murders?
You misunderstand.
The perpetrator isn’t human.
Everything goes as Oyashiro decides it will.
Oyashiro’s curse is mere superstition!
You don’t believe in Oyashiro?
H-How could I believe in such a thing?
Oyashiro does exist.
Has someone apologized to you?
And for a long, long time?
Oyashiro came to me too.
That’s why I transferred.
That’s why I returned to Hinamizawa.
Only I can listen to your problems.
I won’t let you transfer.
Now, tell me.
What?
I’ll listen.
I’ll save you.
So tell me.
No way!
The hell do you want from me?
Get any closer and the next swing
will crush your skulls, you damn bastards!
I think you should keep lying down.
Rena...
I called the doctor, so he should be here soon.
Why are you here?
Pardon me!
Mion? Why?
Your family wasn’t here, so I called her.
Oh? You seem plenty fine to me!
Seems I didn’t have much to worry about.
Rena, did you call the director?
Yeah, right after calling you.
The director will be here soon.
Who’s the director?
You don’t know? If I say director, I mean the director.
You’re into baseball nowadays, right?
He’ll be happy to hear that!
So who’s the director?
The director is the director.
So who is that?
Y-You guys...
Oh, yeah!
Let’s finish that game before they arrive!
Game?
The ohagi homework.
I bet you forgot about it, right?
Wh-What’s going on?
Don’t move.
It’s time for your punishment.
What is that?
What are you doing?
Kei, you know, right?
What?
What am I supposed to know?
We suspected drugs, but we couldn’t
detect anything of the kind.
Give up.
Stop!
Stop it!
They came.
The perpetrators are Rena and Mion.
There are more than four or
five adults who own a white van.
Tomitake’s cause of death was
from an unknown drug.
This syringe proves that.
Why?
Why’d it have to come to this?
There he is! At the back!
Just a second.
Oh, Ooishi, you have a call from the public.
Oh, thank you.
It’s from a public payphone.
Hello, you’re speaking with Ooishi.
O-Ooishi?
Maebara? Did something happen?
Uh...
What happened?
Hinamizawa
Telephone booth
U-U-U-Um, I...
Hinamizawa
Telephone booth
Calm down, Maebara.
Hinamizawa
Telephone booth
I’ll send a nearby officer your way right now.
I’ll be there right away, too.
Um, that’s probably useless...
It’ll be too late.
Only one
phone booth
in town.
I sent a car.
Give it five.
Only one
phone booth
in town.
I sent a car.
Give it five.
Only one
phone booth
in town.
I sent a car.
Give it five.
Calm down, Maebara!
What’s the situation right now?
That’s too long! How many people are in the car?
Two.
Did you call the resident officer?
He’s on scheduled patrol.
Kuma, please prepare a car!
Yes, sir!
Are you still on the line, Maebara?
There’s an officer headed there right now.
He’ll be there in two to three minutes.
Maebara, who’s the perpetrator?
How many?
A-At first I also thought it was a human...
But actually...
It seems that Oyashiro actually exists.
Right now...
Maebara?
It keeps following me...
No matter how much I run, run, run, and run,
it sticks to me like a shadow.
Little by little, little by little...
It keeps creeping up closer and closer behind me...
Maebara, is he...
Right now, by any chance, could he be...
Behind me... Right behind me...
Who’s there?
How could I possibly look behind me?
If I turn around, I’ll... I’ll...
I know you’re afraid! But I need you to tell me!
Just give him a little backwards glance!
Tell me who’s behind you, Maebara!
Maebara, you couldn’t be...
You’re not clawing at your throat, are you?
Hello, Maebara? Maebara...
I-I’m s-sorry...
Ooishi, the car is ready.
Ooishi!
“I’m sorry”?
June, 1983
In Shishibone City, Hinamizawa,
two female students were murdered.
The suspect is Maebara Keiichi.
After inviting two classmates over,
Ryuguu Rena and Sonozaki Mion,
he beat them to death with a bat.
He fled the scene and was later found
collapsed in a telephone booth by officers.
Twenty-four hours later, he was
pronounced dead at the hospital.
The autopsy concluded that the cause
of death was hypovolemic shock.
He lost his life due to heavy blood loss
after franctically clawing away at his own throat.
We found no signs of drug use.
Later, a handwritten memo was
found in the perpetrator’s room.
It was made of two sheets of B5 college-ruled paper,
cut in two, and taped behind the clock on the wall.
That memo must’ve originally been one B5 page
which was torn to remove a
few lines in the middle of the page.
From the large amount of
tape residue left behind on the clock
it can be surmised that another item
had been taped alongside the memo.
The memo reads as follows:
“My name is Maebara Keiichi,
and my life is currently in grave danger.
I don’t know why or who is behind it.
But the one thing I do know
is that it has something to do with Oyashiro’s curse.
The perpetrators are Rena and Mion.
There are more than four or
five adults who own a white van.”
The following is from the second sheet:
“I don’t know how things turned out like this.
By the time you read this,
I will probably already be dead.
To the one reading this, I ask you
to please uncover the truth in my stead.
That is my one and only wish.
Signed, Maebara Keiichi.”
To get my happiness I had done everything
I did everything in my power to obtain happiness
But had done nothing to be blamed and accused of
But nothing you could blame or accuse me of
The sound of footsteps became louder every day
The sound of the footsteps increased every day
Then I noticed the fact there was no time
And at some point I realized that I had run out of time
I was a believer in life to be myself always
I believed enough in life to always stay true to myself
And was asking whether I would be alive
Yet I pondered whether or not I’m truly alive
Give me a reason why not to adopt in this way
So give me a reason-Tell me why I shouldn’t adopt these thoughts
Or judge me to be guilty of so many incurable sins
Or judge me guilty of all these incurable sins
Tell me why, or why not
Complaining way too much
You’re complaining oh, so much
Maybe I overlooked something fatal for me
But maybe I had overlooked a fatal flaw within myself all this time
Preview:
I want you to look at the real me.
Next Chapter
Preview:
I want you to forgive the whimsical you.
I want you to understand the other I.
When They Cry: “Cotton Drifting”
Chapter One: Jealousy.
Cotton Drifting
Chapter One:
Jealousy
Can you believe it?