She's unbelievably strong!
This is Tiamat, Mother of Monsters...
Pathetic little fools. Do you really think your futile struggle
is enough to protect your kind from annihilation?
Humanity's history has reached its end.
Not yet!
We're here to stop that!
The time of your destruction is now.
Mash, lend me your strength!
Okay then!
Let me handle her.
In the meantime, you two get away.
Merlin?!
Dealing with beautiful yet troublesome ladies is my specialty.
And after all, I'm immortal!
Laughable.
Oh?
His wounds—
So he really is immortal?
I'm half-incubus, you see.
My very existence is somewhat of a dream.
How fascinating. Powerless, yet also deathless.
Then take this. It's been quite a while
since I used the power of my eyes.
A half-incubus statue will make
a fine decoration for my temple.
Don't tell me she has Mystic Eyes of Petrification?
Sorry, guys, but cancel everything I just said.
You've got to protect me, Fujimaru!
Huh?!
Don't ask why, but if I lose consciousness,
we'll all be in big trouble! So, please!
Sorry about this, Mash!
Please use my mana!
Right!
B-But I can't hold it for long!
Senpai, please escape—
What's this?
Vassal of King Gilgamesh, Rider Ushiwakamaru.
Face me!
This is my battle now, Fujimaru-dono.
I beg you, run for the Northern Wall and don't look back!
Don't think you can get away from me!
Far too slow!
Taste the venerable blade of Genji, Usumidori!
Now, hurry!
But, Ushiwaka, we can't leave you!
Don't be foolish! With my fleetness of foot,
I'll rejoin you before you know it!
Or do you intend to die here in vain?
Is your fight one that you'll
so easily allow to end in defeat?
All right.
But promise me!
Promise you'll come back!
I swear it! I'd never break a promise to a friend!
Dear, dear. Mother's fickle nature
has brewed up more trouble still.
Gilgamesh...
Why won't you show yourself?
Laughably slow!
You couldn't even swat a fly!
Lowly puppet of the human race!
Let me show you how this puppet can dance,
foul deity!
Sir Fujimaru! This way!
We heard what happened! Hurry!
Hm?
Is that—
Insolent mite!
Your imposing frame hinders you more than it helps!
Curse you!
The Tales of the Wandering Shana-Ou, Act II!
Usumidori: Heavenly Blade Steps!
Feel the kiss of my sword!
I expected no less of Ushiwakamaru.
I really wish she'd just retreat, though.
No!
It can't be!
Ushiwaka!
She put up a valiant struggle.
Every human must die by my hand.
Not even the last child will I spare.
Struggle as much as you like.
It all will end in vain!
No. Far from it.
Leonidas!
Are those soldiers...
Not one of our sacrifices—be they Lady Ushiwaka
or our troops—were made in vain.
This battlefield belongs to us now!
Molon labé!
-
`
Molon labé!
-
`
Molon labé!
-
`
Molon labé!
-
`
Rank-and-file soldiers are no match for me!
Onward, my friends! Bring your souls hither!
Thermopylae Enomotia!
Turn to stone!
Unbelievable! You defy my gaze's power?
Who are you?!
My ancestor is the great hero, Heracles.
My bloodline is of Zeus, ruler of all the gods!
The offspring of Zeus?!
The very same!
And the ruler of the country that
above all others venerated Ares, god of war!
King of Sparta, Leonidas!
And now I see you for what you truly are,
Avenger!
What need would Tiamat have to wield Mystic Eyes?
Know the great name of Zeus,
as I know your true name, that of the wicked goddess
whose gaze turned men to stone!
The one whom divine wrath turned
from goddess to monster, Gorgon!
You... How do you know that name?
Who among the people of Greece could ever forget it?
Leonidas!
I admire your valor.
Take pride in knowing you will die a hero,
without having to witness the
death throes of the world of man.
Not possible.
Just as my soul is, so the human world is undying.
I entrust the future to you.
Leonidas...
On the contrary, that is impossible.
The human world nears its end.
Your most powerful guardian has died for nothing!
For nothing?
Now I see,
Gorgon, or whatever you call yourself.
When it comes to battle, you're a rank amateur!
You...
Standing upon the great bridge at Gojou,
mighty Benkei waited for his foe...
Don't!
We are Heroic Spirits.
Shadows of people whose names were carved
forever into the annals of human history.
Our reward for the restoration of humanity
will be our history's continuation.
Yes. A thousand years after my death,
there existed a child who admired Ushiwakamaru.
Knowing that fact is enough to compel me to fight.
It makes risking this transient life of mine worth it!
The Tales of the Wandering Shana-Ou, Act IV!
Dan-no-Ura Eight-Boat Leap!
Insolent counterfeit!
Ushiwaka!
Fare thee well, Fujimaru-dono!
Has she fallen?
No!
She withstood two Noble Phantasms!
Is this...
the power of a goddess?
No. Look closer.
That's...
That light! The Grail!
Oh? So your eyes aren't entirely useless.
The Grail is making her immortal!
Underestimate me at your peril.
I do not rely on the Grail's magic.
I will not borrow the power
of an outside force to destroy humanity.
And now, I will lay waste to Uruk myself
and snuff out the life of the king!
Rise, my children! There is no reason
to wait for the appointed time.
Unleash your hatred against the humans
who have so far eluded us
and trample them all underfoot!
Please, wait a moment.
Isn't that a little short-sighted, Mother?
What?
Conquering Uruk is only a small step towards our goal.
Isn't the real issue the other goddesses,
rather than the humans?
Once Uruk falls, the alliance is dissolved.
It is for those coming battles that
the second generation is being prepared.
One hundred thousand offspring
await birth within the Blood Fort.
Until they are born,
the Three Goddess Alliance must be upheld.
Besides,
we should take our time and torment
these humans as long as we can.
They stole these lands from the beasts,
took their young away,
took up arms against Mother,
and then had the gall
to forget what they had done.
Be grateful that my son
shows such restraint, humans.
But the hour of your destruction still looms.
When the sun rises for the tenth time,
we will come to destroy Uruk.
Be sure to remember that.
She finally went home.
It's hard to have such an unreasonable mother.
But we children can't choose our parents.
Don't you agree, Fujimaru Ritsuka?
What's the meaning of this, Enkidu?!
What does it look like? I just saved your lives.
What?
If we slaughtered all the humans now,
the other two goddesses would be after us in a second.
That makes sense.
So just what are you, anyhow?
You clearly aren't Enkidu.
A prototype of the new humanity
who will rule the world after you,
replacing you archaic humans.
My True Name is Kingu!
K-Kingu?
The god who led the offspring
of Tiamat in Babylonian myth?!
I am a perfect being.
A human of the next generation.
So let me make you a guarantee.
Humanity will not be destroyed.
It will be reborn, right here.
The sole successor of your history will be me.
I-I won't let you—
The joy of returning to nothingness
is the final salvation I will grant you.
Lord Leonidas,
who never stopped defending the Northern Wall, is...
The demonic beasts just keep on coming.
Is it all over?
Lord Leonidas...
There you are.
Benkei!
I will be taking my leave as well.
Tell King Gilgamesh I am sorry
for not meeting his expectations.
What?
But why?
I am not the Musashibou Benkei
whose name you know, Fujimaru-dono.
What are you saying?
I am merely a disloyal man who deserted
his lord Minamoto no Yoshitsune,
Hitachibou Kaison.
The day that my lord and Benkei-dono met their deaths,
I abandoned them and fled.
Thereafter, I devoted every day of my life
to spreading Yoshitsune-sama's legend far and wide.
So hearing that you still remember that legend
brought me great happiness, Fujimaru-dono.
Benkei-san...
But I let it happen again.
I was terribly afraid of that wicked goddess.
Thus I retreated along with the other soldiers.
But you brought those soldiers home alive.
Don't blame yourself!
When Leonidas-dono took to the battlefield,
and when Ushiwakamaru-sama fought so bravely,
yet again, all I did was watch.
I am a mere coward, unworthy of the name Musashibou.
I see no point in fighting any longer.
That's not true!
We need you, Benkei-san!
You think much too highly of me.
The only fitting fate for a foolish man like me
is to wander and fight demonic beasts
until I fall dead in the wilderness.
Benkei-san...
There's nothing we can do.
It's going to hurt our combat resources to lose him,
but it would be foolish to try and force
a man who's lost the will to fight.
Come on, don't look at me like that.
Even I can understand how he feels.
Then...
Look over there.
Take up these bricks,
and pile them here like so.
A tactic anyone is capable of,
yet one of vital importance.
We humans need to do everything we can,
no matter how insignificant it seems!
He's right!
That was our creed!
We've been doing everything we can.
That's what we staked our pride on!
I'll help you!
Me too!
Senpai...
Even without Leonidas to lead them,
they're not going to give in to despair.
We can't let it get us down, either.
Right!
Where am I?
I haven't disappeared yet.
So we should just keep going this way?
Right.
This path will take you out of the temple.
Follow the road, and it will take you back to Uruk.
Thank you, mister.
Thank you!
Oh?
You're awake already.
Servants are certainly resilient.
I've heard of that green hair.
So you're Enkidu?
This is the first time I've had
the displeasure of meeting you.
Yes, I suppose you're right.
Welcome to my humble abode.
I suppose you're going to use my body as an incubator.
I'm glad you're so quick on the uptake.
As you can see, this is a factory of sorts.
Tiamat's demonic beasts are all
born from one maternal body.
Which has its limits, you see.
One piece of flesh yields three uridimmu.
But three pieces of flesh are necessary
to produce one ugallu.
Now I see.
You defile the human corpses
you steal by using them as tools.
So noble, these so-called offspring of Tiamat—
Oh, I beg your pardon.
My hand slipped.
Both of us could stand to be more careful.
Me, with my hands itching to be put to use,
and you, with that smart mouth of yours.
Though you'll be just like them soon enough.
Luckily, the brain is the last part to change.
So you're just as stupid as your mother.
Allowing the consciousness to remain
until the last is unbelievably foolish.
Every single one of them
must have fought to the very end,
even after their transformation was complete.
Fight back all you like.
Entertain any fantasy you like.
You're free to dream your dreams until the end.
Why did you let those children go?
A difference in values.
I don't bear grudges the way Mother does.
I only kill threats.
But you had no reason to keep them alive, either.
I see you're as hopeless at warfare as your mother.
And you fancy yourself the successor to humanity?
Don't make me laugh!
I see.
We'll have to take more extreme measures with you.
I won't implant an egg in you after all.
I'm taking you straight to Mother.
Tiamat's Authority is the Sea of Life.
Those who fall into its waters
become her offspring just as they are.
Primordial life.
The magi know it as the mud of the Holy Grail.
The King of Mages named it the Chaos Tide.
Now I have something to look forward to.
I wonder. What kind of monster will you turn into?
Mother of Monsters
As time passes by, I replay them inside
Thoughts of another, thoughts within me
We meet, and then part ways again
Within slumber, I dream a warm reverie of bygone days
Where our feelings weave together as one
With nothing to come between them
When I’m so afraid to stumble, for fear I might fall
That fear of taking another step overwhelms me
I hope I can take my memories of you
And let them become the strength that urges me on
so
shi
te
And then
Today I’ll take one more step forward
ya
sa
shii
Holding close our past and those warm memories
I’ll keep choosing my own path, though it takes me far from you
I believe that my choice is right
For everything is connected by our story