This is your story,
and the story of another.
The story of a journey.
It’s a success! We did it!
D-Director!
Director, it’s not safe here! Please evacuate!
Our second defensive barrier has been breached!
What is the director doing in there?!
I’ve got to hurry.
Yes. I did have to hurry.
I didn’t have even a second to spare.
That’s a nice fragrance.
Darjeeling, as usual?
As long as it’s drinkable,
it could be water for all I care.
I’m glad to see you in good health, Archaman.
Though I hear you won’t be continuing as a magus.
I’m doing the best I can with the knowledge and skills I have now.
An excess of modesty is itself closer to bragging.
But I did feel that might be the case.
So, where are you now?
Well, I never did find a place that felt right.
Actually, I have a favor to ask you.
If you’re willing, I’d like you to take me on here.
What do you say?
All right.
It all starts here, Romani Archaman.
Existences recorded within the
collective knowledge of humankind,
known as Heroic Spirits,
can be given physical form using mana
and commanded as "Servants."
Furthermore, a Heroic Spirit unable to materialize by itself
could be made to possess
the body of a human being,
thereby becoming what was called a "Pseudo-Servant"—
but our experiment’s goal
was something else altogether.
A fusion of Heroic Spirit and human—
a living weapon with a conscious will.
The Demi-Servant Project.
That’s what you’ve been
working on for over a decade.
That’s right.
I’ve raised a number of test subjects for that purpose.
Of all the subjects, she was the most ideal.
But the Heroic Spirit that fused with her
refused to cooperate with us and went silent,
leaving her without a Servant’s powers—
only the immense physical strain.
Not quite.
We did succeed in activating the Relic.
Using it as a catalyst
will allow us to perform more stable
experiments with the Heroic Spirit System.
Servants are an invaluable factor
in the preservation of human history.
A successful Rayshift is only half the battle—
we also need to prepare a stockpile of weapons.
But now work can begin on a
more stable summoning system,
all thanks to her noble sacrifice.
But she’s a Designer Baby.
Her rate of cellular decay was already high,
and the experiment may have
accelerated it even further.
On the other hand, her fusion with a Heroic Spirit
will allow her physical body to remain at its peak.
She won’t age, even as her cells degrade.
She’s lucky, don’t you think?
She doesn’t need to fight.
All she has to do is continue to live.
She’ll accompany Team A
as a catalyst for summoning.
I don’t expect anything more from her,
and I’d rather you didn’t either.
Let me be her personal physician.
Is that all right with you?
That depends. Are you asking out of pity?
No. I ask purely that you allow me to
maintain her health as a doctor.
Her condition is very precarious.
I don’t think anyone else can ensure
that she’ll live two more years.
Very well.
Senpai?
Oh, no. I was only appointed to Chaldea five years ago,
so if anything, you’d be my senpai.
Nice to meet you. My name is Romani Archaman.
I’ll be your doctor from now on.
You can call me Roman.
Hm...
Dr. Roman.
Has a nice ring to it, right?
Roman.
A word that means "an optimistic observation
of the future as holding countless possibilities."
Is that right?
Wow, you know a lot for a ten-year-old.
You really are my senpai.
The senpai-kouhai relationship
is one of teaching and learning,
but I haven’t taught you anything, Doctor.
All of my knowledge was input by Sheba,
so Sheba would be the senpai in this case.
Well, if you look at it that way, then I suppose so.
Yes. That fits my definition of what a senpai is.
I see.
I’d interpret it a little differently.
The way I see it,
if there’s anyone who would truly be your senpai,
it would be someone who’s an ordinary human.
Someone who’s an ordinary human?
A person who can live among other people and
share the joy, sorrow, and anger that they feel.
Someone like that.
So a senpai when it comes to
socialization and living life?
I suppose so.
And also someone who can
focus on the long term, I guess?
Focus on the long term?
Yes.
Someone who cares about their home and neighbors,
whose heart is full of compassion for others.
Someone who sees people in need
and acts to help them, no matter the reason.
In my opinion, this is the
greatest virtue humans possess.
In other words, someone who is
not egotistic but altruistic.
Would that not be a weakness?
To an animal, it would be a disadvantage.
I suppose that’s true. Human beings are
capable of thinking before they act,
and they have to be able to make difficult decisions.
But that also makes them the only organisms to
knowingly do things they know won’t benefit them.
I find that fascinating.
I see. I will add these to the list of
qualifications for my future senpai.
Are you not my senpai?
Nope. I’m still far too inexperienced to qualify.
Now, as your doctor, there’s something
I’d better talk to you about.
It’s about your lifespan.
You were a Designer Baby.
That means your cells decay very fast.
Even if we’re very careful
about maintaining your health,
your lifespan will be eighteen years at most.
First of all, do you understand that?
Yes.
All lifeforms can only operate for a limited duration.
I have no misconceptions concerning
the length of my own operational period.
I see.
This is going to be even more difficult than I thought.
Are you referring to maintaining my health?
Ah, yes. There’s that, of course.
But that’s up to me.
As long as I’m around,
I’ll keep you alive and healthy.
The problem is...
No, never mind that.
In any case, let’s do our best together, Mash.
This is utter folly.
Now, now. Settle down,
Successfully Summoned Heroic Spirit Number 3.
Or rather, Leonardo Da Vinci.
I’m perfectly settled. But I’m also
getting awfully fed up with all this.
Safeguarding all human history?
With the paltry equipment they’ve given us?
Not to mention those Demi-Servant experiments,
which are not only inefficient but also inhumane.
There’s not the slightest bit of beauty in it.
If I’d only been summoned sooner,
I’d never have allowed those mediocre fools
to make such a mess of everything.
You have every reason to be upset.
This is all wrong.
I want to be truthful with her
and acknowledge that what we’re doing isn’t right.
And you’re a fool of an entirely different sort.
Hey, Romani,
don’t you think this is too cruel?
Do you know of any magic that can reveal the sky,
Professor Lev?
That’s an unexpected question.
Well, all right.
It does exist, but it’s rather pointless.
Does that answer your question?
Rather than try to make the skies above Chaldea blue,
it would be far more economical
to take a trip to Antarctica.
You’d have much clearer skies out there, too.
I see.
I guess you’re right.
But why do you ask?
Does the good doctor feel a touch homesick?
Not at all.
It’s just...
So it’s about Mash?
Yes.
I see. Very interesting.
I was invited to join Chaldea for my ability as a magus,
in order to construct the
Near-Future Observation Lens, Sheba.
In that capacity, I also served as Mash’s teacher.
Though it was only in regard to magecraft,
I’ve known her even longer than you now.
She was raised to be as pure and
reticent as possible, in body and spirit,
so that she could one day become the vessel
for any Heroic Spirit necessary.
Mash is indeed very mentally stable.
The theory of her upbringing was sound.
No doubt ever enters her mind.
But the physical wounds she bears
are extremely painful.
Every test she’s subjected to hurts her.
And that pain can become fear,
ultimately turning to hate.
No heart can endure torture forever and stay pure.
And yet, she...
As of now, she has remained pure.
That girl never compares herself
to other people, Romani.
Thus she never feels envy or hatred toward others.
To her, every human is her senpai
in terms of their lived experiences.
She looks up to everyone
and accepts them for what they are.
No matter how much pain or injustice she endures,
Mash sees only the good in people.
She said there’s nothing she loves
more than seeing people smile—
that it’s all it takes to make her happy.
Come to think of it, I suppose that’s true of us too.
It’s a natural reaction,
isn’t it, Romani?
But aren’t you curious?
After all, no one can tell what kind of
person she’ll grow up to be.
"Pure" is a pretty word indeed,
but "naïve" is an equally accurate one.
Once she’s exposed to the ugliness of humankind
and the corruption that permeates its history,
will she still believe that people are good?
That’s the one thing that still worries me.
What do you wish for?
The Holy Grail War is over.
We’ve won.
...What will you wish for?
The completion of Chaldeas.
I care nothing for the Third Magic.
For an astromancer of the Animusphere line such as I,
it would be unthinkable not to reach the Root via my own unique approach.
What about you, then?
What do you desire?
Oh, it’s you.
You’re five minutes late.
That’s not like you—
You want me to put a stop to Chaldeas, eh?
That’s an awfully difficult request.
The preservation of humanity, or my own life—
which is more important to me?
What a silly question.
What’s happening to the flame of Chaldeas?!
All too soon, the day arrived.
Human history would cease to exist beyond 2016.
The phenomenon couldn’t be explained.
Chaldeas frantically combed 2,000 years
of information about the past
to find the reason for the future’s disappearance.
What they discovered was Time-Space Singularity F.
In the year 2004, at the site of a certain city in Japan,
an unknown quantity that had never existed
in history prior to 2015 was discovered:
an area that was impervious to observation.
Chaldea determined that this was
the cause of humanity’s future extinction,
and submitted their experimental
Rayshift proposal to the UN,
which approved it.
The Rayshift process converts humans into
spiritrons, which are then sent into the past
to intervene in events there.
In other words, it’s a form of retrograde time travel.
And Mash was chosen to be part of Team A,
which would carry out the First Mission.
The Director really doesn’t like me, huh.
She says my nonchalance is contagious.
Well, there’s nothing I can do about that.
It might not look like it,
but I’m charging ahead at top speed.
Excuse me.
It’s occupied—
Huh? Who the heck are you?!
Back then, I never questioned anything.
Not the pain I had to endure,
nor the limited lifespan I possessed,
nor my own existence.
None of the other doctors ever
came into my room before.
Oh, is that right?
Chaldea’s quite an advanced place if people here
can convey their feelings even through glass.
I’m still so inexperienced.
I don’t know how to talk to people
unless we’re face-to-face.
So tell me anything you want about what
you think or how you feel. Don’t hold back.
It makes a huge difference in the volume
of information we’ll be able to get,
and besides, it’s a lot more pleasant this way.
Successfully Summoned Heroic Spirit Number 2...
No, from now on, I’ll call you by name.
Hello. It’s nice to meet you, Mash Kyrielight.
H-Hello. It’s nice to meet you too, Dr. Romani.
If this reaction could be called "human,"
then it was the first true "human"
reaction I showed to anything.
Good morning, Mash! How are you feeling?
From then on, the doctor spent a
great amount of time talking with me.
Every experience was new to me.
Everything I thought and felt, things I liked,
things I considered important,
things that were warm and pleasant.
Sometimes the Doctor told me
funny stories about the facility,
and sometimes I listened to him complain,
but little by little, I started to develop
an interest in the world outside my room.
Good morning, Mash!
I’ve got some good news for you today.
Your vital signs have been excellent lately.
Your brainwaves are also very stable.
If this keeps up, you won’t have to
stay in the clean room anymore,
and you’ll finally be a full-fledged member
of the Chaldea research staff.
Thank you.
Oh, I know! When that happens,
I’ll do something to celebrate!
Is there something you want?
A book, for example, or a toy, or a snack?
Isn’t there anything?
If it’s within my power, I’ll make it happen.
I think I’d like to go outside.
I’d like to go outside and see a clear sky.
That was the only thing I wanted.
Unfortunately, Chaldea is located on a
snowy mountain 6,000 meters above sea level.
The only thing visible outside is a blizzard.
But those rare nights when the sky is clear,
I hear you might get a glimpse
of a beautiful starry sky.
I believe the day will come when
you can see that sky for yourself.
Fou-san.
That was what I’d called the mysterious creature
that had grown attached to me as of late.
Have you ever seen the stars, Fou-san?
Looks like the sky won’t be clear today either.
Fou-san?
Wait!
Please wait for me!
Whenever I’m alone, I start to hear it speak
hitori ni naru to kikoeru no
“If it hurts so much, why not give up?”, it says to me
kurushii nara yamete ii to
The sky was the first thing I’d ever wished for.
It draws me in as crushingly as a black hole
black hole mitai ni fukaku
Our King pitied humankind
and declared that he would save them
from the inevitability of death.
The terrifying yet bewitchingly sweet voice that speaks those words
kowakute miryokuteki na amai koe ga
I cannot comprehend it.
Can you, Mash?
It tries to mimic your voice and the way you speak to me
anata no kuchiguse wo manete
Does humanity truly hold such value?
So I pretend that nothing is wrong
nandemo nai to itte miru
What you love,
what you hate,
But even if that wasn’t true, I wouldn’t care at all
sore ga uso demo kamawanai
what you hold dear,
and what you consider evil...
If it gave me the strength to get back on my feet again
tachitsuzukeru douki ni nareba
It’s all up to you to decide.
By coming to know many things
and seeing many places,
Every lifespan draws to an end eventually
subete no inochi ni owari ga aru no ni
you begin to endow your life with meaning.
Listen well.
So why do humans fear and lament it the way they do?
doushite hito wa obie nageku no darou
It’s not you that creates the world.
The world is what creates you.
Knowing that eventually everything will be lost
itsuka wa ushinai to shitteru kara
An eternal empire will always be.
Even if the emperor changes,
the country changes,
or its very name becomes another.
Makes the ordinary days we’re living shine brighter than anything
atarimae no hibi wa nani yori utsukushii
That is the way of mankind’s prosperity.
That is the tree of life that is mankind.
There is only one future that I’m looking for
watashi ga miteru mirai wa hitotsu dake
The most evil blackguard can do good deeds,
and the holiest saint can do evil.
I’ve never, not even a little, longed to have eternity
eien nado sukoshi mo hoshiku wa nai
That’s what it is to be human.
And that’s what we are!
That’s why everyone has hope in their heart!
Every moment, every second, is so dear to me
ichibyou isshun ga itooshii
Why do you fight?
Because I’m alive right here in this world with you
anata ga iru sekai ni watashi mo ikiteru
Your life is destined to end.
With such a finite span of time allowed to you,
why do you yet cling to life,
Red, blue, indigo
aka ao ai
even knowing there is no hope in your kind’s future?
Water, rainbow, sky
mizu niji sora
Miss Mash.
Their colors
iro
Dreams and wishes are radically different things.
Fixing your glare on reality,
figuring it out,
and fighting on until the end
is the way to open the path to what you wish for.
From now on,
live your life for your own sake.
I can never be a goddess
watashi wa megami ni narenai
Nor will I offer prayers to any deity
dareka ni inori mo sasagenai
There’s no logic behind my actions.
I just do what I want to do.
No—I do what I believe I have to do,
and I do it with my head held high.
I don’t care what anyone else may say
tannin ni nani iwaretemo ii
I know exactly what it is that I hold most dear
taisetsu na mono ga nanika wa wakatteru
You’re the same way.
I know you are.
The sky was the first thing I’d ever wished for.
I wish for nothing more than this
kore ijou nozomu koto wa nannimo nai
But that was no more than a dream
formed waiting at a window in a snowstorm.
The future I desire is the one that exists right here
watashi ga hoshii mirai wa koko ni aru
Now everything is different.
I’ve seen so many places,
met all sorts of people,
The person who first taught me what loneliness is
hajimete sabishisa wo kureta hito
and came to know came to know both
the world’s vastness and its warmth.
Who gave a meaning to my solitary existence
tada no kodoku ni kachi wo ataete kureta no
Oh, that’s right.
There is only one future that I’m looking for
watashi ga miteru mirai wa hitotsu dake
I can feel it.
I’ve gained my own form.
I’ve never, not even a little, longed to have eternity
eien nado sukoshi mo hoshiku wa nai
My true wish,
and my own identity,
found over the course of this journey.
Every moment, every second, is so dear to me
ichibyou isshun ga itooshii
The journey on which I was born and came to life.
And now it’s my turn to give the world an answer.
Because I’m alive right here in this world with you
anata ga iru sekai ni watashi mo ikiteru
Would you please hold my hand?
Thank you... so much...
Senpai.
Today we will conduct the
Rayshift to the Seventh Singularity.
Once again...
I am setting out on a journey.