Unbelievable...
I myself can scarcely believe it!
Your Majesty?
What is the matter?
At last, the blueprints for the Fangs of Napishtim are complete!
Behold!
Look, and look well!
They're most satisfactory, I'd say.
My! This is truly a work of genius!
You might have easily pursued
the path of an architect, my king!
Don't flatter me so.
Lest I take it seriously and be tempted to try.
I'll take them to the armory right away.
Good.
Please rest for a short while until I return.
Perhaps I've kept my nose a touch too firmly
to the grindstone these past few days.
The throne is a symbol of the king's authority,
not a sleeping-platform. But...
I don't think I'll be able to resist.
Absolute Demonic Front: Babylonia
The rapids still beat against me
The bottom so distant it's pitch black
You've gotta be kidding me
Hey, who do you think you are?
o
i
da
re
Quit toying with me
Before time itself loses the battle with darkness!
keru
You may get fired up, but do take care
atsu
chuu
i
For the mask of evil sometimes conceals righteousness
teru
On the contrary, if you don't show it for what it is
You'll never get your arguments in order
A voice sobbing in the absence of mercy
Powerless feet freezing still
ashi
mo
In the future, those things'll be holding you down
So better keep your eyes open
"Things are fine this way", and "I wanna live"
These thoughts won't do you any good if you merely wish for 'em
Don't just mumble such important phrases
tai
setsu
na
phrase
Or you'll turn the whole story to trash
Fly high and sure—Phantom’s begun!
Phan
tom’s
be
gun
A mirage of dazzling brilliance
shin
ki
rou
A mirage that stirs the very heart
shin
ki
rou
There's no point in trying to deliberate between light and dark
Even if everything's lost and gone
Smile as though it were still all there
cchau
But there's one thing I hope you won't forget
shii
'Cause our journey's still far from over
It'll never end until you agree
That we're gonna see what lies beyond this sky
saki
wo
mi
tai
Cut through that spiderweb of terror trying to wind around us
kyou
It's time to prove we've got the stuff to get stronger
shou
mei
no
ji
kan
With a sorrowful, but still eternal
"I'll always have love to give"
I’ll
ne
ver
catch
bad
fate
And when I returned here, I saw that the king, still seated
on his throne, had slipped away into an eternal sleep.
That's—
That's impossible!
This is a man who could gaze into the future,
a man who became a magus of his own accord!
It was so he wouldn't die in battle that he swore
to remain here and command from the throne!
He promised me that!
No way can King Gilgamesh be dead!
Yeah, you said it!
He worked himself to death, of all things?!
If overwork killed him, then I'm worried for myself now!
Hang in there, Romani!
You'd better deny it just as strenuously,
or else you could be next!
Besides, if this was all it took to kill him,
he'd have died a dozen times over by now!
That's a good point.
I-I sorta lost my head over the news,
but come to think of it...
Tell me, Ms. Siduri. While we were in Ur,
did anything unusual take place here?
Unusual?
Come to think of it, reports have been pouring in
of people suddenly weakening and dying all over Uruk!
Weakening and dying?
Yes. I was so greatly upset by the king's death
that it went right out of my head until now,
but an abnormal number have died.
Almost as though death itself were enfolding Uruk.
I see.
Very unusual, yes?
Don't you think the Three Goddess Alliance is to blame?
But which of the goddesses could be doing this?
The Mistress of the Underworld, Ereshkigal.
She's got to be the culprit!
The Mistress of the Underworld...
...Ereshkigal?
What? Did you just say Ereshkigal?!
The scent of death that follows Ereshkigal is hanging over Uruk.
Once the people of Uruk lose their strength, the gallû spirits
she commands rush in and pluck their souls from their bodies.
They likely took King Gilgamesh's soul
to the underworld with the rest.
The underworld!
Please wait! The Alliance's three goddesses
are Gorgon, Quetzalcoatl, and then...
Hey, don't look at me.
What?
The Three Goddess Alliance is made up of
Gorgon, me, and finally, Ereshkigal.
What?!
Ishtar was never in it?!
Wow, you don't say.
Oh, it looks like you've been under
the wrong impression for a while.
Who cares about that? What I want to know is:
how can Ereshkigal be back?
Hello, Chaldea? Is the doctor in?
Right here!
Hm. Let's get our facts straight.
First of all, the third and final member of the Three
Goddess Alliance, Ereshkigal, has finally shown up, but...
I thought Ishtar-san was the only one of
the Sumerian gods remaining in this era.
Dang right! So did I!
Well, you see, in Sumerian myth,
Ishtar was called the Mistress of Heaven,
while her equal and opposite, Ereshkigal,
was Mistress of the Underworld.
Oh, okay. I'm starting to get the picture now.
What are you talking about?
Why, about you.
Huh?
When you were summoned,
Ereshkigal was summoned right along with you.
Huh?!
It was the priestesses who summoned Ishtar-san, right?
And just when they did, the temple matron
who carried out the summoning turned up dead.
No doubt she was killed by Ereshkigal.
Oh, so that's what this is about.
Ishtar, goddess of the harvest,
symbolized life to all humans,
and was also called the Great Earth Mother.
On the other hand, Ereshkigal, who symbolized death,
was the Terrible Earth Mother.
Then the two of them are like the light and dark aspects
of a single deity—so do they share the same divinity, too?
And does this mean she's been traipsing around in my body?!
It seems likely.
Ereshkigal is unable to leave the underworld.
No!
So that was...
Summoning Ishtar also brought Ereshkigal,
who's inextricably linked to her,
and since they share the same divinity,
we could only detect one Sumerian goddess!
Oh, I see!
Oh... I see...
But if it's Ereshkigal, that's a stroke of good luck for us.
What's good about it?!
If she's involved in King Gilgamesh's death,
then we can do something about it.
Really?
Really. And a good thing, too.
We can't afford to have him out of commission.
Ms. Siduri, where is the king's body now?
It has not yet been interred.
If the king's soul is in the underworld as you say...
Then once we defeat Ereshkigal
and free his soul, he'll wake up again.
Let's hurry, then! Come on, Senpai!
Defeat Ereshkigal...
Yes. I don't think we can avoid a fight.
Senpai?
Oh, I'm all right.
Are you really planning to go to her?
We have to do what we can.
This is the underworld we're talking about!
Any Servant, even a Divine Spirit,
is rendered powerless down there!
You're out of your mind
if you think you can beat her like that!
We won't know that until we meet her.
Fujimaru...
You know the way to the underworld,
don't you, Señorita Ishtar?
Huh?!
Please take us there, Ishtar.
All right, all right! If all I have to do is take you there, fine!
The rest of you, stay here.
If something goes wrong, I'm counting on you to go to Kutha
and talk Ereshkigal into giving back Fujimaru and Mash.
Very well. Leave it to us.
I'll join you later.
I'd be no help in the underworld.
I'll be waiting here to welcome you home instead!
In the underworld, Ereshkigal holds
power supreme, or so it's said.
I see.
So while you're down there, we'll stay above ground
and do some research on the city.
Research Uruk?
Oh...
Because of the people weakening and dying?
I want to look into other possible causes
and if any other deaths went unreported.
There's still more we can do.
Yeah. I'll leave it to you.
Right.
We came here before during our search
for the Tablet of Destinies, didn't we?
Look, I know I've asked you over and over,
but do you really want to go there?
Either you win against Ereshkigal and bring everyone back alive,
or you lose and become her prisoners. It's all or nothing.
Ereshkigal isn't a bad goddess. I'm sure of it.
Senpai...
Okay.
I'll have to take your word for it.
Back me up, Mash!
S-Sure!
Loading Maanna's bow gunports with tide convergence rounds!
Setting output to 1/3 isosceles of lapis lazuli!
Shatter, gates of the underworld!
Pierce the skyless depths of Ki with An's brilliant light!
Wh-What?!
Go!
Ouch!
Are you okay, Master?
Mostly.
Yes! Flawlessly done!
Did you have to do it like that, Ishtar?
H-Hey! We're here in the underworld,
aren't we? Don't complain!
This is...
the underworld.
This isn't good.
So we can see them, but communications are cut off?
We'll just have to do what we can.
Has the underworld been directly below Kutha all this time?
So rather than a separate plane of existence,
it's literally a world underneath the surface?
Well, obviously.
In the Age of Gods, the heavens, the earth, and the underworld
exist side by side, as though painted onto a single scroll.
Those are souls of humans who died on the surface.
Really?!
Souls trapped like those aren't even permitted to disappear.
Ereshkigal puts the souls of the humans
who strike her fancy in those cages
and keeps them as playthings
for tens of thousands of years.
Does that mean the souls of the
people dying in Uruk are here too?
I'm sure it does.
There are a lot more here than usual.
I'm sure she has the Alliance to thank for that.
Is she aiming to create a kingdom of the dead or something?
Where is Ereshkigal?
Down this path and through seven gates
of stone lies Ereshkigal's palace.
That's where you'll find her.
You know the underworld pretty well, huh?
Huh?!
You knew how to find it,
and what all the rules down here are.
Oh, you're right!
N-No, see, that's just my
goddess powers at work, y'know?
I thought those didn't work
in the underworld, though.
Guh...
Ishtar is a goddess, after all!
Of course she knows all sorts of things we don't!
That's true! She's such a dependable ally!
Oh, geez!
I've been here before! That's why! Okay?!
I'd really hoped to avoid this subject.
I feel like I should apologize.
You have nothing to be sorry for.
I shouldn't have taken it out on you like that.
I've made a lot of mistakes descending into the underworld.
Really?
Yeah.
When I conquered Mount Ebih,
I became convinced that I was infallible.
I let it go to my head and set
my sights on the netherworld,
but that ended in crushing defeat for me. A total rout!
My seven raiments of Authority stripped from me,
I was dragged naked before her,
and then impaled with spears to top it off!
Wow, I...
I can see why you would prefer not to mention that.
I've done my very best to avoid her ever since.
That's whose front door we're marching up to.
Master!
Answer me this.
Is that the gate?
O brave warriors, fallen to the underworld,
where dost thy soul reside?
You'll be asked a question with two possible answers.
The gates of the underworld impartially determine
the qualities of each soul, good or evil.
The qualities of the soul?
There are seven of these.
The last time I came here, this was the gate
where I was stripped of my Authority.
Answer me this, Fujimaru, o sinful one.
It knows his name?
The standards which judge beauty
seem myriad, but are absolute.
Black surpasses white,
as the land doth surpass the heavens.
Therefore, I ask of you:
Which is the true beauty, Ereshkigal or Ishtar?
Huh?
Hey! What's the big idea?
That's not what you asked last time!
This is an incredibly difficult question!
Answer me. Answer me!
Um...
Well, that's an easy one, isn't it?!
M... My answer is Ishtar!
Right on, Fujimaru!
Over there you have the goddess of rot and veggies,
and over here, the goddess of beauty and abundance!
In a beauty contest, I'll win one thousand percent
of the time, naturally!
Ishtar-san!
Are you all right?
Thou hast chosen... poorly.
My answer is Ereshkigal.
Very good!
L-Let's move on.
That was exhausting!
You did well.
I wasn't expecting "which goddess is better?"
to come up in every question.
The gate we just passed through was the sixth.
One more to go!
I'm fun-size now, but anyway, let's press on!
Will you really be okay like that, Ishtar-san?
I don't think I'll be much help in battle,
but that would have been the case
even in my original size.
I can take care of myself against Ereshkigal,
so don't worry about me!
I'm glad to hear it, but even so,
don't push yourself too hard.
H-Hey!
King Gilgamesh?!
How good of you to come pick me up.
W-Wasn't Ereshkigal keeping you prisoner?
While I did let my guard down and carelessly end up dying,
I know the underworld like my own backyard.
It was no trouble at all to give her the slip.
Before the gallû spirits could arrive,
I merely concealed myself in the shadows,
stopped my breathing, entered a trance,
and erased all signs of my presence. It was child's play!
After they passed by, I merely bade my time...
Hey! Knock it off! Let me go! Ooh, curse you!
Until I was confronted with such a hilarious development
that I could hold back no longer
and burst forth from my hiding place to laugh heartily
at your well-deserved predicament!
Speak, Fujimaru. What turn of events lead to
this adorably miniaturized Ishtar before my eyes?
Well, Ereshkigal cursed her, you see...
Were you struck such a blow to your ego
that your physical stature deflated to match?
Are you even listening?!
He told you Ereshkigal did it!
When she failed in her previous attempt
at descending to the underworld, Ishtar was cursed.
So now, every gate I pass through diminishes my Divinity,
and me along with it!
Ha! Little fool!
I knew we should never have come to save you!
Indeed! The littlest fool I've ever seen!
Did I hear you say you'd come to save me,
or did I work myself to death a second time
and begin to hallucinate?
I wish you had, so I could just leave you here!
Why not fling yourself into the abyss right now?
Hmph! As though I would choose such a dull end!
I still have much to accomplish.
Aren't you going back to the surface?
I cannot. For all intents and purposes, I'm still dead.
Without her permission,
I am unable to leave the underworld.
Oh, I see.
Therefore, I shall punish Ereshkigal
and leave this place behind with a smile on my face!
So this is the final gate, is it?
I need not hear the question.
I already know the answer you seek: Me!
Don't make me laugh, pal.
Hmph.
With Ishtar in her present state,
besting Ereshkigal in battle will prove difficult.
I keep telling you, I wouldn't have
been able to help in the first place!
How strong is Ereshkigal?
Mash?
I think King Gilgamesh is right.
We're probably going to have to fight,
so we should know what kind of power Ereshkigal has.
Compared to Ishtar here, her Divinity is lesser.
You know what she's like too, King Gilgamesh?
Well, to a certain extent.
If you consider Ishtar to be a goddess
who obtained everything,
Ereshkigal is a goddess who never wished for anything.
What do you mean?
When the underworld first came into being,
her very existence was offered up as
a sacrifice to be its foundation.
Someone had to become the pillar
that maintained the stability of this place,
and that responsibility was thrust
onto Ereshkigal's shoulders.
Ereshkigal had only just been born
when she was cast down into the underworld,
and forced to live for aeons among
naught but the spirits of the dead she oversaw.
That's really sad.
For me, it's less that she couldn't go outside
and more that she could never see the new world
or meet the people in it.
That's the saddest part, I think.
As compensation for all she lost, while inside the underworld,
Ereshkigal was granted complete invulnerability.
Those who enter its borders, be they Servants
or gods, are rendered powerless.
But that doesn't apply to the living.
Only those who have died
are bound by the underworld's laws.
That means Mash and Fujimaru are capable of taking her on.
In terms of both Divinity and Authority,
she's intermediate at best.
Your chances of victory are rather good.
I see.
Okay, that's all the time we have for chitchat.
We've reached her palace.
It's...
Romani!
There's an enormous open space
just in front of Fujimaru and the others.
No irregularities detected.
Atmospheric magnetic fields also appear stable...
What?
But... there's nothing here but empty wasteland.
Such is the underworld.
Nothing beautiful or extravagant exists here.
Isn't that so?
O queen of the gallû spirits,
you who gazes eternally at a dark sky!
Barometric pressure is five hundred hectopascals?!
Adiabatic cooling is causing a sharp drop in temperature.
It's got to feel like minus six degrees to them!
That's barely enough to sustain biological activity!
Fujimaru, get out of there now!
Cower before me. Revere me.
Look on me and know despair, humans.
I am she who oversees death,
mistress of the underworld.
Under my heel, the sacred mountain is as rubble.
My name is Ereshkigal!
The Death of the King
Stepped into the shadow land
land
There's no paradise to be found
Worn, weary old remedies
sa
biru
old
re
me
dies
Not one any good to me now
ka
ku
shin
na
n
te
nai
Yet still, I will go up the river
Cling with all I have to the ladder
Let even my tears be fuel for the lamp
For my only sign, for my only light
hi
to
tsu
no
sign
hi
to
tsu
no
light
So that in the deep night before the dawn, this song can go on and on
So these aimless meandering dreams may never tangle, but roam free
a
te
naku
So we never turn back to where our paths crossed in our wandering
tachi
fu
ri
ka
e
ranu
you
ni
So even if you start going down the wrong road, I'll never let you go
fu
mi
ha
zu
shita
Even in a world unending, I will stand up and fight
Hear the voice of all life
As long as it still rings out, so together with you, I'll be there
dasu
I'll
be
there
We'll keep the boat steady on the water and sail on