Insane.
Look at 'em go.
Match!
You really are a fast one, Kanao!
Your current score sits at ten wins, ten losses.
Don't count me out yet.
You guys up for a jog?
While keeping up our Breathing, you mean?
Yeah.
You want me to keep this up 24/7?
Monjirou!
Take this!
That's nothin'!
You're all brawn and no brains!
Let's go!
Episode_26
New_Mission
A Few Months Ago
Waning
Six
Where am I?
Waning
One
Is this the work of her Blood Art?
Feels like this entire space is distorted around her.
Only the Waning Blood Moons have been summoned.
That's never happened before.
Waning Five hasn't come yet.
We were warped!
It's her Blood Art again!
Waning
Six
Who is this woman?
What is she?
Lower your head and get on your knees.
Waning
Six
Prostrate yourselves before me.
It's Lord Muzan!
That's his voice! I didn't recognise him!
Waning
Six
His appearance and aura have completely changed.
His shapeshifting prowess is mind-boggling!
P-Please forgive us, my Lord! We didn't realise
you had assumed a different form and aura, so—
Waning
Four
Who granted you permission to speak?
Waning
Four
Don't presume to voice your worthless thoughts.
Answer my questions, and my questions only.
Rui was killed.
He was the Waning Five.
I have but one question to ask of you.
Why is it that the Waning
Blood Moons are so utterly weak?
Joining the ranks of the Blood Moons
should not be enough to satisfy you.
This is merely your starting point.
To devour more humans, to obtain more power...
Your starting point for proving yourself useful to me.
The members of the Waxing Six
have remained the same for over a century.
They have always been the ones to
dispose of those Hashira demon hunters.
But what about the Waning Six?
How many times have you been replaced?
Easy for you to say, but we...
"Easy for you to say, but we..."
What is it? Go ahead. Tell me.
He can read my mind?!
I'm screwed!
"Screwed" how, exactly?
Tell me.
Please forgive me, Lord Kibutsuji!
Please!
Please show me mercy!
I'm truly sorry!
I'm truly—
Waning
Six
Why is this happening?
Is he gonna kill me?
After everything I went through
to become a Blood Moon?
Why?
Why?!
This was supposed to be my
stepping stone towards greater things!
Do you fear the demon hunters more than you fear me?
No!
Every time you encounter a Hashira,
the only thing on your mind is how to escape.
Oh no, I wouldn't dream of it!
I'd put my life on the line to fight for you!
Are you refuting what I just said?
Waning
Four
This is it. This is the end.
Our minds are being read.
No matter what we do or say, he's gonna kill us!
There's no way we can beat him in a fight, either!
In that case...
All we can do is run!
Waning
One
What a fool.
Waning
One
I've gotta get out of here! Somehow!
Now that I've made it this far...
Waning
Three
I believe the Blood Moons are better off
consisting of just the Waxing Six.
I am hereby dismantling the Waning Six.
He caught me?
For real?
Was it that biwa player's Art?
No, I didn't hear her play anything at all.
Why?
Why can't I regenerate my body?
Do you have any last words?
I can still be of use to you!
If you could give me but a short reprieve,
I swear I'll be of use to you!
How long a reprieve are you asking for, specifically?
How do you intend to make yourself useful?
What exactly can you accomplish
with your current skills?
Your blood!
Give me a share of your blood
and I will acclimate without fail!
I will fight for you as an even more powerful demon!
What makes you think you can
order me to give you my blood?
How audacious.
Know your place.
You misunderstand!
I just...
Hold your tongue. I misunderstood nothing.
I'm never mistaken about anything.
I hold the authority.
My word is absolute.
You have no right to object to my words.
Whatever I say is right is right.
You just tried to tell me what to do.
That act merits death.
Waning
One
Do you have any last words?
That guy's gonna die as well.
Everything hinges on the Lord's mood.
I'm as good as dead, too.
Well, let's see...
It almost feels like this is right out of my dreams.
The kind where I get to die by your hand in person.
The other demons' final breaths
were like music to my ears!
I feel so blessed!
Waning
One
Since I just adore seeing others in despair and agony.
Waning
One
It's like a dream come true for me!
Waning
One
I thank you dearly for leaving me for last!
Waning
One
That's what I like to hear.
I shall share an ample amount of my blood with you.
Although you might be unable to withstand
the volume of blood and perish, anyway.
But, if you do manage to acclimate,
you will acquire even greater strength.
In that event, make yourself useful to me.
Kill the Hashira!
I will share even more of my blood if you can take out
the demon hunter wearing hanafuda-like earrings.
What the—?
I see something!
This vision is gushing into me
alongside Lord Muzan's blood!
If I kill the Hashira and this kid,
he'll give me more of his blood!
It's like a dream come true!
It's morning! Wake up!
What the heck?
What's going on?
The casualties of the Infinite Train are increasing.
Over forty people have gone missing.
You are to join Rengoku Kyoujurou on-site.
Head west at once!
Demon Slayer
I have decided to send Tanjirou and
the others on the Infinite Train mission.
Shinobu, may I ask what
made you recommend Tanjirou?
Tanjirou has a pure soul and is capable of
striving hard on a daily basis.
The promise he has shown has exceeded my expectations.
And above all, he has a clear goal in mind:
Claiming Kibutsuji's head.
As far as that goes, I'm in agreement with you.
Also, Tanjirou himself told me that his father
had used the Fire Breathing technique.
Oh?
At this point in time, there's no denying
that he still has a long way to go,
but perhaps Rengoku, the Flame Pillar,
might be able to provide some guidance.
You're right.
Considering his sister, who won't
devour humans even after becoming a demon,
and his encounter with Kibutsuji,
it very well might be Tanjirou's destiny.
All right, time to pack up!
Someone's coming around the corner.
He bumped into me even though I got out of the way.
Wait, huh? That guy...
Wasn't he at the Final Selection?
He got such an amazing build in such a short time.
But I wonder...
His scent...
Long time no see! Glad to see you're doing well!
Oh, really?
You're already leaving?
It wasn't for long, but I'm glad
we got to spend that time together.
Good luck!
Take care!
Thank you so much for looking out
for us, even though you were so busy!
Thanks to you, we can jump right back into the fray!
No need to thank me.
I only survived the Final Selection
by sheer luck, after all.
And since then, I've been too afraid to
go into battle. I'm nothing but a coward.
Hey, that doesn't matter.
You helped me out, so your feelings
have become part of me.
I'll carry them onto the battlefield.
Look after me again if I get hurt, okay?
Oh! There you are!
Kanao!
We're heading out now.
Thanks for everything!
Oh? What's that?
All I did was follow the Master's orders.
There's no need for you to thank me.
Farewell.
She actually spoke to me!
What was that you just flipped?
Farewell.
A coin?
It says "heads" and "tails", huh?
Why'd you flip it?
Farewell.
You really made it twirl!
I flip this to decide if I want to do something
without being ordered to do so.
I just decided whether or not to speak to you.
Heads was "don't speak", tails was "speak".
It came up tails, so I spoke with you.
Farewell.
Why don't you decide for yourself?
What did you want to do, Kanao?
It doesn't matter.
Nothing matters at all, so I can't decide for myself.
I don't think there's anything
in the world that doesn't matter.
I guess the voice in your heart is but a mere whisper.
Sure, following orders is important, but...
Hey, can I borrow that for a sec?
Yes.
Thanks!
Okay! Let's flip it to decide!
Decide what?
Whether or not
you're gonna listen to the voice
in your heart from now on!
I flipped it too high!
Heads! Let's make it heads!
If it comes up heads, you're gonna
start following your own heart!
Huh? Where'd it go?
Oh, is that it?
Look at that, Kanao! I caught it!
Are you ready?
Which side did it land on?
His back was blocking it,
so I couldn't catch a glimpse.
It's heads!
Kanao!
Good luck!
It's the heart that drives people forward.
Your heart can grow as strong as you want it to!
All right! See you again sometime!
H-How did you make it come up heads?
I saw his hand when he flipped it.
I'm sure he didn't cheat.
Just by chance.
Besides, even if it were tails, I was planning on
tossing it over and over until it came up heads!
Take care!
You can do it!
Hooray!
Please take this.
Thanks!
Don't eat it right now!
Please go out and defeat tons of demons!
You can count on us!
I told you not to eat it right now!
Shut up!
Tomioka!
Are you heading into battle now?
Yes!
I hear you've mastered
Permanent Total Concentration Breathing.
Yes!
Keep at it.
I will.
Tomioka...
About Nezuko... Thank you very much.
I had no idea you were putting
your life on the line for us.
I just don't know how I could ever thank you.
Thank me by doing exemplary work.
Our duty as Demon Slayers is to slay demons.
That's all.
Right!
Take care, you guys!
You're all heartbroken to say
goodbye to me, aren't you?
I can stay behind if it upsets you so!
Master Zenitsu, please try to learn how to be
considerate and respectful of girls.
Right.
I'm feeling giddy.
But you do feel a little sad
that I'm leaving, don't you?
Not at all!
Okay, guys!
We're heading out!
Hey... Hey! Hey!
Wha—
Wh-Wha—
What the hell is this creature?
I bet it's that thing!
The master of this land—
No, the ruler of this land!
See how long and intimidating it is?
There's no mistaking it!
Looks like it's asleep right now,
but don't let your guard down!
Uh, no. It's just a train.
First time seeing one?
Shush! Calm down!
I'll lead the charge!
No, you calm down, Inosuke!
You never know, it might be
the guardian spirit of this land.
It might not be a good idea to attack it.
No, didn't you hear me? It's just a steam train.
You know what a "train" is, right?
It's a vehicle for transporting people.
You damn country bumpkins!
Huh? "Train"? Ah, so this is what the crow meant!
What's his problem?
Comin' through!
Stop that! You're embarrassing us!
What do you think you're doing?
Hey, they've got swords!
Call the police!
Oh, shit! Crap, crap, crap!
Run!
We went through hell and back
thanks to you, Inosuke! Apologize right now!
Why'd we have to run away from
the police in the first place?!
The Demon Slayers aren't officially
recognised by the government!
We can't exactly walk around
in broad daylight with our swords.
And they'd just think we're crazy
if we started blabbering on about demons.
Even though we're working so hard?
That's just how it is, unfortunately.
Let's hide our swords on our backs for now.
Nice try. Put on some clothes, moron.
Oh, crap! The train's leaving!
Are the cops still around?
We'll have to go even if they are.
I'm taking you head-on, master of this land!
Hey, moron!
We should go, too!
Hey! You three!
Tanjirou! Inosuke!
Zenitsu!
Man, it's fast!
Say, Tanjirou.
Are you sure about bringing Nezuko along?
Wouldn't the Demon Slayer HQ
be the safest place to keep her?
Yeah. It's fine.
No matter where we go,
Nezuko and I will always be together.
We're never gonna be apart again.
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
I now know what I cherish most
boku wo tsurete susume
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
I will save you no matter what!
Your big brother will definitely save you, you hear?
kowabaru kokoro
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
Kibutsuji Muzan!
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
I won't let you get away!
No matter where you go!
sore dakesa
And that's all I need
We'll be staying together.
yoru no nioi ni
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
We refuse to live apart from one another.
I spent all thirty nights
sora nirandemo
That I'll never be able to escape
No one will ever sever
Staring into the sky
kawatte ikeru no wa
All I can do is adapt
the bond
between us!
jibun jishin dake
To the world I now find myself in
sore dakesa
And nothing more
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
I now know what I cherish most
Nezuko,
I promise you...
boku wo tsurete susume
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
doushitatte
And I can't afford to stop!
kesenai yume mo
I can't erase my fantasies
tomarenai ima mo
And there's no way to rewind time
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
But so long as I have someone left to protect
nandemo tachiagare
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
sekai ni uchinomesarete
This world once showed me true despair
makeru imi wo shitta
Made me wallow in my own failures
guren no hana yo sakihokore
But now my path is bright and clear
unmei wo terashite
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
Hito shirezu hakanai
Ever-fleeting visions of what could have been
hito shirezu hakanai
chiriyuku ketsumatsu
Wilting away before my very eyes
Mujou ni yabureta
Dominated by selfish cruelty
mujou ni yabureta
himei no kaze fuku
A raging storm plows over the land
Dareka no warau kage
Crying out with laments of others
dareka no warau kage
dareka no nakigoe
As everyone willingly sacrifices one another
Daremo ga shiawase wo negatteru
Just wishing for their own happiness
daremo ga shiawase wo negatteru
doushitatte
And I can't afford to stop!
kesenai yume mo
I can't erase my fantasies
tomarenai ima mo
And there's no way to rewind time
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
But so long as I have someone left to protect
arigatou kanashimi yo
I'll take pride in bearing their pain
sekai ni uchinomesarete
This world once showed me true despair
makeru imi wo shitta
Made me wallow in my own failures
guren no hana yo sakihokore
But now my path is bright and clear
unmei wo terashite
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
My fate dyed in deep red
unmei wo terashite
Demon Slayer
Kamado Tanjirou's
Coming-of-Age Arc
Fin