How?
How did this happen?
Nezuko, don't die! Don't you die on me!
I will save you no matter what!
So please, don't die!
Your big brother will definitely save you, you hear?
Tanjirou?
Your face is all covered in soot.
Come over here.
It might get dangerous once it starts snowing.
It's fine for you to just stay home.
Well, I want everyone to eat their fill on New Year's,
so I'm gonna go sell as much charcoal as I can.
Thank you.
Tanjirou!
You're going to town again today?
I'm coming with you!
Oh no, you won't!
You know you can't keep up with Tanjirou.
But Mom!
No buts.
He won't be taking the cart today,
so you won't be able to ride along if you're tired.
Tanjirou!
I wanna come with you!
I promise I'll be helpful!
Thank you, Hanako.
But you're staying home today.
And so are you, Shigeru.
I'll get you lots of tasty stuff while I'm there, okay?
For real?
Yeah.
And Hanako, I'll read you a book when I get back.
Okay!
That's a good girl.
Thank you so much, Tanjirou.
No problem.
All right, I'll be heading out now.
Takeo.
Could you go chop some wood?
Don't overwork yourself, though.
I mean, sure, but...
I wanted to do it together with you...
There, there.
What's wrong with you?!
Take's all red!
Sh-Shut up!
There, there.
Knock it off already!
Hurry back, okay?
Stay safe, okay?
Tanjirou!
Ah, Nezuko.
I was just putting Rokuta to sleep.
Don't want him making a scene when you leave.
He really misses Dad.
Everyone's really been clinging to you
ever since he passed away.
Have a nice trip!
Our lives aren't always easy,
but we're happy.
However, life can be as fickle as the weather.
Ever-changing, never stagnating.
It won't always be sunny,
but snowfall doesn't last forever, either.
And...
whenever happiness meets its end,
it always carries
the smell of blood.
Oh my, Tanjirou!
I can't believe you came down
the mountain in this weather.
You're such a hard worker!
You might catch a cold!
This is nothing, really.
Are you in need of some charcoal?
Hey, Tanjirou!
Can I have some?
Oh, and thanks for fixing
my sliding doors the other day!
I need some as well!
Tanjirou!
Oh man, perfect timing!
I'm being accused of breaking this plate!
Help a brother out, will ya?
Give it a sniff!
It smells like a cat.
See?!
Oh dear, so it was a cat?
I told you it wasn't me!
Tanjirou!
Could you give me a hand with this luggage?
Gosh, it's gotten dark already.
I'm glad I sold everything, though.
Tanjirou, hold it!
You weren't planning on going
back up the mountain, were you?
It's too dangerous.
I've got a good nose, so I'll be fine.
You can stay here for the night.
Get over here.
But...
Don't argue, make haste!
Before the demons show up.
Thanks for dinner.
Say, Saburo.
What are demons like?
Man-eating demons have always
roamed the lands after dark.
That's why you shouldn't stroll around at night.
If you're done eating, sleep.
You can set off at sunrise.
Couldn't these demons enter people's homes?
Yes, they can. And they do.
But can't they just eat everyone then?
That's why the demon hunters hunt them down.
Have for ages.
I'm cutting the lights.
Go to sleep now.
Saburo has been all alone ever since he lost his family.
He's probably lonely.
I'll bring my siblings along next time.
It's fine, there are no demons to be afraid of.
But come to think of it,
Grandma used to say the same thing
when she was still with us.
Be careful, you hear?
Sure!
Whenever happiness meets its end,
it always carries...
The smell of blood!
Nezuko!
What happened here? Are you okay?
Just what happened here?
Mom...
Hanako...
Takeo...
Shigeru...
Nezuko...
Rokuta...
Nezuko's the only one who's still warm!
If I can get her to a doctor,
she might still make it!
How did this happen?
Was it a bear?
Maybe it wasn't able to hibernate.
I can hardly breathe.
The air's so cold that my lungs sting!
Keep running!
Move your legs faster!
There's still a long way to town.
Hurry!
Don't you die on me!
I will save you no matter what!
Your big brother will definitely save you, you hear?
Oh, no!
The snow saved me.
Though it made me slip to begin with.
Nezuko?
Nezuko, are you all right?
Don't stand up!
Let me carry you to town, okay?
Nezuko!
Sh-She's...
a demon!
Is this what Saburo was talking about?
Nezuko? A man-eating demon?
No, there's no way.
Nezuko's been a human from the day she was born!
However, her scent is no longer the same.
But there's no way she killed them!
She was lying as if she were protecting Rokuta,
and there's no blood on her mouth or hands.
And then there's that scent...
That one other scent!
Her body got bigger!
And she's getting stronger and stronger!
While I was sleeping all carefree at Saburo's house,
everyone was brutally murdered!
It must have hurt a lot.
You suffered, didn't you?
I'm so sorry I wasn't there to save you.
I have to at least save Nezuko somehow.
But she's so strong! I can't push her back!
Nezuko!
Fight against it, Nezuko!
Don't give in!
You've gotta hang in there!
Whatever you do, don't become a demon!
You've gotta stay strong!
Hang in there!
What the...
Who's that?
A sword?
Why are you protecting that thing?
She's my sister!
She's my little sister!
Nezuko!
You call that thing your little sister?
Don't move!
My job is to slay demons.
As such, I will claim your sister's head.
Please wait!
She hasn't killed anyone!
Back at my house, there was another scent.
One I had never smelled before!
It probably belongs to the one who killed my family!
It wasn't Nezuko!
I don't know what's going on with her now, but...
But still...
It's simple.
Her wounds were exposed to demon blood,
so she transformed into a demon.
That's how man-eating demons multiply.
Nezuko would never eat humans!
You've gotta be kidding.
She was about to eat you just now.
You're wrong!
I'm sure she still recognizes me!
I won't let her hurt anyone!
I'll turn her back into a human!
I swear I'll find a way to cure her!
There is no cure.
Once a human becomes a demon,
there is no turning back.
I'll find a way!
I swear I'll turn her back!
So please! Please don't kill her!
I'll even hunt down the one
who slaughtered my family!
I'll make everything okay again!
So please!
Please!
Please don't do it!
Please, don't take anyone else from me.
Please stop.
I beg you!
Please don't kill my little sister!
Please, don't do it!
Please...
Never show your back to an enemy!
Stop that pathetic grovelling!
If it was the least bit effective,
your family wouldn't be dead!
You're a weakling—a coward who folds at adversity.
And you think you can cure your sister,
let alone even find your enemy?
Don't make me laugh!
The weak have neither rights nor options!
It's their fate to be crushed by the strong!
There may be demons out there
who know a way to cure your sister!
But don't even for a second think
they'll happily go along with your wishes!
Naturally, I have no reason to care about you either!
That's just reality!
Why did you throw yourself over your sister earlier?
Was that your way of protecting her?
Why didn't you swing your axe?
Why did you turn your back to me?
All those blunders led to your sister's capture!
I should've skewered her along with you!
Don't cry.
Don't despair.
Now's not the time for that.
I know you're devastated right now.
Your family was massacred,
and your sister turned into a demon.
It must be painful.
Your heart is likely crushed right now.
I get it.
Had I gotten here even half a day sooner,
your family might have still been alive right now.
However, you can't turn back time.
Feel the anger.
The pure, unforgiving wrath will
become the force that drives you forward!
With such fragile resolve,
protecting or curing your sister,
let alone getting revenge will be mere fantasy!
N—
No!
A straightforward attack driven solely by emotion.
You fool!
Where's his axe?
Right before he passed behind the tree,
he threw that rock at me
and, simultaneously, flung the axe into the air.
He hid his hands as he pretended to attack
so I wouldn't realize he was unarmed.
He knew he didn't stand a chance head-on,
so he tried to take me out after I struck him down!
This kid...
Damn it!
She's gonna eat him!
Nezuko...
It wasn't Nezuko!
She would never eat humans!
He's by no means
the first to make such claims,
only to be eaten later.
When a demon is starving, it will eat any
human flesh it comes across. Even its own family.
They have no other way to sustain themselves.
I've seen it happen more times than I can count.
This girl has been gravely wounded,
and she's expending energy to heal those injuries.
Her transformation must have also drained her greatly.
That means she's undoubtedly
severely starved right now.
She must've wanted to feast
on a human as soon as possible.
Yet she opted to protect him instead,
and is even going so far as to attack me...
There might just be
something
special about these two.
I'm sorry for leaving you behind, Tanjirou.
Take good care of Nezuko for me, okay?
You awake?
Go see an old man named Urokodaki Sakonji
who lives at the foot of Mt. Sagiri.
Tell him that Tomioka Giyuu sent you.
Your sister should be fine for now while it's cloudy,
but make sure she's never exposed to the sun.
Let's go.
Episode_1
Cruelty
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
kowabaru kokoro
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
That I'll never be able to escape
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
All I can do is adapt
kawatte ikeru no wa
To the world I now find myself in
jibun jishin dake
And nothing more
sore dakesa
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
And I can't afford to stop!
doushitatte
I can't erase my fantasies
kesenai yume mo
And there's no way to rewind time
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as I have someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
This world once showed me true despair
sekai ni uchinomesarete
Made me wallow in my own failures
makeru imi wo shitta
But now my path is bright and clear
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
unmei wo terashite