Take this!
Move it!
Draw your sword and fight me!
You spineless punk!
Enough already!
I'll just skewer you along with that box!
Knock it off!
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
kowabaru kokoro
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
That I'll never be able to escape
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
All I can do is adapt
kawatte ikeru no wa
To the world I now find myself in
jibun jishin dake
And nothing more
sore dakesa
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
And I can't afford to stop!
doushitatte
I can't erase my fantasies
kesenai yume mo
And there's no way to rewind time
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as I have someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
This world once showed me true despair
sekai ni uchinomesarete
Made me wallow in my own failures
makeru imi wo shitta
But now my path is bright and clear
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
unmei wo terashite
Episode_14
The_House
with_the
Wisteria_Family_Crest
Episode_14
The_House
with_the
Wisteria_Family_Crest
Knock it off!
H-He just broke his bones!
Aren't you a Demon Slayer?
Don't you get why Zenitsu refuses to draw his sword?
It's because we're forbidden from drawing
our blades on one another without reason.
Yet here you are, giving him a one-sided beatdown!
Is this your idea of having fun?
You're scum. Absolute scum.
Oh, that's your problem?
My bad.
In that case, let's settle this with fisticuffs.
No, no, I don't think you get it at all!
To begin with...
We're not supposed to fight each other, period!
Fighting barehanded doesn't make it fine!
Listen to me!
Gee, look at him! How can he move like that?
Tanjirou just fractured some of his ribs.
Hold on, isn't Tanjirou violating the rules, too?
Oh, and he's got broken bones, too.
Th-This guy...
His attacks aim bizarrely low!
It's almost like I'm...
I'm...
fighting a four-legged beast!
Hit him from a low angle.
Even lower than your opponent!
His joints...
That flexibility is superhuman!
I'm pretty awesome, dontcha think?
Did he just repeat that?
He's so full of himself.
Check out what else I can do!
Stop that! That's a bad idea!
You shouldn't be doing that with broken bones!
You'll just make it worse!
Worse? Fine by me!
Nothing can top the pleasure I'm feeling right now!
You should really be thinking harder about the future!
Why would I care?
You need to
calm down a little!
That sound! Did your skulls fracture?
Huh? A girl? What? Your face!
What the hell?
You got a problem with my face or something?
You're one creepy guy, you know that?
You've got quite the girly face
for such a ripped body.
What the hell are you staring at my face for?
I-I'm not!
I'm not looking at your face!
We don't have a problem with your face!
It's quite petite, fair-skinned,
and therefore attractive!
Come and say that to my fist!
Not happening! I'm done fighting!
Try head-butting me one more time!
Nope, I'm done!
I told you to do it! Now come!
Just relax for a bit! Are you fine?
Hey, Mr. Forehead!
Let me tell you my name.
It's Hashibira Inosuke!
Don't you dare forget!
How do you spell that?
Spell? Spell...
I don't know how to read or write!
My name is written on my loinclo—
What's wrong?
He froze.
What's the matter?
He collapsed!
Is he dead?
He's not.
It's probably a concussion.
Since I head-butted the hell out of him.
Are you okay, Tanjirou?
Yeah.
Amazing! Can I touch your head?
Here!
That's scary!
There isn't a single drop of blood
coming from Tanjirou's head.
Just how hard is his forehead?
Hard enough make that wild boar pass out, at least.
Tanjirou, your head is so hard!
You think so?
Demon Slayer
He's alive!
Fight me! Fight me!
Hey, you! Come 'ere!
This is how he acts when he wakes up?
I hate that more than anything!
What the hell are you guys doing?
It's a burial.
Come help us out, Inosuke.
There are still people who
were killed inside the house.
What's the point of burying
the corpses of these creatures?
I ain't doing that! Count me out!
Forget that! Fight me instead!
Man, he really is a special case.
What does he mean, "what's the point"?
I see.
You can't do it because your wounds are hurting you.
Those two are beyond help!
Both of them are completely bonkers.
Don't worry, it's fine.
Everyone has a different pain threshold.
It's a lot of work to carry the bodies
outside and give them a proper burial.
We'll all do the best we can, so don't worry!
He's completely off.
You should go get some rest.
Sorry for asking too much of you!
Don't underestimate me, dammit!
I'll bury a hundred—No, two hundred of your corpses!
Just you watch! I'm going to
bury more than any of you!
What is that guy doing?
You're better off ignoring him.
Yeah.
Descend the mountain!
That crow is talking!
Just don't think anymore.
Okay.
All right, follow me!
Follow yours truly!
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
We're descending the mountain.
We're not done with our battle yet!
You're exhausted, aren't you?
Come on, we're heading down.
I'm not exhausted!
Let's fight!
I won't have it!
I won't have it! I won't have it!
You can't go, Shouichi!
You're so strong, Shouichi!
Shouichi is the one who's gonna protect me!
Can't you see Shouichi doesn't want to stay?
Please don't leave me behind!
Cease this right now!
Hold out your hands!
That will ward off demons.
Carrier of the rareblood,
keep that on your person!
It smells of wisteria.
Wisteria?
It's a flower that demons can't tolerate.
You should hold onto that.
Demon repellent! Demon repellent!
We're truly grateful!
We can get home on our own.
Take care now!
Now then, follow me!
Follow yours truly!
Fight me!
I swear I'm gonna find a weak point
and take you down, loser!
My name's not "loser"!
It's Kamado Tanjirou!
Kamaboko Gonpachiro!
I'm gonna bring you down!
Who the hell are you talking about?
That'd be you!
I don't know anyone by that name!
Can't you just shut up?
Wisteria
A wisteria family crest...
Time to rest! Time to rest!
Since you've sustained heavy injuries,
you are to rest until you're fully recovered!
You sure it's okay to rest?
I just fought a demon despite being injured, y'know.
Ke-ke-ke.
"Ke-ke-ke"?
Let's eat this thing.
What?
Yes?
Sorry to bother you so late at night!
A monster!
It's a monster!
Hey, you!
Who the hell are you?
I see you're a demon hunter.
You look pretty weak!
Hey!
Come in.
That old lady sure walks fast!
This is where you'll be staying.
Here's a change of clothes.
And here is your meal.
She has to be a monster, Tanjirou!
That old lady's some kind of monster!
She's so fast, it's eerie! She's a monster!
A monster ha—
Use your chopsticks.
If you're that hungry, you can have this, too.
Here.
No!
He's totally forgotten about the box!
Gimme a break, you thug!
Moron! Eyelashes!
Here is your bedding.
There she is! The monster ha—
First come, first served!
I'm taking this one!
That's fine. Sleep wherever you want.
Where do you want to sleep, Zenitsu?
Here is the doctor.
Hello.
Yes.
Severe!
Who would've guessed that
all three of us had broken ribs?
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
3 ribs
4 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
4 ribs
l
3 ribs
2 ribs
l
4 ribs
3 ribs
l
2 ribs
This bump hurts a lot more than my ribs.
Sorry.
Hey, you'd better apologize.
It really hurt, you know.
Getting pounded to a pulp like that.
Say you're sorry.
I'll pass.
Say you're sorry!
I'll pass!
Just say you're sorry!
If you're gonna be like that,
we'll stop eating together with you.
What's up with that?
Meals always taste better
when you eat together, y'know.
He's right about that.
Did you guys hit your heads or something?
Who are you to talk?
Is there something I can help you with?
Monster!
Hey!
Wisteria
According to the crow,
this house with the wisteria family crest belongs to
a family that was once rescued by demon hunters,
Wisteria
which is why they take care of people
free of charge if they hunt demons.
Wisteria
That's what I was told, but I never thought
they'd greet us with this much hospitality.
Wisteria
Just how great are the Demon Slayers anyway?
Now that you mention it,
why did you join the Demon Slayers, Inosuke?
You had some kind of reason, right?
A Demon Slayer barged in on me on my mountain,
so we competed to see who was
stronger, and I seized his sword.
What an unfortunate soul.
And then, I heard there was something
called the "Final Selection",
and the fact that demons do exist.
So that's why you joined the Demon Slayers?
And hey, turns out both of us
grew up on mountains, huh?
Don't lump me in with you!
I don't have any parents or siblings!
Testing my strength against other
living beings is my one and only pleasure!
Is that right?
Tanjirou.
Since no one else is asking,
I'll be the one to do so.
Why are you traveling with a demon?
Zenitsu...
You knew about that and
still protected the box, huh?
You really are a great guy, you know that?
Thanks!
You...
You really shouldn't heap so much praise on me!
I've got a keen sense of smell.
I knew it from the start.
Just how kind you are.
And how strong...
No, I'm not strong.
Don't give me that.
I haven't forgiven you for stopping me
from having Shouichi tag along.
It's trying to come out!
It's all right.
How can it be all right?
Huh? Huh?
Shush!
It's the middle of the night, Zenitsu!
Why won't he take the bait?
Even when I stole his food...
Come to think of it, what did it take to make him mad?
I forgot.
Oh my gosh! It's not even locked?
P-P-Protect me!
Someone please protect me!
Even you'll do, Inosuke!
Stay away from me!
It's out!
I've got to hide! I'm so scared!
Nezuko!
I've been thinking too much.
Zenitsu...
Nezuko's my—
Tanjirou...
Listen here.
Z-Zenitsu?
Just who do you think you are?
You've been traveling with a girl this cute?
With a girl this cute in tow,
day after day, you've been traveling,
and you've been on cloud nine
the whole time, huh?
Zenitsu, it's not like—
Give me back all the blood I shed!
I... Listen, I...
I didn't give it my all just so you could
spend time in la-la land, making out with a girl!
That's not what I got pummeled and
kicked by that weird wild boar for!
Zenitsu, calm down!
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
The Demon Slayers isn't something
you join just for the fun of it!
Guys like you must be purged! Pronto!
Come to think of it, there's also the crimes of
thwarting my marriage and sending Shouichi home.
Urgent purging!
Don't you ever underestimate the Demon Slayers!
A guy like you! A guy like you!
Zenitsu, cut it out!
Mock the Demon Slayers
and you'll be sent straight to Hell!
You shall feel my wrath!
I don't want to be imprisoned by sadness
kanashimi ni torewaretaku wa nai
I don't want to come back
utsumuita basho ni
To the place I cast my head down crying
namida wo otoshite yukitakunai
Free from the shackles of fate
unmei wo furihodoite
You're supposed to start running
hashiridaseru hazu nanda
That dream is meant to come true
negai wa kanau hazu nanda
Break free from the troubles of yesterday
tatakitsubuse kinou no katou
Pray for the future from the edge of darkness
Ride the wind that's leading the way
mukai kaze wo nototte
Face the unseen beyond the storm
arashi no saki wa mienaku tatte
There's only one path—
mou michi wa erabenai kachinokore
To make it out alive!
The choice between love and light
mayoi wa itsumo aijou to hikari wo hakari ni kakeru
Will always cast doubt upon your mind
Now rise up once more
saa tachiagarunda mou ichido
Now, where might you strike down
ima kimi wa sono yaiba wo
With that blade of yours?
doko he furiorosu
Demon Slayer
Combined Junior and Senior High School!
Tales of the
Demon Slayer Academy
Tales of the Demon Slayer Academy!
Self-introductions
The new semester's begun.
Announce your names.
Yes, sir!
I'm Kamado Tanjirou!
My family runs a bakery,
and I'm the eldest of six children!
No piercings
Take off those earrings.
I'm Hashibira Inosuke!
No dressing
down
Button up your shirt.
Um, I'm Agatsuma—
No hair coloring
Dye your hair black.
But this is my natural hair color.
No hair coloring
No backtalk!
Unfair!
It's also forbidden to hold bread in your mouth!
Next Episode:
Mount Natagumo
Next, Episode 15,
"Mount Natagumo".
Next Episode:
Mount Natagumo
To Be Continued
Spartan education!