No way...
My sword!
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
kowabaru kokoro
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
That I'll never be able to escape
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
All I can do is adapt
kawatte ikeru no wa
To the world I now find myself in
jibun jishin dake
And nothing more
sore dakesa
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
And I can't afford to stop!
doushitatte
I can't erase my fantasies
kesenai yume mo
And there's no way to rewind time
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as I have someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
This world once showed me true despair
sekai ni uchinomesarete
Made me wallow in my own failures
makeru imi wo shitta
But now my path is bright and clear
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
unmei wo terashite
Episode_19
The_Fire_God
Wow!
This guy's on a different level!
The force of his strike is in a different class!
He's head and shoulders above the rest!
He sliced through that
tough-as-nails monster like tofu!
Amazing! Simply amazing!
Who is this guy?
Damn, I still have goosebumps!
Hold up a second!
Fight me, Mismatched Haori!
You beat that Blood Moon!
And now I'm gonna beat you!
That's how it works!
Once I've done that
that'll make me the strongest!
Get back to training, you buffoon.
The f—
That thing doesn't even compare
to an actual Blood Moon.
You couldn't even figure that out?
Sure I can!
I never thought that dumbass
was a Blood Moon, either!
Tanjirou was the one that said he was a Blood Moon!
All I did was repeat what he said, got it?
What the hell? Did he just tie me up?
So fast!
This guy's so fast.
Hey, wait! Get back here!
You have no business on the battlefield
if you can't even tell what state you're in.
I can't hear you!
You're too quiet and you walk too fast!
I told you to get back here!
Untie me right now!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Yoo-hoo!
Are you all right?
Gramps...
Whoever might you be calling "Gramps"?
Gramps showed up just now
and told me not to give up.
That was your life flashing before your eyes.
There's a theory that states that the reason
you see such images right before dying
is because you're searching for a way to
avoid death by looking through all your memories.
Well, it's not like I can confirm that,
since I've never experienced it myself.
Right, you did a good job slowing down
the venom with your breathing.
Had you not done that,
you'd have become a spiderling ages ago.
I'll administer an antidote now, okay?
Hurry up! Over here!
Can we get them down?
Be careful, okay?
It's all good! They're still alive!
My sword was cut in half!
I can't believe it!
The webs this boy is controlling...
Are they even tougher than
the body of that other demon?
Master Urokodaki, Mr. Haganezuka,
please forgive me!
Due to my inexperience, my sword has now broken!
This is no time to worry about that!
Think! Think!
If I can't cut through those webs,
I'll have to get right up in his face instead!
It's hopeless!
I can't get through those attacks.
It's like those webs have a life of their own!
He's obviously toying with me, and yet
I'm still getting overwhelmed by these attacks!
Well?
Do you still refuse to take back your words?
Fine.
In that case, I'll slash you to ribbons.
I can't dodge them all!
Nezuko!
I'm sorry that you had to protect me!
A girl emerged from that box on his back.
But she has the aura of a demon!
Hey, you...
Is that...
That girl...
Is she your sibling?
What if she is?
The wound's so deep!
Her left wrist is about to fall off!
Hurry up and heal!
Siblings...
Siblings.
The sister's turned into a demon.
R-Rui?
Yet, she still stays by his side.
The younger sister protected the elder brother.
She risked her own life.
That's a genuine bond!
I want it!
W-Wait a second!
Please hold on for a minute!
I'm your elder sister!
Please don't desert me!
Shut your mouth!
None of you ever managed to
fulfill the roles bestowed upon you.
Not a single time.
W-Wait...
I was the elder sister you wanted, wasn't I?
Please let me redeem myself!
If you want to atone, go kill those people
wandering all over the mountain.
Once you've done that,
I'll forgive you for what just transpired.
F-Fine.
I'll go kill them.
Boy...
Boy, let's have a chat.
Come on out.
Boy?
Chat?
You see, I was really moved.
Seeing the bond you two share gave me chills.
I doubt there are any words in the entire world
that can perfectly describe how moved I was.
And yet, the only fate left for you
is to die by my hands.
It'd be sad if that came to pass, right?
But there's an option left for you.
A single option that lets you escape that outcome.
That sister of yours...
Hand her over to me.
If you hand her over without a struggle,
I will at least spare your life.
What the hell are you talking about?
From today onward, that little sister of yours
shall become my little sister.
You didn't think I'd actually agree to that, right?
Nezuko isn't some kind of item
you can freely trade around.
She's a living being with her own will.
She will never become your sister!
It's fine, you don't need to worry.
I'll forge a bond between us.
I'm stronger than her.
I will forge a bond with terror.
I'll teach her what happens if she defies me.
I've had enough of this crazy talk!
Using terror to shackle someone hand and foot
is not what a true family bond is like!
You will never get what you desire
if you don't fix up that misunderstanding!
You irritate me.
Could you not raise your voice, please?
We just can't see eye to eye, can we?
I will never hand Nezuko over to the likes of you!
That's fine, I suppose.
I'll just kill you then.
Not if I take your head first!
That's the spirit!
I'd love to see you try.
Waning
Five
Let's see if you can even lay a scratch on a Blood Moon!
Waning
Five
Demon Slayer
Family...
A father has his role as the father.
The mother has her role as the mother.
The parents care for their offspring,
and the elder siblings protect the younger ones.
No matter what.
Even if it costs them their own lives.
Waning
Five
The way I see it, if you don't understand your own role,
there's no reason for you to live.
How about you?
What is your role?
Your role is to relinquish your sister to me
and remove yourself from the picture.
If you can't do that, you've lost your reason to live.
Waning
Five
Since you can't defeat me.
Waning Five.
That's what I thought!
This pressure...
This kid is a genuine Blood Moon!
Cutting through those webs won't be easy.
What should I do?
With this shattered blade...
If his neck is even tougher than those webs...
Waning
Five
I don't like that glare in your eyes.
You fool.
Do you really think you can defeat me?
Waning
Five
.
Nezuko!
Waning
Five
All right, she's in my custody now.
Waning
Five
Have you finally realised what your role is?
Let her go!
Had you only done as you were told,
I would have spared your life.
Waning
Five
She's gone!
Nezuko!
Waning
Five
Cease that hollering.
She's a demon. A scratch like that won't kill her.
Waning
Five
But it looks like I'll have to teach her a lesson after all.
Waning
Five
I'm going to let her bleed for a while.
If she still doesn't learn to be docile,
I'll just leave her to hang like that until daybreak
Waning
Five
and have her roast a bit.
Let her...
Let Nezuko go!
.
Waning
Five
.
Look.
I'm sure I'm mistaken, but...
.
You didn't think you could lop off my head
just by getting close to me, right?
Fine by me. Here.
Give it your best shot.
The blade won't pierce him!
See?
Didn't I tell you?
Waning
Five
You don't stand a chance against me.
Waning
Five
My body's sturdier than any of my webs.
If you can't cut through those, there's no way
in hell you'll chop off my head.
H-He's strong...
His power is on a completely different level
from any demons I've fought so far!
So this is a Blood Moon's power.
The power of a demon with a
high concentration of Kibutsuji's blood.
Waning
Five
You're so loud.
Mind shutting up for a bit?
Stop that!
Waning
Five
I'm your elder brother now.
Enough of that infernal wailing.
Calm down! Don't let your anger get the best of you!
You'll play right into his hands!
Waning
Five
Did she pass out?
Waning
Five
She's asleep?
This demon gives off an unusual vibe.
She's different from other demons somehow.
How interesting.
Concentrate!
Get your breathing under control!
Unleash your strongest and most decisive form!
Total Concentration!
.
You still don't realise it's futile?
Waning
Five
Water Breathing!
Tenth Form!
The Perpetual Cycle of Death and Rebirth!
I did it! I cut through the webs!
Waning
Five
He's gaining more and more force with each rotation.
Waning
Five
This could spell trouble.
I can do it!
If I close the distance between us, I can beat him!
Say,
Five
you didn't think I've been going all out yet, did you?
Blood Arts!
Cutting Gossamer Cage!
Waning
Five
I've had enough of the likes of you.
Waning
Five
Farewell.
Waning
Five
No way!
I can't cut through these!
I haven't gotten enough spin yet!
These webs are giving off a totally different scent!
But I can't afford to lose here!
I'm gonna die!
I'll lose!
I...
Dad...
Tanjirou.
Breathe.
Get your breathing under control
and become the Fire God.
When I close my eyes, I can still see it
me wo tojite omoidasu
Those times long gone which I held so dear
sugisarishi ano koro wo
Tanjirou.
Look.
It's your father's dance.
But I can't go back, can't rewind time
modorenai kaerenai
Our family works with fire,
so to ward off injuries and disasters,
we offer this dance to the Fire God,
along with our prayers, on New Year's Day.
And now the darkness keeps spreading around me
hirogatta fukai yami
Hey, Mom.
How can Dad dance in the snow
for so long when he's so frail?
I bet my lungs would freeze.
I use a special breathing technique.
It's a special breathing form that invigorates you,
no matter how much you move.
Breathing?
That's right.
If you can master the correct way to breathe,
you'll be able to dance forever, too.
The cold won't bother you, either.
Tanjirou.
If nothing else, make sure at least that dance
and these earrings get passed down to you.
Promise me.
I can't go back, can't rewind time
modorenai kaerenai
Dance for the Fire God!
Now only the darkness remains around me
ima wa tada fukai yami
Waltz!
My webs!
But then I hear a gentle laugh
nakitakunaru you na
Don't stop!
Keep moving onward!
If you stop now,
Bringing tears to my eyes
yasashii oto
the backlash from forcibly switching
between breathing forms will kick in!
Once that happens, you won't be
able to move for a while!
In the midst of this painful journey it says
donna ni kurushikutemo
That's why you have to finish it now!
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
Run!
"Don't give up!"
susume
"Keep living on!"
You have to protect Nezuko!
Carrying me past the despair
zetsubou wo tachi
No matter how much I might still lose
ushinattemo ushinattemo
This guy!
I have no choice but to continue living on
ikiteiku shika nai
There it is! The opening thread!
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
You've gotta take him down now!
Even if
There's something I have to protect
mamoru mono ga aru
it means getting cut down alongside him!
Nezuko.
Wake up, Nezuko.
You have to go save your brother.
I know you can do it, Nezuko.
Do your best.
Please, Nezuko.
Or your brother will be killed, too!
No matter how much I might still lose
ushinattemo ushinattemo
Blood Arts!
I have no choice but to continue living on
ikiteiku shika nai
Blood Burst!
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
No way!
My webs were incinerated?!
There's something I have to protect
mamoru mono ga aru
No one will ever sever
the bond
between us!
This is the fate I've been entrusted with
ware ni kasu itaku wo
I've made up my mind, so I have to follow through
unmei to kakugo suru
I might struggle as it tries to tear me down
doro wo name agaitemo
But I can't ignore this tiny invisible thread
me ni mienu hosoi ito
It connects me to a gentle smile
nakitaku naru you na
Bringing tears to my eyes
yasashii oto
In the midst of this frustrating journey it says
donna ni kuyashikutemo
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
"Keep moving!"
mae e
"Move forward!"
A song in my heart
utae
Carries me past the despair
zetsubou wo tachi
No matter how painful it might be
kizutsuitemo kizutsuitemo
I have no choice but to get back on my feet
tachiagaru shika nai
No matter how overwhelming it might be
donna ni uchinomesaretemo
There's something I have to protect
mamoru mono ga aru
Demon Slayer
Rustle
PREVIEW
I wonder why I suddenly remembered
the Dance for the Fire God right then.
Thanks, Dad.
Thanks to that, I was able to
cut through that demon's neck!
Thank you, too, Nezuko!
This week, I have a Taisho secret
about the Kamado Family!
After every festival, Mom and Dad
would always toast rice crackers for us.
Rustle
PREVIEW
Those were the good times,
making loud cracking noises while we ate them!
Thanks, Nezuko. This isn't the time
to bask in memories, huh?
Next, Episode 20, "Pretend Family"!
Did I actually defeat a Blood Moon?
To Be Continued