Naho! Kiyo! Sumi!
I'd like you to help me train.
Could you please clobber me with these blanket beaters
if I interrupt my Breathing while I'm asleep?
Please help me out!
Sure!
Thank you!
He's got it, right?
He's doing a great job!
Yeah!
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
kowabaru kokoro
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
That I'll never be able to escape
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
All I can do is adapt
kawatte ikeru no wa
To the world I now find myself in
jibun jishin dake
And nothing more
sore dakesa
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
And I can't afford to stop!
doushitatte
I can't erase my fantasies
kesenai yume mo
And there's no way to rewind time
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as I have someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
This world once showed me true despair
sekai ni uchinomesarete
Made me wallow in my own failures
makeru imi wo shitta
But now my path is bright and clear
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
unmei wo terashite
Episode_25
Tsuguko,
Tsuyuri_Kanao
Episode_25
Tsuguko,
Tsuyuri_Kanao
I'm utterly pathetic...
Please give me another chance!
Sure!
If you'd please!
We believe in you!
This time for sure!
Please give me one more chance!
You came alone again today, Tanjirou?
I'm sorry!
I tried to get them to tag along, but...
Well, it doesn't matter to me.
I'll give them another nudge later!
I'm getting used to training
while maintaining my Breathing!
I still can't keep it up all day unless I push myself,
Four-hundred-ninety-seven!
but the longer I can last,
the bigger the stamina boost I'll get!
Four-hundred-ninety-eight!
Four-hundred-ninety-nine!
Five hundred!
Five-hundred-one!
You can do it!
I can do this!
I'm slowly catching up to her!
I can keep up!
Ow, ow, ow...
Thanks a bunch!
Zenitsu! Inosuke!
I refuse to get involved.
You can do it!
It broke!
Now all that's left to do is break this one!
Yeah!
I did it!
Thanks, all of you!
Shit.
Tanjirou's already gone off to train.
The sun's only just come up.
I'm not really one to put my all in anything.
There's nothing more draining than perseverance.
Oh, it's you.
Maybe it's just because Tanjirou's so far beyond us now,
but no matter how long he instructs us,
I just can't seem to get the hang of it.
I've since realised that we're
complete and utter lost causes.
Wait, did you just say "Yes, you are"?
Bit cruel, don't you think?
Would it kill you to say
"You're working hard, too" for once?
What was that? "Work harder"?
Guess there's no way around it.
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
SPBOUUTLZI
YVOYLEEOUS
UODJKLRDEV
ZRJJQJJXUZ
EFKTZWIHWZ
DGZBJQSLIL
IUCFKLCBCX
IIEHSCZQJR
BOHIJRINMJ
WEYRUMNMYI
Medicine
For Agatsuma Zenitsu:
Take 5 times daily
After each meal
7 days' worth
Gross!
Come on, Monitsu.
What Tanjirou is mastering is a skill called
"Permanent Total Concentration Breathing".
By continually using your Breathing
Technique every second of the day,
your base stamina will skyrocket!
Let's give it a go!
Impossible!
Seriously impossible!
I still can't maintain it all day
unless I really throw myself into it,
but if anyone can, it'd be you two!
You go like this to make your lungs expand!
When that rattles your blood, your bones and muscles
will go, "Boom! Boom! You gotta stop it!"
All that's left to do is train like crazy!
Now, now.
We're talking about a basic—No, an entry-level skill,
so there's no reason you shouldn't be able to do it.
That said, it is true that one must
put in a lot of effort to master the basics.
Although it's not like it's some
big hurdle for you to overcome, right?
Something as simple as this should be
child's play. Right, Inosuke?
It'd be a downright shame if it wasn't,
despite being an entry-level skill.
But if you disagree, I suppose that's that.
No need to brood over it.
The hell you tryna say?!
Of course I can!
Look down on me and I'll rip off your damn tits!
Good luck, Zenitsu!
I'm cheering for you!
Yes, ma'am!
You're in the same class,
so why not join them, Kanao?
More! More! Boom! Boom! Boom!
You damn wimp!
You got this, Zenitsu!
It hurts.
I'm hungry.
I'm sad.
I feel hopeless.
I'm in agony.
I'm lonely.
That's what my life was like.
But then, one day,
I heard a snap.
And I never knew pain again.
Demon Slayer
I never knew pain again.
Living in poverty, even after my parents
sold me, didn't make me feel sad.
Excuse me, may I have a minute of your time?
Could you tell us why that child is all tied up?
Is she a criminal, perhaps?
Can't you tell?
She's flea-ridden, and her face is dirty.
Not to mention, she might try making a run for it.
Hello there. Nice to meet you.
My name is Kochou Kanae.
What's your name?
She ain't got one, y'hear?
Her parents never gave her one.
Happy now? Get away from her already.
Please don't touch my sister.
The hell's your problem?
If you wanna chit-chat with
the kid, you'd better pay up!
Very well, then. We'll purchase her.
Would this suffice?
Hey! Come back here, dammit!
I'd pick it up right now if I were you!
Y'know, considering the crowd and the wind!
Is it really okay to do this?
It's fine!
Please excuse us!
Hands off! It's my property!
Oh, my.
Sister! Sister!
Sister, this child is hopeless!
She won't even touch her food unless ordered to!
She just sits there doing nothing unless told to act!
Even as her stomach growls and growls!
Oh, my.
Just what are we gonna do with her?
Now, now, don't be like that, okay?
I love seeing you smile, Shinobu.
But we can't do anything with a kid who
can't even think for herself! It's too dangerous!
Well, you may have a point, but...
She can't do anything by herself!
When you're alone and unsure of what to do,
you can decide by flipping this coin.
Sounds good, right, Kanao?
Sister!
There's no need to get so up in arms about it, y'know.
Since Kanao is so adorable!
That's not a valid reason!
When given the chance, a person's soul
will open up, so don't worry.
I'm sure yours will one day change
once you've fallen in love, Kanao!
You're doing great! Keep it up!
Right now! Harder! Bam!
That's it! You can do it, Zenitsu!
You've got this! Looking good!
Inosuke! Inosuke!
Our reforged Sun Blades
will be arriving any time now!
For real?
Yeah! The crow just told me!
That's Mr. Haganezuka's scent!
Yahoo!
Hurry! Hurry!
Mr. Haganezuka!
Hey! Hey! Mr. Haganezuka!
Long time no see!
Have you been well...
M-Mr. Haganezuka?
How dare you? How dare you snap my sword in two?
You've got a lot a nerve!
I'm sorry!
B-But in my defence,
I came this close to being killed!
My opponent was insanely strong!
Rubbish! That's got nothing to do with it!
This is your fault! All. Your. Fault!
It broke because you're so pitifully weak!
There's no way my sword would snap otherwise!
But...
I'm gonna kill you!
Is that a new training regimen?
As if.
Well, Haganezuka is a very passionate artisan.
Right.
He loves his swords more than anyone.
He's unlike any other,
even in the sword-forgers' homelands.
I wouldn't doubt it.
My name is Kanamori.
I was the one who forged Lord Inosuke's new swords.
I would be thrilled if they prove useful in battle.
Pristine, are they not?
The dull sheen of that cyan-grey hue is so cool.
It's a fine colour for a sword.
I'm happy for you, Inosuke.
Your old sword was chipped all over.
How do you like the grips?
The thing is, this is the first time I've ever
forged swords for a dual-wielder.
Lord Inosuke?
Better.
I'll kill you, you ungrateful brat!
You bastard! Are you proud of what you've done?
We're sorry! We're really, really sorry!
You bastard!
That's it! You're bloody dead, kiddo!
Unbelievable! Simply unbelievable!
We're sorry! We're sorry!
Taking a stone to those swords? Unbelievable!
We're really sorry!
Looks like he'll manage.
He was doing his best, after all!
Let's make him rice balls again!
Yeah!
My body's changed!
I can't wait to swing my sword with these hands!
I did it!
Good move! You can do it!
Stay focused! Persevere!
I got past her!
Go!
It'd be cruel to splash this
stinky medicated water over her.
Tan
Sense
of
Reason
Sense
of
Reason
He won!
Does that even count?
Doesn't matter. The result is the same!
Hooray! I did it!
I did it!
Shit.
Just you damn wait!
All right, say "ah"!
Good! Looks like your jaw is as good as new.
You can close your mouth now.
That concludes the examination.
Since you've recovered physically,
you may take on your missions without qualms.
So I'm done with my training?
Yes. All that's left for you now is actual combat.
Right!
Oh, before I forget.
There's something I wanted to ask you.
What would that be?
Have you ever heard of the Fire God's Dance?
I have not.
Uh, i-in that case, how about Fire Breathing?
Doesn't ring a bell.
A-Actually, this is something that
happened during my childhood.
Yes, yes.
I see.
So, for some reason, your father used Fire Breathing.
All I can tell you is that while Flame Breathing
does exist, it's different from Fire Breathing.
What? They're not the same thing?
Sorry, I'm not familiar with the details myself.
But I do know that they're very strict
about the exact phrasing.
You must never refer to
Flame Breathing as Fire Breathing.
The Flame Hashira, Rengoku,
might know the specifics.
But unfortunately, he's out on a mission.
Understood!
Thank you for all that you've taught me.
I'll be sure to ask Mr. Rengoku if I see him again.
Right.
Now then, please excuse me!
Kamado?
Yes?
I'm expecting great things from you.
Got it!
She's slept through the entire day again.
I know they said you could be
sleeping to recover your stamina,
but it worries me if you don't
open your eyes once in a while.
Hey, your brother will probably be leaving
this place soon to go on his next mission.
My wounds have healed,
and I've gotten even stronger!
I'm maintaining my Breathing even now!
I think Zenitsu and Inosuke will tag along, too.
Having those two by my side gives me confidence.
I see.
You think so, too, Nezuko?
They're good guys.
If I want to turn you back into a human,
I must take down the strongest demons I can find
and send Miss Tamayo their blood samples.
Am I capable of doing that?
I know you can do it, Tanjirou.
Thanks, Nezuko. You just encouraged me, didn't you?
I'll do my best, okay?
I don't want to be imprisoned by sadness
kanashimi ni torewaretaku wa nai
I don't want to come back
utsumuita basho ni
To the place I cast my head down crying
namida wo otoshite yukitakunai
Free from the shackles of fate
unmei wo furihodoite
You're supposed to start running
hashiridaseru hazu nanda
That dream is meant to come true
negai wa kanau hazu nanda
Break free from the troubles of yesterday
tatakitsubuse kinou no katou
Pray for the future from the edge of darkness
Ride the wind that's leading the way
mukai kaze wo nototte
Face the unseen beyond the storm
arashi no saki wa mienaku tatte
There's only one path—
mou michi wa erabenai kachinokore
To make it out alive!
The choice between love and light
mayoi wa itsumo aijou to hikari wo hakari ni kakeru
Will always cast doubt upon your mind
Now rise up once more
saa tachiagarunda mou ichido
Now, where might you strike down
ima kimi wa sono yaiba wo
With that blade of yours?
doko he furiorosu
Demon Slayer
PREVIEW
Maintaining my Breathing is way too demanding!
Totally ain't happening, damn it.
You both look wiped out.
Oh, I know!
Here's a Taisho secret for you!
The medicated water we use for
reflex training, when added to your bath,
is actually great for healing exhaustion and wounds.
PREVIEW
Well, I'm off to train,
but maybe you two should catch a break.
I ain't even close to done yet!
Don't underestimate me!
We're doing even more training?
Okay, fine! Only attendance is mandatory, right?
Next, Episode 26, "New Mission".
Okay, I'm heading out now, Nezuko!
To Be Continued