When the tensed-up strings of your heart are strummed
haritsumeta kodou no ito wo hajikarete
Does the darkness that clings to your body
karadajuu ni haritsuku kurayami wa
Encroach upon your mind and perplex you?
anata wo madowase okashite yuku no
Oblivious to your fate in just a few hours
suujikan ato no unmei mo shiranai de
Even though the feelings you engraved into your heart
kokoro ni kizanda kono omoi wa kowasenai hazu nanoni
Weren’t meant to be abandoned
Your voice brings me back
anata no koe ga watashi wo hikimodosu
As the cherry petals fall near my crumbling feet
kuzureru ashimoto ni sakura ga maichiru
Cut through the labyrinth before it consumes you
nomikomaresou na meikyuu wo kirisaite
And please feel my unending power
tomaranai watashi no netsu wo kanjiteite