This hollow voice
nagareru
Seeks flowing light and overlapping fingers
hikari wo tada kasaneru yubi wo
Its echoes vainly ring
motometa koe wa
Within a garden that was sealed away
tozasareta niwa no naka munashiku hibiku
The dawn in full glory
mitasareta akatsuki
Light and darkness
hikari to yami
A time of slumber
madoromi no toki
A promise that won’t be allowed
yurusarenai yakusoku
A memory strung up as decoration
kazareta kioku
Questioning the end
owari wo toikakeru
Layers of precious sin
kasaneta itoshii tsumi
A gentle lie
yasashii uso
A sleepy sadness
nemureru kanashimi
I whispered a prayer as my wings were taken from me
inori tsubuyaku tsubasa wo ubawareta
May I find even the slightest bit of light in this dream
yume ni wazuka demo hikari wo