Now, there's a sight that gives me spring vibes.
Shinichi Sakurai: 19-year-old college sophomore
Sakurai!
Huh?
Uzaki, right?
Hana Uzaki!
Looks like I'll be
your junior again this year!
Hana Uzaki: 18-year-old college freshman
Here's to a great year!
Huh? You won't be swimming in college?
Nope. They don't even have
a swim club here to begin with.
What a shame, since you kept it up in high school.
Ah, what's it matter?
There's plenty other things to do in college.
Sakurai...
Y-Yep, there sure is.
Or so I thought.
Spring
Oh, Sakurai!
What the...
Summer
What in the...
Fall
What in the what?
Winter
What in the what?!
Spring once again
I kinda figured it'd turn out the same this year.
Shinichi Sakurai: 20-year-old college junior
Sakurai!
Whoops!
Overshot you!
Uzaki, right?
All alone again today, aren't we?
Hana Uzaki: 19-year-old college sophomore
Well then, guess I've
gotta hang out with you!
Hana Uzaki: 19-year-old college sophomore
Your college loner
lifestyle ends today!
honto wa sasotte hoshii nante
You think I want to be asked to hang out with you?
omottemo nankanai sonnakoto manzara zenzen naisu
No, no! I've never even thought about it once!
uzagarami soremo hitotsuno
I'm only subtly ushering you
nadamesukashi negotiation
To begin considering the possibilities!
kyou no yotei kiiteageteru noni nan nan
I thought I'd be nice and hear what you had planned for today
nansuka sore (nansuka sore)
But why would I want to come along? (Seriously, what're you imagining?)
souiu taido de korarecha watashimo nanka nanka moyarusu
Even I think your being so serious and gloomy is super creepy!
souda
Totally!
uzaitte omowaretatte iikotonante honrainai
Just brushing me off as annoying won't help you a lot
demo itsuka uzakawaiitte omowarechaeba mondainai
But praising my blossoming body would be ideal!
toriaezu damemoto datte koe kakechatte soshitara
I thought I'd just rush up some day and chatter away (why not?)
sunnari nottekuru
And you just went along
are kekkou choroisune
With my silly whims
bocchi wa itsudatte yappari samishiitte
Being so distant sure seems lonely
kocchini oidette mouchotto mouchotto!
So just stick close to me and come nearer, step by step!
ittari kitari oshitari hiitari
Even if you turn aside, step away or block my attempts
nando nando nando kurikaesundarou
I'll repeat them again, again and again without hesitation
omoi no yukue wa fumei da
Eagerly anticipating the results!
nadamesukashite soukai kibun tsuukai happy happy
Teasing you soothes, refreshes and makes me just way too happy
atekosuri janaissu zenbu zenbu honkissu
I'm not just saying this either, I'm totally serious!
shinpuru ni tanoshindeimasu enjoy and joy
I want to show you how to love life's simple joys!
kyouzonkyouei no rireishon
Let's cherish them together every day
desune desune
Sounds great? Right, right?
dakedo kakehiki ja seesaw game
We're just going up and down with this seesaw game
kimayoi kimagure kimamani matteru
Though irritating and whimsical, I'll always wait for you
aa sasotte hoshii nante
Ah, being asked out by you
omottemo nankanai sonnakoto attara it's so nice
Was something I hadn't thought about, but it'd be so nice!
karakatte tawamureatte kongaragatte have a nice day janaisu
Teasing you, playing and horsing around would make every day nice!
Episode 1
Uzaki Wants to Hang Out!
What you wanna do for lunch?
Mhm... Let's check out the dining hall, I guess.
Schedule Updates
Faculty
Status
Course Name
Classroom
School of Law
School of
Information Sciences
School of Philosophy
School of Law
School of Education
Moved
Cancelled
Electoral Systems I - The Rational Politician
Fundamentals of Quantitative Finance
History of Western Philosophy (Practical)
Art History (Practical II)
Electoral Systems I - The Rational Politician
Fundamentals of Quantitative Finance
History of Western Philosophy (Practical)
Art History (Practical II)
Analytic Tools of Institutional Theory (3)
Game Theory and Collective Action Theory
8th Annual Seminar: Theory and Design of College Education
Oh, mind if we tag along?
Cancelled, huh? Looks like
I have a free afternoon today.
Sakurai!
I don't have to work today, either.
What to do, what to do...
Eek!
What's with that glare?
S-Scary...
Sakurai!
Guess I'll just go out and about for once.
Not like I often get to enjoy peace
and quiet with her around, after all.
Sakurai, Sakurai, Sakurai, Sakurai!
How many times do I have to tell you to stop yelling?
How many times do I have to tell you to stop yel
ling?
I kept calling you, but you just wouldn't respond!
So, where ya headed today, Sakurai?
What the hell do you think you're doing, dumbass?
Oh, going out for lunch today?
Aw, too bad.
My friends and I already ate.
But if you insist, I'd be fine with watching you eat.
I've got no classes this afternoon.
I'm just going out for a stroll.
Later.
What are you following me for, Uzaki?
Wow, you look pissed.
Well, as it turns out,
I'm suddenly free this afternoon, too.
Given half the chance,
I know you'll do the old loner thing.
And two's gotta be way more fun than one!
Mind your own business.
Besides, haven't I told you a million times
that I much prefer some quiet time alone?
Here we go again. Being a loner is no fun!
Stop calling me that.
Good point, you're no loner! I'm with you!
Quit tagging along, you damn pest!
Feeling shy?
Like hell!
So, where are we going?
Not telling.
Karaoke? Bowling?
Aw, tell me!
Hell, no.
Ugh!
What are you acting so cold for?
Not in the mood today.
Not in the mood?
What's the deal? You had no problem
hanging out with me before!
Huh?
You just treat me however you fancy!
Am I just a convenient woman to
have around when you're in the mood?!
Stop spouting junk that's so easy to misunderstand!
Enemy of womankind.
Utter trash.
Scum.
Fine! Suit yourself!
Tag along if you must!
Hooray!
Hey, let's go get food after we're done.
I'll gladly sit with you for dinner!
I ain't paying.
Aw, cheapskate.
You tryna sponge off of me or what?
Wait, were you gonna watch
a movie by yourself today?
Huh? Yeah.
Going to the movies solo!
What's so funny about that?
Doesn't get much lonelier than that!
Other than, like, solo BBQ or solo sushi-go-round!
Shut up for once, would you?
You'll make an enemy out of everyone.
At least quiet down a little.
Listen up, we're in the age of the individual.
We all want to find time in our busy lives
to watch a movie the way we like it.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Shouldn't everyone be free to enjoy
their free time however they want?
Don't laugh off other's hobbies because yours differ.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
There's plenty of people that like watching movies,
be it alone or with friends.
That's just how it is.
I see.
Spoken like a true loner!
Can I wallop her just once?
Anyone can go watch a movie alone
whenever they feel like it.
Throw other people into the mix
and scheduling becomes a pain.
I see.
But you can't talk about spoilers loudly
with your friends after if you go alone!
That's one of the absolute worst things you can do!
It's okay.
I get it.
You're determined to soldier on alone
despite your loneliness.
Don't give me that affectionate look!
Honestly.
I knew I shouldn't have brought you.
I was planning to follow you
all sneaky-like, anyway.
What's your deal?
Is that your idea of fun?
Huh?
Well, it'd be funny if I spotted you
going into some weird store or something!
I know I'd laugh myself silly
if I saw you buying dirty DVDs!
Ow! Ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Having your nose
pulled up really hurts
Sakurai, I... Sakurai! Sakurai!
I give! I give! I give!
You, as a college student, are an adult!
Stop prying into other people's hobbies,
or digging into their private lives!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
Sheesh.
Sold out
##############################
Nyaventures: The Kuso Cat War / English
##########################
Golden Catnap / Japanese
##############################
One Million Yen Kuso Cat / Japanese
#################################
Underdog, the Tiger and the Fish / Japanese
I haven't even had time to pick a movie
with you all up in my business.
You came without a movie in mind?
It was a last-minute thing.
Besides, picking something on a whim
is one of the thrills of going solo.
Oh, is it, now?
Uzaki.
Yes?
You wanna watch something? It's on me.
Huh? Really? What about going solo?
Not like I have to go solo.
And with you here, I can watch
something different from usual.
I could probably cover for two
with my membership card.
Seriously?!
Well, if you insist, I'll let you treat me!
Thanks!
Let's see...
This one!
What a bargain! Heroes as far as the eye can see!
Ooh, that's a great one.
I've seen it before, but what's another watch?
Huh!
For two college students, please. I'll be using points.
Certainly. One moment.
She has her moments, but maybe I went a bit too far.
Seems she's happy to get treated,
so I guess we're even now.
By the way, Sakurai...
You've saved up enough points by yourself
to cover someone else's ticket?
That's honestly kinda sad.
She says stuff like that after I pay for her?
You're, like, a professional loner!
Huh? Uh, wait... Sakurai?
It just a joke! Sorry! I'm so sorry!
Yow! Stop! Stop!
Will that couple ever shut up?!
That was great!
Yeah. A good film's always worth a rewatch.
All those points you banked
by going to the movies alone—gone!
That's your standard for "great"?!
Damn it. So much for being nice.
Hey, can we stop by the electronics store?
Computer and
Cellphone Accessories
I need new earbuds.
Computer and
Cellphone Accessories
Yeah, sure.
See, it's that kind of thing.
Huh?
What is it about these kinds of shops that makes me
think "Since I'm here, I should buy something"?
Hey, nice.
Sakurai!
Yeah?
Over here! This way!
What happened to those earbuds?
C'mon, the next seat's open!
Mind listening?
Well, whatever. Might be nice after a movie.
Right?
That hits the spot!
This is nice. Real nice.
Right?
Though I usually have more trouble with
my shoulders than my back.
LO
Shoulders?
H I
Wha—where'd that come from?
Oh, sorry...
She's just sitting in a massage chair
I can't help but make noise during a massage...
My, uh, my shoulders have always been tight—
Well, um... I-If you keep doing that...
She's just sitting in a massage chair
I'd buy this on the spot if I could!
It... It just... It feels...
sooo good...
No, really. We told you she's just sitting a massage chair
She's just sitting a massage chair, okay?
Let's get going, okay?!
We haven't even been here for five minutes!
Shut up!
S-Save that for home!
Save what?
Good grief, this moron.
Moaning like crazy in public.
Hey, Sakurai!
What now?
Ten minutes of standing on this,
and it's like getting a full workout!
Well?
You try!
Oh, my God!
You're such an idiot!
Totally oblivious
Whoa! Check it out!
What is it this time?
Look! It's VR! VR!
VR Gear Demo
Huh! So this is virtual reality...
Would you like to try it out?
Yes! I wanna give it a try!
My screen turns when I turn!
VR is amazing!
This is really cool, Sakurai!
Okay, okay. You don't need to yell.
My weapon! No! Not this one!
Ammo! I'm outta ammo!
Hey, is there anyone behind you?
Huh? Behind me?!
Here they come! Look at 'em all!
Your reactions are the best.
They should put you in a commer—
I died!
Wow, VR is so cool!
Er, are you all right?
I'm fine.
What's wrong, Sakurai?
Um, would your boyfriend like to have a turn?
I'm not her boyfriend.
But... okay.
Something not so dangerous.
These ocean graphics are something else!
Hey, you look like a normal person with those goggles.
They hide your mean look!
Shut it, dimwit.
Whoa!
That's huge! A giant shark!
Wait, isn't it swimming this way?
Huh? Is it?!
I-It's biting me! It's totally biting me! Yow!
You're way too scared!
You're one to talk!
Let me go! Hey!
I'm gonna get this disgraceful display
on video and tease you about it later!
Uh, miss?
Don't get too close to the player...
Just so huge!
Hmm? What's this?
A jellyfish? Octopus? Sunfish?!
It's so big. And soft!
And kind of frightening!
I never thought much of VR,
but damn! It's out of this world!
It's so powerful—and even reproduces touch!
Are you all right, miss?
Yeah, it's okay. I'm fine.
You said VR made you want to
do something physical,
and here you are,
excitedly racking up a pile of strikes!
Focus!
Will you shut up?
C'mon, here comes the next one!
You can do it! Knock it out of the park! Home run!
That's enough out of—
That so didn't fly straight!
Dammit.
You said you did this before. You totally didn't!
You really tick me off, dammit.
I played for one year in junior high.
Ooh! I wanna try, too!
Here's my card. There's still some on there.
Thanks!
Don't stand too close or the ball will hit you.
Got it!
If I hit a home run, dinner's on you!
Eyes forward! You wanna get hurt?
Okay...
Plant the feet...
Swivel the hips...
Like the real deal.
Huh, wait. Did—
Did you stretch?
Oh.
It... It hurts...
Are you nuts, whipping out a full swing like that?!
On your back, right now!
I could feel it crack...
Yeah, I'll say!
I copied you
and look where it got me...
A novice can't just start putting
their hips into a swing!
Of course you're gonna hurt yourself, moron!
This is all your fault, Sakurai...
How so?!
Just go home and get some sleep.
And see a doctor tomorrow.
A doctor, you say?
No, I want to go out for dinner!
Do you ever give up?!
TANEDA RAMEN
Let's eat!
Since you can walk fine on your own,
it's probably nothing serious.
If it still hurts tomorrow, see a doctor.
And you really should head home now and go sleep.
I'll be fine.
Yummy yum yum.
You're severely out of shape, aren't you?
That injury proves you haven't been active much.
What did you expect? I'm just starting out!
Beginners need to warm up, at least.
Back injuries are a big deal.
Fine.
You realise that this never would've happened
if you hadn't forced your way along, ri—
Huh?
My chicken...
Hey.
Why are you eating it?
Huh?
Did you eat them all?!
Eh?
W-We weren't sharing?
We weren't, you idiot!
And exactly how are we sharing
if you eat everything?!
I don't want it anymore!
Temper, temper! Your poor girlfriend!
She's not my girlfriend...
Another order of chicken, please.
Coming right up!
Your chicken's so good, my chopsticks just kept going!
Good one, missy!
Talk about a sunny personality.
Here you go.
On the house. Eat up!
Wow! For real?
Oh, no, we couldn't!
Go on, it's fine!
Delish!
Honestly.
It'd be rude not to accept it, Sakurai!
Well, I guess you're right.
Okay, don't mind if I—
Why do you eat everything?!
Sorry! I didn't mean to!
Here's your chicken.
Again?!
Stingy!
Sakurai!
Good morning!
Hey.
I had fun yesterday!
What?
All you did was hurt your back.
Huh?
C'mon, it was fun not being a loner for a day, right?
I made it clear from the very beginning
that I intended to spend the day alone.
Oh, look at you, pretending you weren't happy.
Watch it.
I've never been to a batting cage with
my girlfriends before, either. That was new!
Teach me how to swing, okay?
Next time I wanna really send it flying!
Hey, how 'bout we go again today?
I have work.
Aw.
Next time, then!
"Next time", huh?
This idiot really doesn't let a little pain
get in the way of having fun.
I don't know when she got like this...
Like this? Or like this?
Well, at least I won't be bored.
I can put up with her a little, I guess.
Yeah, next time.
Uh, Sakurai?
Hmm?
After that thing we did yesterday?
My back still hurts!
It's all your fault, y'know!
Phrasing!
It even hurts to walk! Carry me!
C'mon, it's your fault!
Shut up!
Happy, mischevious chatter echoes through the air
itazurana kotoba ga afureru itsumo no gogo
taikutsuna mainichi ni kaze ga fuita
Imbuing these mundane afternoons with its distinctive flavour
arifureta sekai de kimi to sugoshita jikan wa
When I'm with you in this world filled with adventures
atarimae janai kigashita
Every second feels like a new, special find
nando datte waraiatte
No matter how often we laugh together, I'll never grow tired of it
tanoshii hibi wo kasane
I will treasure each and every day we spend together
mune no oku ni shimaikonda omoi wo sagasuyo
Slowly hinting at those feelings concealed deep in my chest
kokoro no tobira wo tataiteru
These knockings against the door of my heart
hitotsu futatsu narihibiku nokku
First once, then twice, resound deep inside
darenimo kikoenai mama kimochi wa nemuru
My still-dormant feelings await to be roused by their prince
akarui hizashi no sono ura de
Hidden behind my bright, sunny disposition
honto no koto kakurenbo shiteru
My true hopes are waiting to be discovered by you
itsuka kitto mitsuketene nantene
So make sure to some day!
Just kidding!
Epi
sode
Mr. Manager
Epi
Episode 2
Mr. Manager
Wants to Sneak a Peek!
Next time we'll meet the café owner!