A sound “soul”
O
dwells within a sound mind
and a sound body
and a sound body.
Death Weapon Meister Academy
Death Weapon Meister Academy...
Commonly known as the DWMA.
DWMA
It’s an institution to train weapons
and meisters, established by Death.
It was created in order to prevent Kishins,
the demon gods who plunged
the entire world into the depths of terror,
drove people into a maelstrom of madness,
and nearly destroyed everything,
from ever being born again.
well, the gist of it is that it’s
an organization of justice, to keep the peace.
DWMA
Why is it a school, anyway?
Oh well.
Now then, let’s all get ourselves
duly keyed up, and get going!
tsunaida tamashii no hi ga mune wo sasu nara
If the light of our linked souls points towards your heart
kotoba yori motto tsuyoi hibiki ga ima kikoeru ka
Can you hear the echoes that resonate stronger than words?
roku ni me mo awasazu
We barely ever look each other in the eye
unmei ni made karande’ku
Yet our very fates have started to become intertwined
yukisaki moro kabutte’ru
Our paths cross
kuenai yoru wo hashire
So let’s brave the deadly night together
fukaoi shi sugita mabushisa ga
Though the glares that come with showing determination
warui yume ni tsuzuite mo
May seep into your nightmares
tsunaida tamashii no hi ga mune wo sasu nara
If the light of our linked souls points towards your heart
kotoba yori motto tsuyoi hibiki ga ima kikoeru ka
Can you hear the echoes that resonate stronger than words?
deatta wake wa dou datte ii
The reason why we met doesn’t matter
hikitsukerarete
We’re drawn together
fureta shunkan no kizu no bun dake
The more we get hurt during the moments we connect
tashika ni nareru
The clearer everything becomes
More power...
More...
power...!
Soul Eater, that’s him.
Yeah, Maka. No question about it.
His soul has become a Kishin egg.
He’s not human.
Souls that have strayed from the human path
run the risk of transforming into a Kishin.
In the name of Lord Death, purge him and recover his soul.
What’s up, Maka?
I’m not human either. I am a weapon.
Although, I suppose I do usually take on a human form.
My form isn’t the issue here.
The issue lies with souls!
I know.
Mass murderer Jack the Ripper,
your soul is mine!
The weapon and meister are united as one!
Let’s go, Soul!
Yeah!
This marks our ninety-ninth soul!
I thank thee for the meal.
Recovery complete.
At long last, we’ve put away our ninety-ninth soul
that had turned into a Kishin egg, huh?
Just one more to go.
Once I eat the soul of a witch,
I will become Lord Death’s weapon, a Death Scythe.
That will also boost my manliness even further.
I’m going to report our current status to Lord Death.
The number to the Death Room is...
42-42-564.
Hello, Lord Death?
This is Meister Maka.
Oh?
Maka, how are you?
How are things going?
We just recovered our ninety-ninth soul.
We only have one left: The soul of a witch.
Maka, you really do take after your mother.
You’re a fine scythemeister.
Hey, Soul Eater!
If you try anything with Maka,
I, as a Death Scythe—no,
as her father, will kill you, you dimwit.
Shut up, will ya?
There’s no way someone as cool as me
is suited to be with a pipsqueek like her.
The hell did you just say?!
Are you saying my Maka doesn’t have any appeal?!
You can atleast try doing something
with her! You’re a man, right?!
What are you talking about?
Maka, I love you.
No way!
Papa, I don’t even think of you as my father.
Well, family matters aside,
following the recovery of ninety-nine souls
that have strayed from the human path,
which is to say, souls that have
turned into Kishin eggs,
as well as one soul of a witch,
Witch
you earn the right to become a Death Scythe.
The issue, then, becomes that soul.
I’ve seen so many meisters lose their lives
battling witches that it really bothers me.
Watch yourself, Maka.
Maka... your papa...
Make yourself an exceptional Scythe,
one that rivals the Death Scythe
your mother made, okay?
your papa only wants...
Right.
Also, be careful not to make any mistakes.
That last one is the soul of a witch, after all.
If you mess up, you forfeit all the other Kishin eggs
you’ve recovered up to this point.
We know.
Expect the best from us, Lord Death.
Okay then, with that in mind...
Maka...!
Uh, you’re being a little noisy there.
Maka!
Cut it out, or I’ll bring out the Reaper Chop!
Tell me that beforehand...
Resonance of the Soul
Will Soul Eater
become a Death Scythe?
~
Resonance of the Soul:
“Will Soul Eater Become a Death Scythe?”
Whatever I look at becomes my captive.
I am a cute, pretty lady!
Do my back next.
Still, though,
I like pumpkins!
Pump-pump-pumpkin, pumpkin!
That is my magic...
Blair the Witch is in that house, right?
A pumpkin, huh? Pretty cool.
This is gonna taste good.
It wouldn’t be very manly to sneak our way in.
I’m gonna go devour her head-on!
No way! She isn’t anything like
the others we’ve faced up to n—
Here goes!
Wai—Hold on!
S-She’s naked?
Oh, my. What’s the matter, little guy?
C-Cool guys are used to seeing women naked.
Your nose is gushing blood
pretty well there, considering.
Never mind that, your soul is—
You idiot!
Sorry to disturb your bath, but your soul is mine.
Are you okay, little guy?
Hurry up and turn into a scythe.
I know, I know...
Witch, I’m going to devour your soul!
Witch?
Amazing! He transformed into a scythe!
I’m taking your soul, and Soul
is going to become a Death Scythe.
The ultimate weapon, surpassing my Papa!
I like you.
Let me have that scythe.
Pump-pump-pumpkin, pumpkin.
Halloween Cannon!
Oh, Mr. Death Scythe, you’re such a horndog!
Come to think of it, you have a daughter, right?
What is she like?
Hold on, you can’t ask that.
Huh? Why not?
Mr. Death Scythe, as you can see,
can’t keep his hands off of women.
He isn’t getting along with his wife as a result.
They’ve ended up in the middle of divorce proceedings.
His daughter, Maka, even said "l hate you, Papa!"
Sounds kind of complicated.
Maka!
It’s not like that, Maka!
Papa... Papa loves you and Mama
more than anything, Maka!
It’s the truth! And nothing but!
Thank you very much.
Mr. Death Scythe...
Come again, okay?
Uh-huh.
Bye!
The
Next
Day
The Next Day
Damn. She’s enticing my cool self
with her witchly allure.
That’s a witch for you.
But if you give in to her seductiveness,
you’ll never become a Death Scythe.
Shut up, pipsqueek.
It’s her!
What do we do?
Huh?
Ah! The little scythe boy!
The
Next,
Next
Day
The Next, Next Day
For today,
I wrote down a thorough strategy on this note.
The hell’s that for?
There’s none of that “today’s strategy” business here.
What good is one little note going to do?
Then tell me, how do you think
we’re going to beat Blair?!
Who knows? Tried with heart yet?
What’s with you?!
The two of us have to put our heads together!
Otherwise, you’ll never become
a Death Scythe! Don’t you get it?!
All right. Cut it out.
Soul?! Geez, why are all men like this?!
Pump-pump-pumpkin... Pumpkin...
Halloween Cannon!
The
Next,
Next
Day
Round Three
You’ll never beat me.
What are you doing, you numbskull?!
Oh, shut up.
This is all because your nose
keeps bleeding, right, Soul?
Huh?
Men really are lowlifes!
Are you sure you didn’t go rushing in back there
because you knew Blair was in the tub?
There’s no way I could have known that!
Why the hell do women always say
such unreasonable things so confidently?!
Women’s intuition.
Geez, I don’t even know what that means!
Now, now, little scythe boy.
If you’re going to fight with her anyway,
why not just come over here and become mine?
I’ll overlook anything you do.
H-Hang on!
Soul’s my partner!
Don’t go arranging things
without consenting his meister first!
That so?
In that case...
I’ll kill you and make him mine.
She’s gone?
Pump-pumpkin pumpkin.
Smashing Pumpkin!
What do we do, Soul?
We’re no match for her.
Soul?
Hey, Soul?
What’s the matter?
Why not just come over here and become mine?
Man, Caba-cabra sure is fun!
Good grief, your daughter is in trouble.
What have you been up to?
Huh?
Did something happen to Maka?!
She’s in a tight spot in her fight with the witch.
She’s a goner.
What?!
Sit tight, Maka!
Hold it!
We could go and easily take out an opponent
like that with one swing of the scythe—
no, even just one smack of my Reaper Chop!
However...
that’s not the issue, right?
As her father, you understand that, right?
Maka...
Still, that witch is a little odd, huh?
Hey, Soul, why aren’t you answering me?
Maka...
Soul...?
That’s enough.
Hey, what do you think you’re doing?!
I’m giving up on dealing with this hassle.
I’m going to become Miss Blair’s scythe!
Wow! Really?
Yeah, that’s right!
Get your hands off of Maka, you dimwit!
Is this really the time to be saying that?
Blair!
You’re deluding Soul’s mind
with your magic, aren’t you?!
You’re such an idiot.
Any man would pass on a pipsqueek
like you for a curvy woman with a nice body.
It’s so obvious.
Oh! Indeed, she is an incredibly fine woman!
You keep quiet for a little while.
What is this?
Men are such lowlifes.
All you ever do is womanize.
And yet...
After I finally decided to trust one of you...
Unbelievable.
You can all just die!
Hey, Soul.
You know how you said that
women always say unreasonable things?
Well, is male infidelity any more reasonable, you dumbass?!
How would I know?
Cool men don’t go cheating around, after all.
Maka!
Yes!
We did it, Maka.
Yeah.
Thank you, Soul.
The issue isn’t with one’s form.
The issue lies with their soul, right?
Once you eat that...
Yeah! I can become a Death Scythe.
My power!
I can feel my power...
not rising at all...
Not rising at all...
Huh?
Oh, no...
Y-You wouldn’t happen to be...
I never said I was a witch, meow.
I’m just a cat with strong magical powers.
“The issue isn’t with one’s form”, right?
Uh-oh. Sure enough...
I don’t care if she’s a cat! I’ve decided!
I’m going to be your catn—
Does that mean I
devoured ninety-nine Kishin eggs, and one cat’s soul?
Now that you mention it...
The last one is a witch’s soul.
If you mess up, you forfeit all the other
Kishin eggs you’ve recovered up to this point.
You forfeit them all.
Forfeit.
Which means...
Failure
We goofed up?!
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
I’m a failure as a meister!
We have to start over from the beginning.
And here I thought I was going to
become the ultimate cool guy!
How are you still alive after we
took your soul, anyway?
Don’t you know that cats have many lives?
Never mind that. Soul, come and be mine.
Hey, Blair! Stop following us!
Come on, Soul...
This is not cool at all.
This boy’s name is Black☆Star.
An assassin who conceals himself
in darkness, and moves with the darkness.
Tsubaki, are these guys our target this time around?
Yeah. AI Capone and his men.
There must be about a hundred of them.
Two against a hundred, huh? Perfect.
Black☆Star...
Let’s go recover all of the souls that
have strayed from the human path,
and have turned into Kishin eggs.
Wielder of the magical dark arms, Tsubaki.
However, this boy has a big problem.
Let’s go.
Prologue 02: Black☆Star.
Coming soon.
kuzuboshi kirameku
The stardust twinkles
yume no hoshi sa
The star of my dreams
I wanna be
ikou ze
Let’s go
Let’s go!
I...
(I...)
Wanna...
(Wanna...)
I wanna be!
(1-2-3-4!)
sekai wa kuroku somatte’ru
The world is stained in black
haku iki wa shiroi mama na no ni
But our breath remains a clear white
ima wo bukkowashi ni ikoutte
Ever since that day we vowed
yakusoku shita ano hi kara
To go smash up the present
kitto mada ma ni au hazu dakara
I’m sure we can still make it in time
I wanna be
massao na
Counted together
zetsubou to issho ni
With pallid hopelessness
himei wo age
Scream out!
tsukisasare
Sprint through!
subete ga kawaru mae ni
Before everything transitions
I...
(I...)
Wanna...
(Wanna...)
I wanna be!
And so, Soul Eater has begun!
What did you all think?
It’s not cool.
Hey, Soul, how long are you planning
on being depressed?
Next time, the underworld mafia and a lone wolf samurai
are targeted by a conceited assassin.
In other words, the story is
going to be like rice piled on pasta,
sandwiched between two pieces of bread, right?
Why is it all carbs?
Ah, that might be pretty yummy.
Soul Eater, episode 2:
I am the star!
The Big Man
is Showing Up Here?
~
“l Am the Star!
The Big Man is Showing Up Here?”
Your soul is mine!