It's so soft and fluffy!
I'm glad you like it.
Thanks, Shiorin!
This is the best present ever!
Thank you, too, for the
wonderful present you gave me.
There are so many pretty animals and plants.
I hope I can go see them with you someday.
We will!
Your condition's been improving steadily
ever since we came to this farm.
We'll make it!
I'll carry you on my back and fly away if I have to!
Are you okay?
We spent the entire day shopping today...
Rest a little for now.
I'm sorry, Hatsune. All I ever do is make you worry...
I'm sorry...
The Light that Pierces the Darkness
Like Two Sisters in a Pod
All right! It's time for the harvest!
Yeah!
Looks like somebody's energetic this morning.
We're counting on you today.
Right!
This soil is well-drained.
I can tell they take good care of it every day.
Huh... So this is the plant spice comes from?
Karyl, here. Smell this.
It smells great!
It makes my stomach roar.
Doesn't it?
Morning!
Did you take a good, long rest from your journey?
Hiya!
Yes, we're supercharged now!
Didn't fly here this time, did you?
This harvest is too important.
Using my superpowers tires me out,
so I'm holding off for today!
Ah, sorry! Forget everything I just said!
H-Hold on!
So you're saying that isn't magic,
but some superpower?
I've never met anyone with superpowers before.
A miracle...
It's too late now.
You all seem like nice people,
so let's keep it between us, okay?
Oh, so it's our own little secret! How crazy is that?
Take it more seriously!
At least be somewhat rattled, will you?
W-We've got trouble!
Miss Rima?
Kokkoro?
What in the world happened?
O-On our way over here, we were ambushed
by something that looked just like us.
Then a swordswoman showed up, dressed all in black...
Shiorin! Where's Shiorin?
I'm sorry. We lost sight of her during the attack.
Rima did everything she could, though!
She fought and fought until she could
no longer fight, and then carried us over here.
Miss Rima, I'll treat your wounds.
Thanks, Kokkoro... but what are you doing here?
We also came to help with the harvest.
That means the rumours are true!
More and more people that travel here tell the same story
about being attacked by lookalikes in the forest.
Come to think of it, I heard
the innkeeper went missing, too...
Excuse me a moment!
Shiorin...
Perhaps I went a little overboard.
So, those were Shadows.
What in the world is she trying to accomplish?
Well, no matter.
There's no one else who satisfies
my hunger like she does.
Now, I believe it's time for act two.
Make more... Make more...
How fun.
What melody will you play for me next?
Now, come! We shall put on a grand show!
Let me go! I have to go save Shiorin!
Calm down. You can't do it alone.
Wait!
I'll go with you!
Shiori was beyond excited
to finally come see you again!
Miss Rima...
I'll go, too.
Yuuki?
Team B-B doesn't abandon those who need help!
Th-That's right. We're Team B-B!
If someone's in trouble,
we help them, no questions asked!
That's the kind of people we want to be!
My lord, I will go, too.
Everyone...
Thank you.
Karyl, we should also—
Karyl?
Ya think Peco lady's harvesting now?
I guess so.
She said she'll feed us a meal with
the legendary spice when she gets back.
I'm already psyched, bro!
I know!
Look at that. It's our Landosol Castle.
Wow, sure is pretty.
A toast to another day in our beautiful, peaceful Landosol.
Cheers!
I don't like this. Something's odd.
'Tis a scary place.
I don't like this.
Miss Rima, how are your injuries?
All better thanks to your healing magic!
The forest feels really strange.
It's as if it's holding its breath,
afraid of something...
I'll take a look from above.
Rimama?! Hatsune can fly?!
It's magic.
Not a superpower.
Shiorin, where are you?
What was that?!
Miss Hatsune!
Hatsune!
Was that...?
Shiorin!
Thank goodness you're all right!
Shiorin?
Enchanted Arrow.
Shiorin, why...
Make more. Make more.
Make more of me.
Hatsune!
That arrow...
You mean that attack earlier was...
Shiorin...
Let's go.
He's right! Let's go find out what's going on!
I'll find her again and confirm for myself!
So they're doing it, huh?
The one causing all this trouble's got to be her.
My mission is to observe Pecorine.
Nobody told me the Shadows were active!
If we don't stop them, the entire village could be...
Karyl!
No need to yell. I'm right here.
I'm so relieved!
Relieved?
You looked down earlier,
so I was wondering if you were okay.
Wh-What's that? I'm always like this.
I'm not some happy camper like you!
Wh-What?
Yeah! This is how you ought to be!
D-Don't be stupid.
Well, come on! Let's go with Yuuki
and the others and look for Shiori!
Those voices...
Wai—Pecorine!
Make more... Make more...
Help me!
Coming right up!
You have nothing to fear.
I'll take care of these nasty monsters.
Thank you, lady!
Make more. Make more.
Make more of me.
Pecorine...
What's that?
Is the village under attack?
W-We have to hurry back!
Wait just a minute.
A fun new act is about to begin.
Don't put a dampener on it.
Careful, everyone! That's the
swordswoman who attacked us!
Do you know what's going on here?
If you want to know,
let our swords do the speaking.
Rima!
My lord!
Yuuki!
Wake up! Wake up!
Open your eyes, Yuuki!
Good. You seem fine.
What about the others?!
This is basically a dream.
I just called your consciousness forth temporarily.
You mean...
Kokkoro and the others are still in combat.
No... they can't even put up a fight against her.
They'll be slaughtered.
Send me back! Right now!
I wasn't expecting Christina to pop up so soon.
You've met her before?
Many times.
I doubt she even remembers that, though.
Understand this: I can't get involved
with the real world yet.
The fate of Kokkoro and co lies on your shoulders.
The only way to put up a fight against Christina
is by unleashing your Princess Knight ability.
Princess... Knight?
You once made use of this power
before losing your memories.
Try to remember.
It's all yours,
for you and you alone, to use at will.
Remember the olden days
when you adventured with us.
What's wrong?
Is that all you had to offer?
I suppose that concludes this act, then.
...let you...
I won't let you!
Huh? What's going on?
This power...
I feel power welling up in me!
Let us advance.
Is this
your power?
Here I go!
Metamorapple!
Rima, rima!
Many thanks, Yuuki!
What?
I've got you.
Wish upon a star!
Shooting Star!
I wish you luck!
How interesting.
Your party's power has grown so much,
they almost seem like different people.
And... this isn't magic, is it?
My lord!
What's your name?
Yuuki.
This day has yielded a greater
harvest than I anticipated.
It's been too long since I've had such a good time.
Oh, yes. As for that archer beast...
She's most likely been swallowed by a Shadow.
If she is still herself, then perhaps...
Shiorin!
That's right.
My mission is to observe Pecorine and Yuuki.
I just... I just need to continue
keeping an eye on where this goes.
Yeah! This is how you ought to be!
My tummy's giving in...
I would've gone for a bigger breakfast
had I known this would happen...
Make more... Make more...
What do you think you're doing, Pecorine?
We have to get rid of these fiends
and harvest a lot of spice, no?
Yes!
Are you ready for this?
Grim Burst!
Shiorin!
Don't give in! I'm coming to save you right now!
Hatsune?!
Are you all right?
Korosuke!
Exactly what the hell is going on?
I'm sorry, Hatsune...
I... can't...
Shiorin!
Stay strong, Shiorin!
We're getting out of here!
Hatsune?
Don't fall asleep, Shiorin!
Sleeping is my job! Things will
get hairy if you take over my job!
Come on, let's go!
I can't.
I'll... only be a burden to you.
If this goes on, we'll both...
So you have to get out of here,
even if you're the only one...
Hatsune?
You're not a burden at all, Shiorin.
You're always cheering me up!
Remember what I told you?
I'll just carry you on my back and fly away!
Make more... Make more...
Make more of me...
A Shadow!
I used too much of my power...
I made it this far, and yet...
Shiorin?
Thank you, Hatsune.
Thank you for always protecting me.
One day, I will be the one to protect you.
That is my wish, and my goal.
I'm right here with you.
Enchanted Arrow!
Get out...
Get out of me!
That's...
Karyl!
I know! You'd better do this right!
Dark Vortex!
Full power! Full throttle!
Princess Strike!
Talk about sloppy.
You must not have eaten enough.
I sure am hungry.
Shiori?
Rima...
Thank goodness! She's the usual Shiori again!
Is Hatsune all right?!
She's... sleeping?
Shh.
A Little, Lyrical Kids' Meal
Country-Style Fried Eggs
Wow! This is so good!
So good!