Sorry, did I wake you?
You can sleep a little longer.
I'd like to focus on this.
What's with that look?
I'm kinda sad that you're acting like
we've never met before.
I'm...
Well, you can call me Ameth.
I can't interact with reality
until I'm done with my self-repairs.
In light of that, I have assigned someone else
to serve as your guide in my stead.
I wish we could chat for a little longer,
but you can't keep dreaming forever.
What a pretty star!
A shooting star?
The Adventure Begins
Sautéed Mushrooms at Sunset
Kokkoro.
You must not fail to carry out
the oracle of Lady Ameth.
Father...
I'll serve my lord to my utmost ability.
On the hills up ahead lies the land of prophecy.
I wonder what he's like.
I musn't look sloppy in his presence.
So that person is...
He is my
lord—
M-My lord!
Th-That was too close.
Start with a low, low, low flame,
then turn the heat up, up.
Even if your baby cries...
It looks like you've finally woken up.
Are you in pain?
Doesn't look like you are.
I was sent by the great Lady Ameth
to serve as your guide.
My name is Kokkoro.
It is my sworn duty to protect you,
from dawn to dusk,
from the cradle to the grave,
and to devote my entire being
to your service, my lord.
Oh my?
If it's fine with you, would you
be willing to share your name with me?
Yuuki.
My name is Yuuki.
I'm glad to hear that.
You are definitely the lord I was meant to serve.
According to the oracle of Lady Ameth,
it would seem you have lost many of your memories.
I'm sure you must be quite confused.
But I am here to guide you,
so you can rest at ease.
Please, have some.
It would appear they still haven't given up.
My lord.
They will serve as the perfect
opponents for us right now.
By accumulating experience,
you will slowly regain your original abilities.
Any foe would be powerless before you.
And I shall brush away any sparks
that may rain upon you.
Now, let us advance!
M-My lord!
A-Are you all right, my lord?
Please forgive me.
You had only just awakened, so...
M-My lord!
Landosol's only another day away or so.
It's a real shame stone monsters are too hard to eat.
That should do it!
Father, Mother...
Help! Somebody, please! Help us!
What's going on?
Ouch, ouch, ouch! Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Bro! Hang in there, Bro!
All I see is one, big blur...
Don't be ridiculous, Bro!
No! Whatever you do, don't close your eyes!
Did some monster attack you?
Oh, you came at the nick of time, young lady!
I can see a beautiful flower field...
My bro's chronic beriberi has taken a turn
for the worst, and now he's all like this!
Oh, my late grandma is waving at me...
Do you see that sack up there?
His medicine is in there!
Could you please fetch it for him?
It hurts... It hurts...
Of course! The medicine, you said?
We're counting on you, cutie!
I got it!
Oh, huh?
Wha-ha-ha—?
T'was a success, Bro!
Much obliged!
Whaaa—?!
Wait! Please!
Royal Capital: Landosol
We've arrived.
But truly, I am relieved you weren't injured.
Want to go bathing with me?
A tail?
Bathing?
I have some great soap.
Thanks, but I'll pass.
She is of the beast clan.
In this world there are humans,
elves, beasts, and demons,
Oh, you'll find that place on
the second corner down the road.
just to name a few.
Incidentally, I am an elf.
Landosol, where we are right now,
is the largest nation on the continent of Astraea.
We are currently in its capital.
We got some fresh fish here! Come take a look!
Ah, forgive me. It all seemed so curious to me...
Huh? My lord?
Come now! Step right up!
Welcome!
Oh? Brother and sister out shopping together?
How cute. What would you like?
I-I'm not his little sister...
Oh, you're not?
Girlfriend then, perhaps?
N-N-No, I'm not!
Sorry about that. So, what kinda
crêpe would you like?
Great!
Chocolate and strawberry, coming right up!
My lord, here you go.
My lord! You shouldn't put that in your mouth!
You're not supposed to eat it!
Spit it out! Spit!
Ptoo.
I forgot you've lost your memories.
This is money.
You can exchange it for various goods
and services from shops.
It's not something you can eat.
Do you understand?
Thanks for the wait!
Wonderful! Now we're all set to go shopping!
Money. Important. Learned.
It's delicious.
This is the first time I've had something like this.
It's so sweet,
and the strawberry-flavoured sau—
Y-You have done well today.
I'll find lodging for us. You can stay here and rest.
What?
I'm sorry, young lady.
But I've got a business to run, y'know.
You're welcome anytime once you can afford it!
My sincerest apologies.
I didn't realise lodging was so expensive.
If it's come to this, I can use
the staff my father gave me to—
He hasn't complained once
about my lacklustre guidance.
Rather, he's fully accepted me.
My lord truly is kind.
Tomorrow... for my lord, I will...
M-My lord!
Please forgive me!
I should have been more alert
while we were camping!
I fear that if this continues,
you'll end up as a wolf snack one day.
So I've decided to take some precautions.
You should try to enjoy yourself while I'm busy.
You can eat out or find something else to do.
This is your allowance for the day.
Here you go.
I'll be back at fifth bell.
Lets meet up again here then.
What's wrong? Has being in
an unfamiliar environment made you ill?
Or is that amount of money insufficient?
My apologies. This is all the money we have.
I'll go sell some of my ornaments for mo—
My lord, what's the matter?
Money important.
Money important! Learned!
This must be the place.
But are you sure you wish to work?
What brings you here?
I'm Karin, and I work for the Guild Association.
If there's anything I can help with,
please don't hesitate to call me.
I heard there is a bulletin board here with job postings.
There is. I'll show you.
Let's see...
Subjugation quests, escort quests...
There's also one for dungeon investigating.
I wouldn't recommend any of these to a beginner.
"Reports of a dragon sighted in the vicinity of Landosol."
"Seeking members for a team to defeat the dragon"
"before its attraction to
Landosol's riches leads to casualties."
This isn't a quest we could handle.
Oh! This one should be suitable!
It's a fetching quest.
There's a request for someone to gather
some mushrooms that grow in the Gado Ruins.
It doesn't seem too dangerous.
I'd recommend this.
We accept!
I hope that poor man from yesterday is all right.
I've gotta get this medicine to him quickly.
I'm also concerned about the sword
Mother and Father gave me.
I'm hungry as a wolf
after fending off all those monsters.
Yeah!
I'm Ikacchi!
You're Charlie!
It's the beriberi man from yesterday!
Are you all right now?
Gah!
That chick just doesn't give up!
She still believes I have beriberi?!
What?
Your medicine! I have your medicine right here!
What do you think?
Looks like the coast is clear.
Just a li'l bit till we're in Landosol, Bro!
Yeah!
And once we sell this thing,
we'll be rolling in dough!
This way, my lord.
Look here.
They grow in places like this.
Look for similar spots and try to find more.
This forest sure is filled with mushrooms.
It must be a little-known hotspot.
What an unusual mushroom.
Since you go "puchipuchi", I'm calling you Puchiko.
I know we need that quest reward,
but I can't take a tiny life like this...
Hide in here, Puchiko.
M-My stomach is so empty...
Mm-mmm!
Nothing gives you quite a boost like rice does!
You really saved me!
It was so kind of you to share
such delicious food with a stranger!
I'm forever in your debt!
Excuse me, but what brings you to a place like this?
Oh, well... I've been travelling for
some personal reasons, you see?
I thought I'd visit my homeland,
Landosol, since it's been so long.
But whoopsie, I almost starved!
And you collapsed?
Sure did! How crazy is that?
Anyway, what about you two?
We're here to gather mushrooms.
Those look delicious.
Feel free to have some.
May I?!
You two must be gods!
Oh, your names are Yuuki and Kokkoro, huh?
Mushroom!
I think they're after me.
I'm sorry for dragging you two into this.
Yuuki?
Um... Miss Starving Peckish Pecorine?
I'm going to call you that for now.
There's no going back now,
so let's get out of this together.
Oh! By "Pecorine", do you mean me?
That's a very cute nickname! How crazy is that?
But... I'm happy to know you both feel that way!
May the light's blessing be with you!
I've boosted your agility, my lord.
You should fare much better now!
Nameko!
Maitake!
My lord!
Kokkoro?!
Maitake!
My lord!
What's this?
Just like Lady Ameth's oracle...
How divine!
This is indeed my lord's unique power,
the proof he is the Princess Knight!
There's more and more power bubbling up inside me!
Is that because of Yuuki?
Yes.
Now, let us advance!
Wind spirits, lend us your aid!
Here I come!
Princess Strike!
What a great haul!
I didn't expect us to get this many mushrooms.
Let's gather them all in one place
and talk to Miss Karin.
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
Okay!
Damn  I was so close to leeching her nutrients
!
A flower field...
In that case,
I've just gotta feed off her directly
!
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
There's another mushroom right here!
And it's a nice bite-sized one!
Wait! That's—
They still taste good, even when eaten raw!
How crazy is that?
M-Miss Pecorine!
Peco, peco... Peco, peco...
I'm Pecorine... Pecorine...
She seems quite cheerful.
I'm glad it wasn't poisonous.
That little one has become
Miss Pecorine's flesh and blood...
Miss Puchi-Pecorine...
It looks like your story has begun at last.
Only the gods will know whether you'll
swing towards the happy or bad ending.
But don't forget this:
What is true in this world,
and what is false in this world...
On your journey to reveal that,
you are sure to meet many new people.
Alone, your power may be tiny.
But the bonds you form along the way
will become the power to save them all.
Since this is something only you can do.
You, the Princess Knight.
Kokkoro...
Yes, my lord?
I'm counting on you.
Of course, my lord.
Seconds, please!
A Moody Cat's Mischief
Warm, Golden Rice Balls