Are you done getting changed?
Yes.
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
kowabaru kokoro
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
That I'll never be able to escape
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
All I can do is adapt
kawatte ikeru no wa
To the world I now find myself in
jibun jishin dake
And nothing more
sore dakesa
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
And I can't afford to stop!
doushitatte
I can’t erase my fantasies
kesenai yume mo
And there's no way to rewind time
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as I have someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
This world once showed me true despair
sekai ni uchinomesarete
Made me wallow in my own failures
makeru imi wo shitta
But now my path is bright and clear
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
unmei wo terashite
The Swordsman and
his Demon Companion
Episode
Tanjirou.
Now that you've become part of the Demon Slayers,
I'd like to explain a few things to you.
All right.
That Demon Slayer uniform you're wearing
right now is made of a special kind of fiber.
The fabric is quite breathable,
yet it repels moisture and won't burn easily.
Even the claws and fangs of lesser demons
cannot rend that uniform.
It's that strong?
Also,
that Sun Blade of yours...
The color varies from owner to owner,
and each hue has its unique properties.
But since very few people end up with
black blades, little is known about them.
So little, in fact, that—
So little is known that...
What, Master Urokodaki?
Since so little is known about them,
they are said to be wielded by swordsmen
that don't make it very far.
I don't know how well I'll do as a Demon Slayer,
but I'm going to turn Nezuko
back into a human no matter what.
Yes, that's right.
I have faith that you can make that happen.
Right.
One more thing.
Take this.
It's a box for you to carry
your sister in during the day.
It's built out of an extremely light wood
called "Cloud Mist Pine".
I coated it with rock lacquer to reinforce its
exterior and to make it even more durable.
Thank you very much!
Wow, so light!
It's really lightweight, Master Urokodaki!
Nezuko!
Get in, will you?
Think you can do it?
Nezuko, we'll always be together from now on, okay?
All right, I'm off.
Stay still for a moment.
Nezuko, are you all right?
Nezuko?
I'm just taking a guess here,
but it could be that Nezuko's recovering her strength
through sleep rather than by consuming flesh.
Nezuko...
Rest up well.
Could this be the town to the northwest?
Oh, look. It's Kazumi.
Poor thing. He looks so haggard.
That's because he was with Satoko when she vanished.
It happens night after night... It's so creepy.
It's so dreadful!
When night falls, yet another
young girl will be abducted!
Kazumi!
If you don't mind, I'd like to hear your story.
Is that all right?
This is where Satoko vanished.
You may not believe me.
I do believe you!
I really do.
I believe you!
There's still a faint trace of a demon,
but it's uneven, so to speak.
Something's not right here.
Who is this kid anyway?
How dare you!
What do you mean, "vanished"?
You bastard!
Dear!
That's enough! Please stop!
I want you to believe me.
She really did vanish.
I believe you.
That's why I've come here, after all.
You're gonna keep going?
Yes.
It's gotten pretty late.
I'm flattered that you're so concerned for me,
but shouldn't you go get some rest
and pick this up again tomorrow?
They are active during the night.
So I can't afford to go get some rest now.
I've caught a new scent in this area.
It's gotta be somewhere nearby.
They?
Don't tell me you're...
Seriously...?
How terrifying.
I want you to stay indoors for the time being.
Yes, Mother.
Now then, good night.
I wonder what became of the girls that disappeared.
I just hope they're all right.
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
So fast!
The scent just got stronger!
The demon's at large!
He jumped?
He spoke of demons.
The Demon Slayers...
He really is...
This is it.
They're here!
I can smell two different scents.
A demon and a human girl!
They're nowhere to be seen.
But...
The spot where the scent is strongest...
is right here!
A deformed demon!
There are demons that use special techniques called the
"Demon Blood Arts", which grants them supernatural abilities.
You may have to fight those kinds
of demons as well from now on.
Where are all the girls you kidnapped?
I've got two more questions for you!
What was that?
Kazumi,
please take care of her and be on standby nearby.
So long as you stay close, I can protect you!
He can probably emerge from any surface,
like the ground or the wall...
Odds are that he could even appear out of thin air.
However,
even if he's submerged, he can't erase his scent!
Here he comes!
Water Breathing!
Fifth Form!
There's three of them!
Calm down!
You can do it!
Eighth Form!
Waterfall Basin!
Demon Slayer
Tanjirou, listen to me closely.
There's only one demon in the world
with the blood that can turn humans into demons.
Just one...
The one who was the first to become
a demon over a thousand years ago.
In other words, he's your true enemy.
Moreover, I believe he's the one who might know
how to turn your sister back into a human.
That demon's name is
Kibutsuji Muzan!
Eighth Form!
Waterfall Basin!
Too shallow!
I missed all the vulnerable spots
because I switched forms midway through!
All three of them share the exact same scent!
I was told that demons don't band together as a rule.
So that means it has to be one demon
that split into three.
I will protect these two while fighting the demon!
Stay determined!
I'll make him tell me everything!
Everything he knows about Kibutsuji Muzan
and how to turn a demon back into a human!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
Second Form!
Water Wheel!
Still not deep enough!
I can't chase him too far.
And I can't take a full swing while guarding others!
You damn bastard!
Screw off, will ya?!
That girl's gonna go stale, goddamn it!
She's already sixteen, y'know?
If I don't devour her soon, she's just
gonna keep losing flavor by the second!
Calm down, my other self.
So what?
There are gonna be nights like this.
I've already fed on plenty of
sixteen-year-old girls in this town.
They were all quite meaty and delicious.
I'm satisfied.
Well, I'm not satisfied, my other self!
I wanna devour more!
You monster...
Return Satoko, the one you abducted
the night before last, to me!
Satoko?
Who are you talking about?
If her hairpin is among these collectibles,
then I've already eaten her.
I missed again!
He escapes underground too fast!
Oh, no! I got too close to the wall!
Why would a demon be accompanying a mere human?
What's the meaning of this?
Who are those two?
A swordsman and a demon working together?
I don't get it at all.
Nezuko...
It may only help to console her,
but while Nezuko was asleep,
I placed her under a hypnotic suggestion.
Suggestion?
"All humans are your family."
"Protect humans."
"The demons are your enemy!"
Nezuko!
"Never forgive any demons
who bring harm onto humans!"
I don't want to be imprisoned by sadness
kanashimi ni torewaretaku wa nai
I don't want to come back
utsumuita basho ni
To the place I cast my head down crying
namida wo otoshite yukitakunai
Free from the shackles of fate
unmei wo furihodoite
You're supposed to start running
hashiridaseru hazu nanda
That dream is meant to come true
negai wa kanau hazu nanda
Break free from the troubles of yesterday
tatakitsubuse kinou no katou
Pray for the future from the edge of darkness
Ride the wind that's leading the way
mukai kaze wo nototte
Face the unseen beyond the storm
arashi no saki wa mienaku tatte
There's only one path—
mou michi wa erabenai kachinokore
To make it out alive!
The choice between love and light
mayoi wa itsumo aijou to hikari wo hakari ni kakeru
Will always cast doubt upon your mind
Now rise up once more
saa tachiagarunda mou ichido
Now, where might you strike down
ima kimi wa sono yaiba wo
With that blade of yours?
doko he furiorosu
Demon Slayer
Rustle
PREVIEW
Your kicks really saved the day, Nezuko!
Thanks!
It didn't break even after
it got kicked from the inside.
That box is super strong!
But isn't it cramped in there?
Aren't you uncomfortable?
I'll build a much bigger box for you!
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
I heard today's demon has had the bad habit of
grinding his teeth like mad since he was a human.
Rustle
PREVIEW
Next, Episode 7, "Kibutsuji Muzan"!
To Be Continued