Tanjirou...
Listen here.
The Demon Slayers aren't something you join for fun!
Guys like you must be purged!
Pronto!
Don't ever underestimate the Demon Slayers!
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
kowabaru kokoro
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
That I'll never be able to escape
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
All I can do is adapt
kawatte ikeru no wa
To the world I now find myself in
jibun jishin dake
And nothing more
sore dakesa
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
And I can't afford to stop!
doushitatte
I can’t erase my fantasies
kesenai yume mo
And there's no way to rewind time
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as I have someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
This world once showed me true despair
sekai ni uchinomesarete
Made me wallow in my own failures
makeru imi wo shitta
But now my path is bright and clear
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
unmei wo terashite
Wisteria
Nezuko!
Zenitsu! Stop following her already!
Ta-n-ji-rou!
Let's be friends, Tanjirou!
Zenitsu! Stop chasing us! I beg you!
Oh, don't be like that, Tanjirou!
Nezuko!
Tanjirou!
Stop!
Zenitsu!
Nezuko!
Tanjirou!
Man, I'm starving.
Pardon me, sir.
Those clothes of yours are quite dirty, I see.
Allow me to clean them for you.
Please wear these in the mean time.
They're pleasant to the touch and quite comfortable.
How does tempura for dinner sound?
You know, something covered with batter and fried.
Hey, wait up!
Come back here, Nezuko!
Wh-What was that for?
Hold up! Hold up!
Stop chasing us, Inosuke!
Tanjirou!
Mount Natagumo
Episode
Fully recovered.
North-northeast! North-northeast!
Your next mission is north-northeast!
The three of you are to go to Mt. Natagumo!
Head to Mt. Natagumo!
We'll be heading out now.
Thank you so much for everything.
Now then, for good luck.
Thank you so much!
What do you think you're doing, old hag?
What are you, a moron?
She's striking sparks for good luck!
It's a purification ceremony because
we're going on a dangerous mission!
Wisteria
Always live your lives with great pride.
I wish you luck in battle!
"Great pride"?
"Luck in battle"?
What's that mean?
Geez, this guy sure is thick.
Well, yeah. Now that you mention it,
it's kind of difficult to understand.
"With great pride"...
I guess it means that you know your place
and that you behave properly
so as to never disgrace yourself.
And the old lady is also praying for our safety.
So, what is this "place"?
What do you mean by "never disgrace"?
Well, that's...
What exactly does it mean to "behave properly"?
Why the hell would that old hag
pray for our safety anyway?
She ain't got anything to do with us, so why?
She has no clue what her own place is, does she?
He sped up!
I won't be beaten!
Wait up!
Hold up!
Could you wait for just a second?
Zenitsu? What's wrong?
I'm scared!
Now that we're nearing our destination,
I'm quaking in my boots!
Why the hell is his ass on the ground?
How creepy is that?
Who are you to talk, Pig Face?
Don't tell me you're not getting
any weird vibes from that mountain!
Still, what good would it do to just sit there?
I told you, he's creepy.
I am anything but creepy!
I'm normal! I'm the normal one!
You guys are the abnormal ones!
What? What's wrong?
Hey...
What is this smell?
Tanjirou!
Come on! Don't leave me here by myself!
Don't leave my side!
H-Help me...
He's got our uniform on!
He's a Demon Slayer!
Something must've happened!
Hold up!
Are you all right?
What happened?
They were attached to me, too!
Help me!
I'm going.
I'll go on ahead.
You can follow me, shivering in your boots.
This is making me hungry.
Inosuke...
This is challenging enough for you, right?
Let's go!
What the hell is this?
A spider web?
Geez, this place is full of spider webs!
What a pain!
You're right.
Inosuke?
What do you want?
Thanks.
I felt a lot more encouraged
since you said you'd come along.
That twisted, ominous scent I was
picking up from the mountain...
It made me freeze a little.
Thanks!
These are pleasant to the touch and quite comfortable.
Always live your lives with great pride.
I wish you luck in battle!
Inosuke...
Let's go.
We've come for backup.
I'm Kamado Tanjirou, Rank Mizunoto.
Mizunoto...
Mizunoto?
Why didn't they send a Hashira?
It doesn't matter how many Mizunoto they send!
It won't make a difference!
Inosuke!
Shut up!
As far as making a difference goes,
your existence itself doesn't make one at all!
Now tell us what's going on, you spineless fool!
Who the hell is this guy?
Did you forget that I have seniority?
Th-The crow gave us the order!
Ten of us Demon Slayers came here.
Not long after we entered the mountain,
the Slayers...
The Slayers started killing each other!
I...
You did well to return.
So most of my children have been slaughtered?
If that's the case, we might find the Blood Moons there.
It seems I'll have to send in some Hashiras.
Giyuu.
Shinobu.
As you wish!
If only humans and demons could just get along.
Don't you agree, Tomioka?
Impossible.
Not so long as demons eat humans.
Demon Slayer
I wonder if they hate me.
Would you really leave your friend by the roadside?
Wouldn't you talk him through it if you were friends?
If they both tried to talk me into going,
Zenitsu...
Zenitsu.
I would've gone, okay?
Sure I would.
But no, off they went on their merry way
up that scary mountain.
Poor me, left all alone here...
Sulking won't do you any good. You have to go help your friends.
Lucky you. You don't have a care in the world.
You don't understand a thing about humans, do you?
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You're not cute at all! I mean it!
Not that side of you!
Seriously, you've got zero charm!
I mean, look at how cute Nezuko is!
And she's a demon!
But you're a sparrow, and you're so vicious!
He took Nezuko with him!
Why did he have to take my
precious Nezuko with him?
Damn it, Tanjirou!
Don't bring a young lass into danger!
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Nezuko!
What is that sound?
There it is again.
It's that sound again!
I heard this sound,
and the next thing I knew,
everyone started killing each other!
Where's it coming from?
These guys are all morons!
They don't even know that
we're not allowed to fight each other!
No, that's not it!
They're not moving normally!
Something is manipulating them!
All right.
I'm gonna slash them to ribbons!
You can't do that!
They're alive!
Some of them are still alive!
Besides, we can't harm the corpses of our teammates!
Stop denying me at every turn!
There's this strange, sweet scent coming from his back!
Threads! They're being manipulated by threads!
Slash the threads!
I already knew that before you caught on!
Where's the demon controlling them?
What's this?
What is this sudden, irritating odor?
What the—?
Spiders!
So those threads are being spun by these spiders?
That means...
Now then, my sweet little marionettes...
Dance until your arms and legs fall off.
We can't get by if all we do is cut the threads!
The spiders are just gonna stick more onto them!
So...
That acrid smell again!
What is it anyway?
It's being carried here by the wind!
All we gotta do is kill all those damn spiders, huh?
That's impossible!
They're tiny, and there's probably a ton of them!
We've got to find the demon who's controlling them!
Don't bother, Inosuke!
Inosuke, if you have some kind of ability
that can pinpoint the demon's location,
then give me a helping hand!
This weird smell has been flowing in
and it's blocking my nose!
And also, um...
It's Murata!
Murata!
Murata and I will find a way to deal with
the people being controlled!
Inosuke, you...
Don't disturb my family's peaceful life.
He's floating!
Wait, no.
He's standing on the threads!
What did he mean by "family"?
Mother will kill you all right away.
Mother?
Damn you!
Where the hell do you think you're going? Fight me!
Fight—
Inosuke!
Why did he show up anyway?
That kid probably isn't the demon pulling the threads!
First, let's...
Okay, okay, okay!
I hear you, all right?
You just need me to find where that demon's at, right?
Shut up already, Mr. Forehead!
Beast Breathing! Seventh Form!
Spatial Awareness!
Found them!
There you are!
I won't let anyone get in our way.
The five of us are going to live in bliss as a family.
No one can break our bond.
I don't want to be imprisoned by sadness
kanashimi ni torewaretaku wa nai
I don't want to come back
utsumuita basho ni
To the place I cast my head down crying
namida wo otoshite yukitakunai
Free from the shackles of fate
unmei wo furihodoite
You're supposed to start running
hashiridaseru hazu nanda
That dream is meant to come true
negai wa kanau hazu nanda
Break free from the troubles of yesterday
tatakitsubuse kinou no katou
Pray for the future from the edge of darkness
Ride the wind that's leading the way
mukai kaze wo nototte
Face the unseen beyond the storm
arashi no saki wa mienaku tatte
There's only one path—
mou michi wa erabenai kachinokore
To make it out alive!
The choice between love and light
mayoi wa itsumo aijou to hikari wo hakari ni kakeru
Will always cast doubt upon your mind
Now rise up once more
saa tachiagarunda mou ichido
Now, where might you strike down
ima kimi wa sono yaiba wo
With that blade of yours?
doko he furiorosu
Demon Slayer
PREVIEW
Whoopsie-daisy!
Nezuko!
Tanjirou!
Where are you?
PREVIEW
l
First, let's calm down
and listen to the
sounds around us!
First, let's calm down
and listen to the
sounds around us!
PREVIEW
Nezuko's in danger!
Stop chirping and help me find her, Chuntarou!
l
I told you
to calm down!
Now, it's time
for a Taisho secret!
My real name
is Ukogi.
That's because my
favorite food is
ukogi rice.
That's because my
favorite food is
ukogi rice.
But Zenitsu
hasn't noticed yet,
so all I get is beans.
But Zenitsu
hasn't noticed yet,
so all I get is beans.
What are you so mad about?
PREVIEW
Here, eat this and calm down.
l
It's an ukogi
rice ball!
Help me look once you're done, okay?
I mean, Nezuko's in danger!
l
He's seriously
worried...
Nezuko!
I guess this is
why you just
can't hate the guy.
I guess this is
why you just
can't hate the guy.
Next, Episode 16,
"Letting Someone Else Go First"!
To Be Continued