Are you heading into battle?
Oh, if it isn't Kochou!
A new demon has surfaced, and the Slayers
that confronted him were taken out.
Innocent folk have fallen victim.
We can't ignore this any longer.
Could it be one of the Twelve Blood Moons?
Most likely. It might have even been
one of the Waxing Moons.
Sounds like you've got a tough mission ahead of you.
But I trust I'll have nothing
to worry about if you're in charge.
Kochou, what are you planning?
Why would you take that headbutting boy in?
You said you wanted to add more
Tsuguko to your ranks,
but I'm sure you've got other reasons in mind.
No worries. It's not as if I'd gobble him up, right?
Of course you wouldn't!
Be careful.
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
kowabaru kokoro
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
That I'll never be able to escape
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
All I can do is adapt
kawatte ikeru no wa
To the world I now find myself in
jibun jishin dake
And nothing more
sore dakesa
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
And I can't afford to stop!
doushitatte
I can’t erase my fantasies
kesenai yume mo
And there's no way to rewind time
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as I have someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
This world once showed me true despair
sekai ni uchinomesarete
Made me wallow in my own failures
makeru imi wo shitta
But now my path is bright and clear
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
unmei wo terashite
Episode 24
Rehabilitation Training
No!
I can't take it anymore!
Seriously, every time with you!
You're the worst off out of anyone here, Zenitsu!
Stuff it and take your medicine right now!
Seriously, this guy...
Tanjirou, here's your medicine.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Hey!
Tanjirou's medicine goes down
the drain pretty easily, huh?
It's different from mine, right?
I sense favouritism! Favouritism, I say!
Zenitsu, this is a hospital ward!
Quiet down a little!
You seem to be doing well!
Murata!
Hey!
Are you all right?
Well, I was pretty close to getting dissolved,
but I made it one way or another in the end.
I hear you guys took quite a beating, though.
Yeah, looks like we'll be taking it easy for a while.
And you ended up with throat issues, Boar Boy?
What's up with him?
He went through a lot.
If you could please let him be...
But for this guy of all people to be so listless—
Tanjirou!
Who's this?
This is Murata. He fought with us on Mt. Natagumo.
I'm Murata! Nice to meet you!
Hey, your arm...
I almost turned into one of those creepy spiders.
I've still got stumps for limbs.
And that's why you need to take your medicine!
But it tastes disgusting!
There's only so much a person can take!
Fine, but don't come crying to me
if your arms don't return to normal!
That's so cold, I almost thought it was winter!
You don't know how good you have it!
If you take your medicine and bask in enough sunlight,
there won't even be any lasting effects!
I can't do it!
Gross is gross! No two ways about it!
Looks like fun. Lucky you.
Murata?
I was summoned to the Hashira Meeting
to give my report on the Mt. Natagumo incident.
I thought I accidentally walked into Hell!
They're absolutely terrifying!
They were pissed at how poorly the newer
Demon Slayers have been performing as of late.
Especially since some of us weren't following
our orders back on Mt. Natagumo.
They then questioned who
in their right mind even trained us.
What good would it do to ask someone of my rank?
The Hashira terrify me...
Hello there.
Hashira! Lady Kochou!
Hello there!
Oh, hello! And goodbye!
Oh, my! See you soon!
Well? How's your rehab going?
It's going well. We've been steadily improving.
Well, how about we start your
Rehabilitation Training then?
Rehabilitation Training?
Yes!
I'm sorry for being so weak...
l
Two Weeks Later
RKJGHERSKJGHSKUJDHF
SDKHFGSDJHF
KJSHERFGKJSRHGKJ
NSREKJHGFSKRJGHSRK
RKJGHERSKJGHSKUJDHF
SDKHFGSDJHF
KJSHERFGKJSRHGKJ
NSREKJHGFSKRJGHSRK
Tanjirou and Inosuke were taken away
by the Hashira, Miss Kochou,
Mirror
and started some kind of "Rehabilitation Training".
Miss Shinobu's voice is like no other.
I don't think I've ever heard anything like it.
It's irregular, and that scares me a little.
But she seemed like a goddess back when she treated
all those people that turned into spiderlings.
No wonder everyone crawled to Lady Shinobu in tears.
Not only that, but she's cute beyond compare!
I bet she could make a living on her looks alone.
And this cute lady is now training Tanjirou
and Inosuke to build up their condition again.
And any minute now...
...they'll come back, looking like they've seen a ghost.
Welcome back, guys!
How'd it go today?
What happened?
What's wrong? Hey...
Sorry.
Don't mind us.
For the love of God, please tell me!
I'll be joining you two in this death march tomorrow!
Oh god, no!
l
The Next Day
RKJGHERSKJGHSKUJDHF
SDKHFGSDJHF
KJSHERFGKJSRHGKJ
NSREKJHGFSKRJGHSRK
RKJGHERSKJGHSKUJDHF
SDKHFGSDJHF
KJSHERFGKJSRHGKJ
NSREKJHGFSKRJGHSRK
I'm scared! This is terrifying!
I don't wanna go!
Since Zenitsu is joining us from today onwards,
I'll go over the process again.
You'll start over there.
They'll make your bodies limber again
after having been bedridden for so long.
Next, there's reflex training.
These cups contain medicated water.
The objective is to splash it over each other.
However, if your opponent blocks
your cup before you can pick it up,
you're not allowed to move it anymore.
Now!
Again!
Stop!
Last up, we've got full-body training.
In simpler terms, you'll be playing tag.
You'll be up against me,
Aoi, and Kanao over there.
Excuse me. If I may?
Is there something that's not clear to you?
No, it's just...
You two. Come with me.
I'm staying right here.
Shut your mouth and come with me, now!
I said now!
Get a move on, you sleazebags!
You damn slowpokes!
The hell is wrong with you?
Sit up straight and listen to me, you morons.
You miserable maggots!
The hell was that, you damn—
Inosuke!
What are you thinking, Zenitsu?
Apologize to him right now!
It's you guys who should apologize!
C'mon, I'm waiting!
How dare you act like you've come back
from Hell when you were in Heaven all along!
All you did was frolic with girls all day,
so why did you look so exhausted?
Prostrate yourselves and apologize!
Cut your own stomach and die!
How can you say that?
Shut it, you headbutting paragon of virtue!
Shut your trap and listen up, got it?
You're allowed to touch girls!
You get to have your bodies massaged!
You get to touch hands with that cup game!
And with tag, you get to touch
their whole freakin' bodies!
Every girl has two bouncy boobs,
one fine rear, and two soft thighs!
They smell so nice when they pass by,
and just looking at them fills me with bliss!
It's the greatest fortune! Heaven on Earth!
You're full of shit! Nothing you said makes any sense!
When you lose to someone smaller
than you, it destroys your soul!
Oh, poor you! You've never been
chummy with a girl before, have you?
Just what you'd expect from a mountain boy!
Oh, this is so sad!
That's it!
The hell do you think you are?
I'll have you know I've stomped on
plenty of little girls before!
That's the worst thing you could do!
The hell's wrong with you?!
That's not gonna get you any girls!
I can get as many girls as I want!
Please train me well!
This is fine! All good!
This guy isn't normal.
I'm always fighting back tears from
the pain, but he's laughing.
I shall take you on.
Begin!
I would never splash tea on a lady.
Now then, full-body training!
Begin!
I win!
I won the battle but lost the war!
I'm gonna kick some ass, too!
All right!
Ouch!
I'm the only one on a losing streak and soaked.
This is so embarrassing!
But...
We just can't beat Kanao.
None of us can get to a cup before her
or stop her from splashing us.
For the next five days,
my losing streak against Kanao kept racking up.
As did Inosuke's.
Zenitsu's, too.
We couldn't so much as lay a finger
on a strand of her hair.
And then one day, the other two
stopped coming to the dojo entirely.
Z-Zenitsu? Inosuke?
Please train me!
Thank you for a good workout.
Why can't I beat her?
What gives her the edge over me?
Let's see. Her reflexes are way faster.
Even if I were in top form, I'd probably lose to her.
Her scent is totally different.
It reminds me of the scent of the Hashira.
Master Tanjirou?
Also... her eyes?
Her eyes are different!
Master Tanjirou?
I have the feeling that...
Um...
Master Tanjirou, are you okay?
We've been calling you over and over.
Sorry! I was lost in thought.
What's up?
Here's a towel for you.
Thanks! That's a big help!
You're all so kind!
Um, Master Tanjirou,
we were wondering if you keep up your
Breathing Technique at all times.
From morning to noon, and even while you're asleep?
Do you use your techniques nonstop?
No, I don't. That's never even come to mind.
Is doing that even possible?
It is!
We're told that being able to
makes all the difference in the world!
Just using it a couple of minutes
at a time already takes its toll on me,
and you want me to do it around the clock?
Some people have already mastered it.
Every Hashira has—and even Miss Kanao!
Please work hard at it!
I see!
Thanks! I'll give it a go!
Demon Slayer
Isn't it about time you came back to training, Inosuke?
Sulking won't do you any good.
Zenitsu, you should come, too!
Yup!
I think I did a splendid job.
Just tell 'em my injury's taken a turn for the worse!
Hey, Kakushi lady over there!
Would you like to have some tea with me?
Total Concentration Breathing.
From dawn to dusk, and even in my sleep.
I said I'd try to keep it up around the clock.
But there's no way I can do that!
I seriously can't!
If I try keeping it up for prolonged amounts of time,
I just end up feeling like I'm on the verge of death!
The toll is too much for me to endure.
My lungs and ears hurt!
My ears are ringing like crazy!
My eardrums!
That scared the heck out of me!
I thought my heart was about to
come out through my eardrums!
I'll never make it at this rate!
When in doubt, return to the basics!
You spineless fool!
Breathing is all about lung capacity.
If I can't get the hang of it,
that means my lungs are too weak.
I have to improve it!
I have to give it my all.
That's always been how I did it!
Hard work is a daily process!
Slow and steady wins the race!
I just need to take one step at a time.
Right!
Master Tanjirou works hard every day!
Yeah! Let's bring him some rice balls, okay?
Good idea! And also...
Blow into these gourds?
That's right.
Whenever she trained Lady Kanao,
Lady Shinobu often had her blow into gourds.
Oh, really?
That's an interesting training technique, huh?
What kind of sound are you supposed to make?
Oh, no. Not that.
She blew into it to make it explode.
Oh, really?
Explode?
What? You mean you blow these up?
Something this hard?
Yes!
Not to mention, this is a special gourd,
so it's tougher than normal ones.
A girl that petite was able to
blow up such strong gourds?
The gourds get bigger and bigger the better you get.
The biggest one Lady Kanao can blow up
is this one.
That's bloody huge!
I'll give it my all!
l
RKJGHERSKJGHSKUJDHF
SDKHFGSDJHF
KJSHERFGKJSRHGKJ
NSREKJHGFSKRJGHSRK
RKJGHERSKJGHSKUJDHF
SDKHFGSDJHF
KJSHERFGKJSRHGKJ
NSREKJHGFSKRJGHSRK
The Next Day
They're not coming today, either?
I'm so sorry.
I'll bring them tomorrow.
Again, I'm really sorry.
No. You need not concern yourself
with those two anymore!
I'll work hard.
I'll work hard!
While throwing myself into the drills
that Master Urokodaki pounded into me,
I'm also trying to maintain my Breathing Technique.
I imagine myself running down the mountain
and race all around the mansion's garden!
All the obstacles are stand-ins
for the trees on that mountain!
Hard work!
l
Fifteen Days Later
RKJGHERSKJGHSKUJDHF
SDKHFGSDJHF
KJSHERFGKJSRHGKJ
NSREKJHGFSKRJGHSRK
RKJGHERSKJGHSKUJDHF
SDKHFGSDJHF
KJSHERFGKJSRHGKJ
NSREKJHGFSKRJGHSRK
I've regained most of my stamina.
And now I can run farther than I could before,
and my lungs are getting stronger!
I'm making good progress!
During the day, I run all over the place and put my lungs into overdrive with swift movements.
So now, I'll breathe in slowly.
Take slow, deep breaths
and send air all the way to my fingertips.
Meditation boosts concentration.
Master Urokodaki said so himself.
Master Urokodaki...
How dare you break my sword!
Please forgive me.
They're reforging my sword for me now,
but I apologize from the bottom of my heart.
Concentrate! You need to concentrate!
Concentrate on your breathing!
Yoo-hoo!
Yes?
I can see you're working very hard.
Even though your friends went off somewhere...
Don't you feel lonely all by yourself?
No! Because once I've mastered it myself,
I can teach them how to do it, too!
You really have a pure soul.
Hey,
why did you take us all here?
Nezuko's situation has officially been acknowledged,
and the three of you were injured so horribly.
And besides that,
I'd like to entrust my dream to you.
Dream?
Yes.
My dream for humans to befriend the demons.
I'm sure that if anyone can
accomplish that, it'd be you guys.
Are you angry?
I always picking up an angry scent from you
even though you're always smiling.
Yes.
You're right.
It might be true that I'm
in a constant state of anger.
Ever since a demon slaughtered my beloved sister.
Every time I see the tears of those
who've lost their loved ones to demons,
every time I hear those cries of despair,
the anger keeps building up
inside me and continues to swell.
Deep down in the innermost depths of my body,
there's a revulsion that I can't fight.
I'm sure the other Hashira feel something similar.
This time they saw Nezuko, who's never
devoured a human, with their own eyes.
And they've memorized her presence.
Out of respect for the Master's wishes,
I doubt anyone would raise a hand to her.
My big sister was a kind-hearted person like you.
She, too, felt sympathy for demons.
Even while on the brink of death,
she never stopped pitying them.
But I was never able to feel that way.
How can you feel sorry
for something that kills humans?
I've yet to hear anything equally ridiculous.
But if that was how my sister truly felt,
then I must carry on that feeling.
If there's to prevent us from
having to kill those pitiful demons,
then I must continue searching for it.
All while preserving that smile my sister loved.
Sister!
But I'm exhausted.
Demons do nothing but lie.
Losing all reason out of self-preservation,
they murder humans with their instincts laid bare.
Tanjirou, please continue doing all that you can.
Please protect Nezuko until the bitter end.
Knowing that you're working so hard
in my place reassures me to no end.
I can rest easier now.
Your Breathing has come to a halt.
I'll do my best.
Total Concentration Breathing!
Mom, Hanako,
Takeo, Shigeru,
Rokuta...
I will turn Nezuko back into
a human no matter what!
I don't want to be imprisoned by sadness
kanashimi ni torewaretaku wa nai
I don't want to come back
utsumuita basho ni
To the place I cast my head down crying
namida wo otoshite yukitakunai
Free from the shackles of fate
unmei wo furihodoite
You're supposed to start running
hashiridaseru hazu nanda
That dream is meant to come true
negai wa kanau hazu nanda
Break free from the troubles of yesterday
tatakitsubuse kinou no katou
Pray for the future from the edge of darkness
Ride the wind that's leading the way
mukai kaze wo nototte
Face the unseen beyond the storm
arashi no saki wa mienaku tatte
There's only one path—
mou michi wa erabenai kachinokore
To make it out alive!
The choice between love and light
mayoi wa itsumo aijou to hikari wo hakari ni kakeru
Will always cast doubt upon your mind
Now rise up once more
saa tachiagarunda mou ichido
Now, where might you strike down
ima kimi wa sono yaiba wo
With that blade of yours?
doko he furiorosu
Demon Slayer
Rustle
PREVIEW
Sniff, sniff! Lady Shinobu,
did something nice happen to you?
Yes! Because I've acquired a precious drug.
Sniff, sniff! Are you angry?
Someone keeps swiping the candy from the shelves.
Sniff, sniff! You're also sad, right?
There's a disturbance in the mountain behind us.
Now, time for a Taisho secret!
Since Aoi has been training under Lady Shinobu,
I hear she can concoct the simpler medicines!
Nothing escapes your nose,
does it, Tanjirou? That's amazing!
PREVIEW
Rustle
Sniff, sniff! For some reason—
Because I enjoy talking with you, Tanjirou.
Thank you so much!
Next, Episode 25, "Tsuguko, Tsuyuri Kanao".
To Be Continued