I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
Demon Slayer
My bewitched heart crusts over by the day
dorodarake no soumatou ni you
Slowly wearing away like an old lantern
kowabaru kokoro
Still clinging to the only bond I have left
furueru te wa tsukamitai mono ga aru
And that's all I need
sore dakesa
The premonition of what darkness lies ahead
yoru no nioi ni
I spent all thirty nights
That I'll never be able to escape
sora nirandemo
Staring into the sky
All I can do is adapt
kawatte ikeru no wa
To the world I now find myself in
jibun jishin dake
And nothing more
sore dakesa
I now know what I cherish most
tsuyoku nareru riyuu wo shitta
So I'll protect this promise 'til the end
boku wo tsurete susume
And I can't afford to stop!
doushitatte
I can’t erase my fantasies
kesenai yume mo
And there's no way to rewind time
tomarenai ima mo
But so long as I have someone left to protect
dareka no tame ni tsuyoku nareru nara
I'll keep rising to my feet as many times as it takes
nandodemo tachiagare
This world once showed me true despair
sekai ni uchinomesarete
Made me wallow in my own failures
makeru imi wo shitta
But now my path is bright and clear
guren no hana yo sakihokore
Overgrown by blood-soaked lotuses
unmei wo terashite
The Final Selection
Episode
The reason I won
was because I learned to detect
the scent of the thread.
When I'm fighting against someone,
and I pick up this scent, I can see the thread.
The thread is connected from my blade
to my opponent's opening,
growing tight the instant I see it.
My blade is drawn towards it with great force,
and I slash through the opening.
Master Urokodaki...
I had no intention of sending you
to the Final Selection.
I didn't want to see more children die.
I was confident you wouldn't be able
to slice through this boulder, but...
Well done, my boy!
Tanjirou, you're
a remarkable kid!
Make sure you come back alive
from the Final Selection.
Both your sister and I will be waiting for you here.
What's the occasion? There's so much.
You've completed your training.
It's a cause for celebration.
Don't be shy. Eat up.
Thank you very much!
Tanjirou,
there's nothing more I can do for you.
From here on out, you will face
much hardship and strife.
Your training will seem like
nothing in comparison.
So, at least for now,
you should rest well without a care in the world.
Hey, Tanjirou...
Yes?
Did you enjoy that hot pot?
Yes! I haven't had such a feast in a long time!
A young lad with a hearty appetite
will grow both bigger and stronger.
But that goes for demons, too.
Remember this.
A demon is as strong as
the number of humans it has devoured.
So the more they eat,
the stronger they get?
That's right.
Some demons gain special powers,
such as being able to morph.
You never know what strange
abilities you'll run into.
When your sense of smell becomes keener,
you'll be able to tell how many humans
a demon has consumed.
What's this?
It's called a "warding mask".
I've imbued it with magic
that protects the wearer from harm.
A warding mask...
Nezuko.
I'll come back no matter what, all right?
Don't worry about your sister.
I'll take good care of her.
All right! Thank you very much!
I'm off, Master Urokodaki!
Say hello to Sabito and Makomo for me!
Tanjirou...
How do you
know the names of those deceased children?
Wow.
Look at all these wisteria flowers.
Even though they're out of season...
There are so many.
Everyone,
we thank you for attending
the Demon Slayers' Final Selection tonight.
Here on Mt. Fujikasane,
the Demon Slayers have captured
a number of demons alive.
They are unable to leave.
That is because wisteria,
which demons hate so much,
blooms year-round from
halfway down the mountain.
However, they don't grow from this point onward,
thus there will be demons about.
To pass the Final Selection, you will
need to survive here for seven days.
And now, be on your way.
Surviving...
That's all I'm gonna think
about for the next seven days.
For starters, I have to survive the night.
Once the sun comes up,
the demons won't be able to do anything.
I can rest up then.
In that case, I'll have to head east!
I'm gonna make my way
to where the sunlight will hit first!
This smell...
It's a demon!
And it's nearby!
Where is it?
Where's it coming from?
I can't pinpoint the direction of the scent!
From above?
A demon...
Damn you!
Don't try to steal my prey, man!
Get off my turf, dammit!
To hell with you! Beat it!
Two of them right from the get-go?
I wonder if I can take them.
That's my prey, y'know!
Shut up!
It's first come, first served!
I'll be fine!
Just calm down and watch their movements!
Remember your training!
It's been ages since I last had human flesh!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
The scent of the thread!
Fourth Form!
Striking Tide!
I did it!
I managed to defeat demons!
I've become stronger!
All that training wasn't for nothing!
I've finally made it!
If I take down a demon with the sword
Master Urokodaki gave me,
not even the bones remain, huh?
A demon's weak spot is its neck!
But even then, a normal sword
won't be enough to kill it.
Then, how do you kill a demon?
The swords wielded by the Demon Slayers
were forged with a special kind of steel.
That's the only way to kill a demon.
They're called "Sun Blades".
Rest in peace.
What's this rotten smell?
No way...
I didn't sign up for this!
What the—
What the hell is that?
Demon Slayer
Hey, Sabito...
Do you think Tanjirou can beat that guy?
I don't know.
No matter how hard you try, it's never enough.
You know that well yourself, don't you?
What's this deformed demon doing here?
They didn't tell us about this!
He got eaten!
Don't be scared!
Save him!
I'm not powerless anymore!
Move!
Water Breathing!
Second Form!
Water Wheel!
Another sweet little fox has come to me.
"Another"?
Little fox cub, what is the year of Meiji now?
It's the Taisho Period now!
Taisho?
What the hell?!
Time has passed into a new period?!
Again! It's happened again while I've been
stuck on this goddamn mountain!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Damn you, Urokodaki! Damn you, Urokodaki!
How do you know Master Urokodaki?
I know him, all right!
He was the one that captured me!
I'll never forget that day,
forty-seven years ago!
Back when he was still hunting demons!
It was the Edo Period during the Keio Era.
Hunting demons? Edo Period?
You're lying!
No demon has ever lived that long!
The only demons in here should be those
who've eaten just two or three humans!
They get killed during the Final Selection,
and they even eat their own kind!
Yeah, but I've survived all this time.
Inside this wisteria prison,
I've eaten at least fifty of you brats.
Fifty?
Eleven, twelve...
Thirteen.
That makes you number fourteen!
What are you talking about?
That's how many of his disciples I've eaten.
I promised myself to kill every single one of them.
Let's see...
There were two in particular that stood out.
Those two...
The more powerful one was a
brat with an unusual hair color.
It was like the color of meat.
He had a huge scar across his cheek.
The other brat was a girl that wore a floral kimono.
She was small and lacking in power, but quite nimble.
They were already killed by this demon?!
But I was with them!
Those fox masks!
All of his disciples wear them.
I'm familiar with the designs Urokodaki carves.
They're the same style as his tengu mask!
Warding masks, right?
I ate them all because of the masks they wore.
They're all here inside my belly.
It's like Urokodaki fed them to me!
When I told that to the girl,
she started crying and fell into a rage.
Her deftness turned into recklessness,
making her much easier to deal with.
I ripped her apart, limb by limb, and then...
Calm down, Tanjirou.
Your breathing's uneven.
It's all right. Never mind us!
I'll make a run for it while
the demon's focused on that guy!
Another one of Urokodaki's brats has died.
I wonder how he'll feel when another kid
doesn't come home again.
What kind of look will he have on his face?
Oh man, I wish I could see it.
I really do.
Tanjirou!
He dodged it?!
So he's still got some life in him?
Great! I get to have some more fun!
Damn it! No matter how many arms I cut,
they grow back in mere seconds!
You can't defeat me just by slashing off my arms.
Then again, even that pink-haired brat
couldn't chop off my head!
I can't just let this go!
I've gotta bring him down now,
before any more lives are sacrificed!
The scent of a demon is coming from the ground?
H-He jumped! Dammit, I missed him!
Sure, but there's no way he can
dodge this attack while in mid-air!
Do you think Tanjirou's going to lose, too?
His neck is so tough after all.
He may lose, and yet, he may win.
Either way, there's one irrefutable fact.
Tanjirou...
is the man who sliced through
the toughest, largest boulder of all.
He deflected it!
Total Concentration!
Water Breathing!
He's gotten too close!
No worries. My neck is tough!
He can't slash through it!
First Form!
As soon as he fails to cut my neck,
I'm going to crush his head!
Just like I did to the other one!
Surface Water Slash!
I don't want to be imprisoned by sadness
kanashimi ni torewaretaku wa nai
I don't want to come back
utsumuita basho ni
To the place I cast my head down crying
namida wo otoshite yukitakunai
Free from the shackles of fate
unmei wo furihodoite
You're supposed to start running
hashiridaseru hazu nanda
That dream is meant to come true
negai wa kanau hazu nanda
Break free from the troubles of yesterday
tatakitsubuse kinou no katou
Pray for the future from the edge of darkness
Ride the wind that's leading the way
mukai kaze wo nototte
Face the unseen beyond the storm
arashi no saki wa mienaku tatte
There's only one path—
mou michi wa erabenai kachinokore
To make it out alive!
The choice between love and light
mayoi wa itsumo aijou to hikari wo hakari ni kakeru
Will always cast doubt upon your mind
Now rise up once more
saa tachiagarunda mou ichido
Now, where might you strike down
ima kimi wa sono yaiba wo
With that blade of yours?
doko he furiorosu
Demon Slayer
Rustle
PREVIEW
Surface Water Slash!
How was that Nezuko?
Aren't I pretty cool?
What? Sabito was cooler than me?
C-Come on, Nezuko!
R-Right!
I saw beautiful wisteria flowers
blooming around the exam grounds.
Let's go see them when you turn back into a human.
Now, it's time for a Taisho secret!
A blond boy named Zenitsu...
I heard he was brought here after he got slapped
by his master for refusing to take the selection exam.
Rustle
PREVIEW
Next, Episode 5, "My Own Steel"!
To Be Continued