Miss Pecorine, you're all right!
What is this place?
This is...
Landosol Castle.
Landosol Castle?
Or at least... I think it is.
But there's no one here, so I can't say for certain.
And this portrait...?
I'm sorry.
There's something I've been hiding from you guys.
My name is...
Eustiana von Astraea.
I'm the princess of Landosol.
But...
Yes, the one everyone calls "Her Majesty"
is named Eustiana, too.
I'm someone...
everyone has forgotten about.
Including my parents.
Eustiana.
Mother!
Father!
At last, it's time.
It's a big world.
Hear the voices of our people with your own ears,
see what this nation is with your own eyes,
and experience it for yourself.
When you complete your journey,
you will have matured enough
to be a ruler worthy of ruling this nation.
Yes.
Eustiana.
Here.
This tiara is one of the royal accessories
handed down in Landosol for generations.
It will surely keep you safe.
The only catch is that using
it will make you very hungry!
I look forward to it! I love to eat!
I'll be off now.
Safe travels.
I got to experience all kinds of things
while travelling around the continent of Astraea.
But when I completed my journey
and returned to Landosol...
Eustiana has returned!
I would like to see my parents!
What are you talking about?!
How dare you utter
Princess Eustiana's name, you ruffian?!
H-Huh? What's happened to all of you?
It's me! Don't you recognise me?
Damn it!
Get her!
Impossible!
Intruder in the castle!
I-I'm sorry...
You're Mother's meal attendant!
It's good to see you again!
It's me, Eustiana—
Is there anyone who remembers me? Anyone?!
It's me! Eustiana!
Does anyone remember me?!
Anyone?!
I've returned home.
I've heard the voices of our
people with my own ears,
and I've seen Landosol with my own eyes.
Does this mean I haven't done enough,
Father, Mother?
Who...
...are you?
It seems a little mouse has
found its way in here,
Father, Mother.
Ah, Eustiana!
Not to worry.
I will exterminate this mouse myself.
I got away from the person
who was using my name
and set out on another journey...
a journey without end.
That's when I met you, Yuuki, and Karyl.
I was so happy. Life was wonderful.
I met all of you,
ate delicious meals with all of you...
But I was always afraid
that everyone would end up forgetting me again...
That the happier I felt, the more
you'd distance yourselves from me.
If I'd told you the truth,
that I was really Eustiana...
I thought...
That's why...
That's why you always
hugged the people important to you.
That way, the connections you had
formed would never go away.
Because I didn't tell the truth...
Because I only looked out for myself...
Because I'm the way I am,
because I'm so selfish...
Karyl left me, too.
I won't leave you.
Whether you're Princess Eustiana or Miss Pecorine,
the days we've spent together as the Gourmet Guild
form an invaluable bond akin to any treasure to me.
I'm sure my lord feels the same way.
And Miss Karyl, as well.
Can we...
Can we stay like this just a little longer?
Dumborine...
I'd say those girls are figuring out
new truths as well right about now.
Please trust me. I'm not your enemy.
Though, I guess I've dragged you too
deep into this to be your ally...
Have I ever.
This space we're in is one I built.
Does it look familiar?
Ameth...
That's right. She goes by "Ameth" now.
She's been trying to help you out, hasn't she?
She's so sweet.
There are signs she's trying to slowly,
carefully restore your memories.
Ready?
This power is for saving your friends,
but it's also a power that can destroy you.
At the moment, you appear
to have lost your memories.
Whether that's caused by the Re:Dive
or not remains unclear.
However, if you unleash this power as you are now,
there's no telling how it would
affect your existence itself.
It probably influenced that earlier fight, too.
Shadows attack people to consume their souls.
They've already wiped out entire villages.
And, more than likely,
they showed up wherever you guys were
in search of more powerful souls.
Those things don't just show up by accident.
The will of someone, or something,
allows them to exist.
As long as you're trapped in this world,
you can never escape that will.
This world came to be as a result of
the battle between you and that will.
You mean...
These memories...
Peco lady!
It's no use! I don't see her!
Quit your whining!
I know she's just fine!
Get your butts into gear and find her!
But where is she?!
Fall back!
This place is still dangerous.
All civilians, stand back!
It's Nightmare!
Shut up!
You always take too long to show up!
You don't have to put it like that!
We're doing our best here!
Hold on, Matsuri.
What good does it do to argue with
the people we're meant to protect?
But...
She's right.
We mustn't lose sight of our goal.
Jun...
Aren't you... the captain of the palace knights?
Captain.
Tomo, did you find anything?
According to witnesses,
there was a swordswoman who fought
to protect the people from the monster.
However, they say she abruptly
disappeared along with the monster.
Disappeared?
Yes.
As for the monster...
It shared many similarities with the
Shadows we've had trouble with recently.
What?
Wow, someone put on quite a show here.
Looks like it was even more powerful
than the one I reported before.
Vice Captain...
A swordswoman who protected the people from
a monster like that with no casualties, eh?
I'm far more interested in that, myself.
Chris, I don't dislike your lack
of concern for what others think,
but you need to focus on your job right now.
My apologies, Captain.
But don't you find it strange?
A monster capable of doing this much damage
found its way into Landosol, the royal capital,
but we didn't find out
until it was already over.
What do you suppose our king is thinking,
deep in that castle of his?
Christina...
Whoops. Just thinking out loud.
Forget what I said.
Oh, while I'm busy thinking out loud anyway...
This is a nation of humans,
so how come we have a beast sitting on our throne?
Rising Tempest!
I'm getting in Her Majesty's way again.
But...
How can I help it?! I can't choose!
Right now, I...
When did I end up like this?
I devoted my entire existence
to Her Majesty alone...
I'm such a fool.
I really am just a fool.
I'm sorry.
You were totally right. I am very selfish.
So...
I want you to help me defeat that monster!
Moron.
Sorry.
I told you too much all at once.
But it's all right.
All of us in Labyrinth will
protect you and your friends.
I'll protect them.
I'll protect my friends.
I took such a long way around
to check up on you in person,
and it looks like it was worth it.
Master, we can't hold out much longer!
Our brother's friends are in trouble!
What should we do? Jump in and help them,
and giving ourselves away to the enemy?
No, looks like everything's fallen into place.
Well then, let's go!
This is my power,
Object Transformation.
I'll lend you just a bit of it
so you can move forward.
I have faith that the bonds you build
will save all of them from this world.
Yuuki?!
Yuuki!
My lord!
Let's go, everyone!
This power...
My magic power...
My lord's feelings...
May the light's blessing be with you!
Princess
Strike!
I hope you're ready for this!
Grim Burst!
Grant my lord a body of steel.
Grant my lord the speed of a falcon.
Now, let us set off!
To victory!
Excellent swordsmanship,
my Princess Knight.
Quit crying, you nincompoops!
But... But...
If Peco lady and
her friends go away...
Don't even say awful things like that!
But, Mama...
If you've got the time to cry,
get your butt to work!
Also, that's "Mom" for you!
Peco lady!
You're okay!
motto tanoshikunacchae
How about we go have some more fun?
yuuwaku saretara
Led purely by instinct alone
Karyl...
me ga te ga tomaranai
Getting more fidgety as our interest rises
haihai mattenaide saa start
Yep, yep!  We're done with the hold up,  let's go!
Thank you for honouring my selfish request.
enryo nante muri da wa
We can't hold ourselves back for much longer
morimori shugi desho
As our curiosity gets the better of us!
That was the last time.
tameshitai desu ne seiippai sukoshi
You're eager and have been consumed too,  right?
Right!
I love you, Karyl!
daitan ni arekore wo
By the flames of passion for adventure
bouken shitai n desu everyday
We're all set and ready to face our adventure of the day
dakara tobidashite
So let's go, rush out!
tobidashite ii yo ne
No holding back!
minna sore ga daisuki
That's the ideal way to go!
Connecting Happy!!
tsunagaru omoi de
Fully embracing each other's feelings
itsumo kimi to ima wo kanjitetai na
Experiencing every second the day has to offer together
dayo ne da ne
Right?  Of course!
doko ni itemo atsumacchae dakara ne
We're stuck together like glue
minna de kyou wa oishii mono demo
Sharing and indulging in all the delicacies we stumble across
tabete tabeta ato de
Savouring each and every last one of  'em
mata raran ue to doka e
As runaways from responsibility
Runaway
On fate's runway!
sorezore no hoppeta ga happy
Cheeks brimming with happiness!
Bread really is best with runny eggs!
It sure is!
It makes me feel the joy of a fresh morning.
Your appetite has grown quite healthy, my lord.
I'm so happy.
That's right.
He's not the little beansprout
he was when we first met.
Mhm!
What's the plan today?
That's easy!
What's the goal of the Gourmet Guild?
The study of all the delicious food in this world!
Right!
Well, let's get going!
It's time for a new adventure!