Wait! Please, wait!
Father... Mother...
Who...
...are you?
So... hungry...
The Whimsical Patissier's Specialty
A Memory of Labyrinths and Crêpes
Everyone! I fried up some eggs
I got first thing this morning!
Did you remember to leave them runny?
Of course!
So you went to the market earlier this morning.
Miss Karyl?
Hold on.
Something's missing!
There's no bread to sandwich
these tasty-looking eggs between!
Exactly! I'm glad you noticed, Karyl!
That's exactly what I wanted to
talk to you all about!
Ta-dah!
When I went to the market,
there weren't many goods for sale.
I asked around and found out that a monster's
made its nest on the bridge leading into town.
They can't transport flour and other goods,
and it's been affecting everyone.
That's terrible.
If the authorities...
It would help a lot if Landosol took action,
but for some reason the royal palace won't do anything.
And when I went to the
Guild Association, I found this quest.
And I'd really like to do it...
Let me check the rank.
Let. Me. Check.
The hell?!
What's your deal?!
Don't just take such scary quests
for us first thing in the morning!
Please, Karyl, don't be like that!
Everyone's in great need right now!
Oh, I know!
If you do it, I'll cuddle you awake every day!
No, thank you!
God, noooo!
Even if we beat him, it will amount to nothing
if we damage the bridge in the process.
So first thing first, we need to lure him away.
How, exactly?
My shoulder guards grant a massive defence boost,
so we could have someone
lure him away while wearing them.
It'll take a lot to hurt you with those on.
Damn it, Dumborine!
You knew we couldn't count on Korosuke,
or even that dunce, Yuuki, to do it!
Why am I, the smart one, being put up with
acting as bait? Screw you, you idiot!
Despite all that, she still volunteered to
act as a decoy! I'm smitten!
Here they come.
Since it's running so fast,
we'll trap its feet and make sure it can't move.
Dumborine!
This is the last time I go along with
your oh, so brilliant ideas, y'hear me?!
Thanks, Karyl!
I'll take care of it for good!
Princess Strike!
We did it!
Now the people of Landosol
can eat their fill again!
Karyl, Yuuki, Kokkoro...
Thank you so much!
Hey!
S-Stop hugging me!
Let me go!
I've confirmed that you did truly complete
the Elder Horn subjugation quest.
And with that, please fill out this paperwork.
Good thing Korosuke was so patient
with teaching you, huh?
No, this is purely my lord's own efforts paying off.
You've worked hard, Yuuki.
Never in a hundred years did I imagine Yuuki
would be the one submitting a guild activity report.
Oh, my?
My apologies, but this part is wrong.
Sheesh... So close, yet so far.
Don't just play it cool if you're
unsure about something. Just ask.
Just jolting down random scribbles won't do.
uki
Today's yet another beautiful day!
Peco lady!
Hi, Ikacchi and Charlie!
We heard you just took out a monster!
Awesome as always!
Huh? How do you know about that?
Well, I mean...
There you are!
Yasuko?
I've been looking all over for you!
I heard you took out that monster for us!
We can finally stock up again thanks to you!
We were clueless about what to do
since we couldn't get any fresh stock in.
Thank you so much!
I'm glad to hear that!
Everyone can eat delicious food again!
Everyone was happy.
Yeah!
Landosol should always be full
of smiling faces, after all!
They were thanking you, too, Miss Karyl.
That really ain't my thing.
Are you hungry?
Let's stop for a light afternoon dessert!
Light?
Here we are!
This is...
...where we came on our first day in Landosol.
Oh? You two have eaten here before?
Charlie told me about this place,
but it seems they get little business,
despite their crêpes being so delicious.
I'd even call it a little-known treasure!
Ah, yes! Welcome... er...
What's wrong, Rino?
Don't be rude to our customers... er...
What's going on? You two sound like
a pair of chickens being strangled.
Oh, what do we have here?
Long time, no see.
Not biting coins anymore, are you?
Money. Important.
Good. Glad to hear it.
The crêpes we had when we came
here before were truly delicious.
Why, thank you!
And these two are...?
Friends.
That's a nice picture.
Anyway, I need to go take care of some things.
Hold down the fort here!
On it!
Come, now!
Since you're our little brother's guildmates,
it's on the house today!
Feel free to eat all you like!
You mean it?!
PriConne
Shizuru! I can't fry fast
enough to keep up with her!
I'm running out of the
fruits we use for toppings!
But we mustn't complain!
We told her
it was on the house!
Is their stall gonna be okay?
Delicious.
Hey, guys!
We really got to indulge today!
It's all thanks to you, Yuuki!
We'll be back sometime.
W-We did it, Shizuru.
We made him happy.
Seeing my little brother smile is... the... best...
Yuuki! Yuuki, keep it together!
Was that...?
A dream? No.
I should've known he wouldn't forget that.
Deeper memories within you
have begun awakening
because you've been forming
so many bonds with people.
Listen well. What you saw was
both a dream and reality.
It may be a past you've relived over and over,
or it may be the future.
The time is drawing nearer.
I'm sorry for pushing you so many times,
but there was no other way.
I have faith in you, Yuuki.
Sword training?
Oh, finally clicked that you're
supposed to be a swordsman, huh?
Mhm.
All right, if you insist.
Don't put too much force into it.
Feel the sword's weight.
That's it. Relax and do what comes naturally.
He's really getting into this.
Is that...?
All of my lord's efforts thus far
will surely come to fruition now.
He's been working tirelessly every single day.
Keep it up, Yuuki!
You can't go to war on an empty stomach!
Everything starts with a good meal,
so make sure you eat plenty.
Okaywmph.
You show so much promise, my lord.
Anyway, Karyl is awfully late.
She said she'd go run an errand first.
We're gonna run out of food.
Let's order the same things again once she gets here!
You're joking, right? Did you really
see Princess Eustania?!
Landosol's been ruled by
its princesses for generations, ye?
So, what was she like?
Well, I only caught a brief glimpse,
but royalty sure have this... what, dignity?
They just radiate dignity.
She's got that kind of beauty that
leaves you with goosebumps!
Ah, imagine if she were as nice to us
lowly peasants as she was beautiful.
Right, not like she cares about us.
If she did, this town wouldn't be
the lawless place it is now.
It's been quite a while
since we came to Landosol,
but we haven't had an opportunity
to see the princess yet.
As someone who grew up in the countryside,
she seems like a character in a fairy tale.
I wonder what she's like.
Here.
No fighting over it, now.
Well, guess it's time for me to get some lunch, too...
Hey, Karyl!
Hiya!
You're going out to eat? Perfect timing!
We're on our way to get some drinks!
We'll go with you, Karyl!
You two do nothing but drink, don't you?
Gulp!
Do you actually work?
O-O-O-Of course!
We do this and that and all kinds of stuff!
That's...
That's the spirit, Yuuki!
What was that sound?
Let's go check!
Miss Pecorine!
Are you okay?
Peco lady!
We've got trouble! There's a monster in Landosol!
Karyl was with us, but we lost sight of her!
What are the palace knights doing?!
I'm sorry.
Look after this child for me.
I have to protect this town
and everyone in it.
You got it!
I'm done for!
Tome!
You imbecile! Don't give up so easily!
I'm really done for!
Yasuko!
Aren't the palace knights here yet?!
Before I go, there's something
I always meant to tell you...
What about the princess?!
What is Princess Eustania doing?!
Tome?!
I...
Tome!
Yasuko, I've always...
Tome?
Tome!
Ow, ow, ow...
Tome! Are you okay?!
Yasuko, please get away from here!
I'll handle this!
What are you saying?! That monster will—
I'll be fine. Trust me!
Go, quickly!
Don't do anything crazy!
Pecorine!
Karyl! I'm glad to see you're okay!
Please help me protect all these people!
Karyl?
Full power! Full throttle!
Princess Strike!
Miss Pecorine saves the day again.
My Princess Strike...
...didn't work?
Miss Karyl! Miss Pecorine!
Are you all right, Karyl?
Pecorine!
Wait, this is...
That shoulder guard will protect you, Karyl.
Stop it! No one asked you to do this!
This isn't what I—
Why...
Why do you...
Just to help other people...
Pecorine!
Idiot... You idiot...
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Why go out of your way to save the weak?
Just ignore them!
Why'd you cover for me?
After I
was ready to abandon you...
You're so...
I've had it.
I can't keep this up any longer.
Miss Pecorine!
I'll cast healing magic right away!
My lord!
Pecorine?
Karyl?
Kokkoro?
No need to be worried.
I tucked them all away somewhere safe.
Hey.
The crêpe lady...
That's right. I run the crêpe stall.
But that's just...
a front I use to conceal my identity.
Is this...
the inside of a castle?
Miss Pecorine?
I always yearn for those times long gone
kodomo no koro ni akogareta
When we good-for-nothings gathered together
ki no ue no koya to aikotoba
Playing around in the treehouse for just the two of us
ochikobore ga atsumarette
And going on our very own adventures
oya ni naisho de bouken suru
While our imaginations may have varied so much
omoiegaiteta mono to wa zenzen nitemo nitsukanaikedo
Simply mimicking the way you acted
ashi wo hippariai nagara
Always put a grin on my face
kimi to aruiteiku
Tomorrow too
asu mo kitto
We might bump heads
butsukatte
Maybe have a fight or two
kenka suru darou
Even so, we're inseparable
soredemo nao
Because you'll forever be a dear friend to me
boku wa kimi wo tomodachi to yobu
So I hope we'll make up this time too
umaku nakanaori dekiru kana
Lost Princess
Garnished with Smiles
To be continued!