The sky was clad in the crimson of the star burning itself out
sora ha akaku somari hoshi ha moete tokedasu
A pure tranquility has subsumed everything
tsumiageta hibi nado mizu ni shizumu konoha no you
Justice and destiny have long since forsaken this world
eien no seigi nado sudeni konoyo ni ha nai
nou de ugomeiteru kono kankaku wo shinjite
No one’s left to guide you but you yourself
A blazing storm blows over the desolate land
kuzureyuku kono chihei wo
Scorching all in its path
yaketa kaze ga fukinuketeyuku
Tears alone aren’t enough to extinguish these roaring flames
namida nagasu dake ja kitto yoake ha konai
So prepare to set out with me
dakara kimi to
We’ll cross the endless seas together
senoku no umi wo koeteyukou
Let your heart be your compass
konpasu mo sutete
Hold your sense of justice close
seigi nara mune ni areba ii to
As you blaze your path through this chaos
konton wo susume