Listen up, Kabane!
I’m a Kabaneri!
I don’t give a damn!
I am...
I’ll always be me!
Someday we’ll wake from this dreamy sense of hope
itsukawa suteru just as dream karino kibouzou
Until then we cling to this hollow, frozen ray of light
kanzenna close kootta senkou
Confined within this iron cage
torikagono nai kaitou
What meaning can we find behind our lives
kikaiteki kanjyouni akita life
If our minds are no better than a machine’s?
hitono seijya tsumaranai
Go full steam ahead
Go steam ahead with your soul
And let your soul scream out loud
And scream it out
The gleam in your fervid eyes
A gleam in your fervid eye
Shows not even an ounce of doubt
There ain’t no doubt
Shoot ’em off!
What you holdin’ off for?
What you holdin’ on for?
You’re not an underdog
Keep goin’ and find your way
Keep findin’ your way
Boost ’em up!
What you holdin’ off for?
What you holdin’ on for?
Let’s go and lose control
Let’s get out of control
Keep that flame burnin’ strong
Keep burnin’ your flame
FEELING
Kabaneri of the Iron Fortress: Revolt
Beginning Tracks